Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
Translation & initial timing
Vegapunk Fansubs
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
Timing
Galaxy 9000
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Quality checking
Sewil
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Editing
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Perona's Wonder Garden and
the Charge of the General Zombies!
No matter where they try to run, track them down and drag them here!
No one can match the Zombie Generals!
Hey, stop wasting time, Captain John.
You're really not living up to your lifetime's infamous reputation.
Okay, okay. I'm going.
Geez... he never changes...
Ab-sama...
Marry me!
Lola!
You...! Go and fight this instant!
I'm your commander here!
Then, marry me.
Why would I?!
Lola... what're you...?!
Aren't you gonna listen to the Grave Ab-sama orders?!
Then, marry me!
Stop joking!
I'm a human!
I need to have a human bride!
Hey, Lola... think about it.
You're a female warthog zombie.
You're dead and rotting!
Stop it!
Hey, what a terrifying method!
Isn't that a marriage certificate?!
To think you're forcing me to marry you!
I can't resist that wild muzzle of yours.
Absalom, give me your finger.
I love you!
Don't mess around!
I don't wanna spend my days being haunted by a dead animal!
Bridal Arts...
Oath Kiss!
Wait, Lola!
Listen carefully.
I've already...
I've already chosen the woman who'll be my bride!
She certainly has a strong temper, but she's a weak, flesh and blood woman in the end!
You'll fail again anyways.
Idiot, look!
She's one of the pirates who landed on this island, perfectly suited to become this handsome man's bride.
I won't let it happen!
That woman...
I'll get rid of her!
Wait!
Lola!
Hey, Kumashi!
Kumashi!
The Risky Brothers are bringing a coffin here.
When you receive it, send it to the master's Dance Hall!
Is that clear?
Is that clear or not?!
Yes...
Don't answer, it's not cute!
From now on, I'll be commanding the treasure collecting group toward the ship.
If anything happens, come and tell me, got it?
That's it, when you don't say anything, you're so cute!
H-Have a nice trip...
You! You talked just now!
Take it there! Take it there! To the master's lair!
Oh no! We dropped it!
Oh no! We broke it!
The delivery for our master!
The coffin opened up!
Where am I?
He's awake!
Damn it!
Hurry and hit him! Beat him to death!
Killing is bad!
Then, half-kill!
Half-kill!
Usopp!
Nami!
Hey, hang in there!
Wake up!
The samurai... certainly...
Did he strike us with the back of the blade?
It seems it was raining here.
The ground is a little wet.
Where are we?
I don't know, but...
Just now those squirrels were carrying us to be delivered in that coffin.
Isn't this an iron coffin?!
Oh no, those three are awake!
This is bad. Call our comrades!
It looks like... we're currently behind the mansion.
Hogback's laboratory was on the top floor.
They've already carried us a long way it seems.
Hey, look behind you!
There's a sturdy building on the opposite side!
What's that?
There was such a huge building behind the mansion all this time?
I've figured out where we are!
What is it?
What do you mean?
We're on the passage that connects the mansion to that huge building.
Passage?
It's so wide, almost like a forest.
Even if it's been made a forest, they were carrying our coffin here while we were unconscious.
That means, they had to have been carrying us to that building.
That's probably the place where zombies are made.
I'm glad we woke up!
Let's run!
That's right! Let's run, right away!
Wait a minute!
We didn't get any treasure because we got scared and started running around screaming...
Is that alright?
What're you thinking, idiot?!
My "Something is wrong"-sensor is having a huge response!
Let's just run away, Nami!
That's right! That's right!
I clearly remember what the zombie said back then.
Let's run! Let's run!
What a shame!
The treasure storehouse isn't here!
Stop thinking useless stuff, let's run!
Let's run, Nami!
How stupid!
I finally understand! I was just too scared at the time!
Weird looking eyes!
Then, where do we run?
Forward?
Back?
That's one hard decision.
If we go back to the mansion, we'll most likely run into that samurai again.
But, we might run into scarier guys if we head forward.
What're these little animals?
Penguins?
Numbers!
One!
Two!
Three!
No...
Greetings, we're...!
The Penguin Zombie Combi-
Ah, I got it wrong.
Trio! We're a trio!
I'm the new guy!
Like we care about that kinda member info!
And behind you all are...
No way...
Our comrades, the Wild Zombies!
Welcome to Perona-sama's Wonder Garden!
More strange creatures came out!
Alright then, let's get 'em!
Usopp!
Fire!
Fire?
Use fire! These guys are zombies!
Deadly...
Usopp!
Chopper!
Watch out, behind you!
Usopp...
Chopper...
You're in the same situation!
Stop!
Bastard! What're you doing to your comrade!
Your enemy is that woman!
She's the one you should beat!
I have no idea who this lady might be or where she came from...
But even if it goes against master's orders...
Even if I die...
I won't hurt a woman!
If you've a problem with that, bring it on!
Damn Zombies!
Hey! What's wrong?!
Hey Piglet!
You did something again, didn't you?!
Spit it out!
I told you from the start that I don't know anything.
And you're laughing now.
What an obvious fella.
How strange...
Not even a scream.
I wonder if they were strangled to death...
Why is your train of thought always so dark?!
How weird...
Even Zoro's disappeared.
Where did they go?!
It can't be helped with Zoro and Sanji!
What're you doing at a time like this?!
Hey! I found the armor lying in there!
Isn't it a man's romance to wear it?!
No way!
R-Romance?!
Of course!
When you gained that iron body, did you change your heart to iron as well?
Please forgive me!
I never intended to go so far as to change my heart to iron!
When you lose something important, a foreboding wind blows through your heart.
Please listen...
"The Heart of a Steely Cyborg Traveler"
Are these guys aware of the current situation?
Hey.
We've come to a large hall.
Really?
Robin, are Usopp and the others there?!
I don't think so.
This hall's interior looks like the outside...
What's with this place?!
It's as if it were an arena.
It's not that simple.
You better resign yourselves.
It's impossible for you to escape from here!
Franky!
Who is it?!
A moving suit of armor!
No doubt it's a zombie.
It's moving even with those spears in its body.
Just 'cause zombies are well equipped...
I won't be scared...!
Strong Right!
The wall was...!
Since it uses fencing...
Weapons Left!
Franky was...!
It'll take more than that to kill me!
Especially for a corpse like you!
He's still getting up.
The latch won't open.
He's completely different from the zombies we've seen so far.
Soon you'll understand!
That's what makes them really terrifying!
That guy, speaking from that far!
They don't feel pain!
Every single one of those armed General Zombies made a name for themselves in battle.
They're unbending warriors!
The leader of a country's knights who turned into a brutal criminal.
A legendary samurai, a pirate, a gunslinger!
Imagine those men after they've become invulnerable!
There's no way someone like you could beat them!
Even now your friends are in peril!
Serves you right!
You bastard!
Wall zombie!
Got it!
He's closed off the path!
That's not the only path that was closed.
Speaking from my experience...
This will be more than just tough.
It's full of armor!
There's no point in fighting them one by one, as our attacks don't harm them.
And we'll just be overwhelmed if we try to face them all straight on.
I see.
You're right, it's not like this is our last battle.
If we run straight ahead from this hall, we'll probably reach the courtyard.
Alright! Then, the three of us will meet up in there.
Be careful not to let anyone else disappear.
Of course.
Get 'em!
Let's go!
Move!
Phoenix of the Thirty-six Earthly Desires!
This technique...!
Zoro!
A scar on the back is a shame for a warrior!
Yet I'm covered with scars!
Who're you?
I thought you were Zoro.
My name is Jigoro!
You're exactly like him!
This is what you use against zombies!
Fresh Fire!
Prepare the buckets!
What?!
Once Fleur!
Eleven flowers
Slam!
Where's Luffy?!
It seems he hasn't come out yet.
Even if we went back, it'd be hard to find that idiot because he's wearing that armor!
Could he have disappeared as well?!
But we can't patiently wait for him.
The zombies will be here in no time!
Hey! Straw Hat!
That hurt, bastard! Let me out!
What the...?
Bastards, let me out, damn it!
It's not fun, damn it!
Open the lid!
A-A coffin?!
Let me out immediately!
Let me out, I'll kick your ass!
That voice just now...!
Let me out!
Hey, I'm telling you to let me out!
Luffy!
No way...!
Is Straw Hat inside of that thing?!
After him, Nico Robin!
What the hell is he doing?!
He let himself get caught!
Straw Hat!
You're not following him!
Hey, hey! Monkey! Monkey! Monkey!
I'm the widely rumored Spider Monkey!
A gigantic spider!
This thing's size exceeds that of average insects! It's a monstrous spider!
Let me out I tell you, idiot!
Open the li-
Ah! Another one.
Damn, the coffin...!
Bastard, what're you gonna do with him?!
Don't worry.
Whatever happens to him, you will also learn firsthand.
You should be worrying about yourselves...
Before you is me, and behind you are the armored soldiers!
With this your crew will be...
Annihilated!