Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for... One Piece!
Compasses and the like will only slow us down
Translation & initial timing
VS
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
Quality-checking
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Even an old treasure map covered in dust...
Isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
Soundtracking
Halee
For our own storms, all we have to do is
Video editing
Sewil
Raw provider
SOFCJ-Raws
Ride someone else's biorythm...
And pretend that it isn't there!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
and go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Let's break the tight-fisted night!
We have no interest in treasure chests
A pocket of romance, and
We are!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Brook's Past!
The Rumbar Pirates and Laboon!
Alright, close it.
Are you sure? What about Perona?
We looked, but we couldn't find her, so there's nothing we can do.
Okay, it's fine now. Invisibility off!
A magnificent escape, fosfos!
Damn, but my knees were shaking back there...
I don't understand what "Tyrant Kuma" was doing on Thriller Bark...
Well, you see, Absalom...
Tyrant Kuma came to deliver the news about the successor of the former Warlord Crocodile. {Sewil: changed from "Tyrant Kuma came to deliver the news about the former Warlord, Crocodile's successor."}
His successor?
But that wasn't the most important part.
Apparently, it's a guy called Blackbeard,
but what's really scary is what the guy's pulled off!
Read this.
The commander of the Second Division of the Whitebeard Pirates, Fire Fist Ace...
...has been captured and taken to the great prison, Impel Down?!
Ace... he's famed as one of Whitebeard's best men...
The government's gotten themselves an incredible card...
Indeed...
They could easily try to use this to bring about the end of the Age of Pirates...
In this kind of situation, there's no time for Moriah-sama to just lie here!
Well, I understand what you're trying to say...
But I just...
Want a bride...
Right. Just get me a corpse that's your type.
Not a zombie! I want a real, living woman!
Man, I guess we ended up all sleeping a whole day right out there in the courtyard...
Well, ya know, we did stay up that whole night fighting!
The day after Moriah's defeat
I'm hungry, Sanji!
Go eat some cheese or something!
Cheese isn't good enough! I can't run on cheese!
Well, why don't you take the cooking stuff over to the courtyard?
The Victims' Association guys don't want to leave the place,
so we're all gonna eat over there.
Sorry about that! Everybody's so happy to finally be in the sun after all these years...
They're all just lying there sunbathing!
But, how can you be in such a good shape anyway?
It's totally strange. It's a mystery!
Do you have enough ingredients?
We got back what was stolen from us...
What's more, we even got a mountain of extra food, so we're fine.
But who brought that, I wonder... I guess there are some kind people here too.
They even brought all the treasure here...
Even if this was Christmas, this really is too much!
I'm so happy...
Wow, a glass bracelet!
Oh, this is cool! I'll take it!
Hey, hey, you can't just go around taking it like that, you know... R-Right, Nami-san...?
It's fine. If it's just that one, it's not even all that valuable.
So that's how it is...?
However! I'm not giving you a single bit of it!
We're not gonna steal anything from the ship of our saviors, you know, Namizou.
Ahh! What a cool knife!
What did you just say?!
Oh, I'm sorry! Oh, but it's got jewels in it...
Huh? I just spoke without thinking... Who's Namizou?
Come to think of it, isn't it odd?
It kinda feels like I've seen you before somewhere...
Could it be...
Lola?!
That's right... Did I even tell you my name?
So it was you, Lola?!
I'm so glad I got to see you again!
Lola, you mean...
Whoa, hey! Wait a second!
Could she really be that boar-zombie?!
You don't remember, huh? I'll tell you all about it later!
Anyway...
I'll give you this! As a sign of my gratitude!
Huh? Is that alright? To me?!
Nami is giving treasure away!
I'm going on ahead, you think this will be enough?
A storm is coming!
Huh, a storm? Seriously?
Ah, this is bliss...
The light is... Hitting me, and...
We're still alive...
We are...
Hey!
Huh?
We've brought food!
Straw Hat!
You should have asked us, we would've carried it!
We can't have our saviours working like this!
Is Zoro awake yet?
He's still sleeping like a log... He's in the mansion.
Hey, wake up!
Chopper!
We've brought the stuff you asked for!
Oh, thanks!
How is he?
This is the first time Zoro's been this badly injured...
He was really close to dying...
I just know it... Something must have happened to him...
While we were unconscious...
Indeed. It's hard to believe that that man would just leave like that.
It's also weird that Luffy is so energetic all of a sudden, isn't it?
I have no idea how that happened either!
What happened, huh?
Actually, I saw it all!
I saw all of it, too!
We'll tell you!
It's about what happened back then! {Halee: Added "It's" at the beginning of the sentence so that it doesn't sound too weird when connected to the previous one.}
Come.
Sanji?
Wait, why? You were pretty cool too, you know!
"Take my life instead of the swordsman's", you know?
Shut up! Hurry up and tell me.
What happened afterwards?
After I fainted, I mean.
Well, that Warlord had another crazy power, you see!
He just put his paw on Straw Hat,
and repelled all of the damage that had been inflicted on him!
Damage...?
Like a huge ball of agony!
Just touching a tiny bit of it, that swordsman screamed in pain!
Sorry, but I seriously thought that swordsman was gonna die.
So, we actually cried!
We cried a lot!
I see... Then, that's why Luffy is in perfect shape, while Zoro ended up like that...
How reckless...
Nothing... happened...
All right! We've gotta tell the rest of the crew this beautiful tale-
Wait! Don't you go running your mouths off with that stuff!
He didn't risk his life so that we'd praise him about it.
And besides...
How do you think Luffy would feel if he knew all that pain he took on himself had gone and hurt his friend?!
Just don't say anything!
As long as everyone is safe, that's all that matters.
Well, I'm gonna go eat.
T-T-T-
They're super cool!
What a lucky captain!
I see.
Hey, you two.
You said you knew something earlier, right?
What did you see?
Don't go askin' us that stuff.
Everyone's safe... that's all that matters.
I... I want to say it!
T-The beautiful tale of what a man had to endure!
W-What?
Let's eat!
So good!
I've never eaten anything so good!
We haven't eaten a proper meal in years!
I'm so happy to be alive!
I've made plenty!
Don't go leaving leftovers, you hear?!
I am so glad I got to eat your food again, Cook-san!
It is so good, I could continue until my stomach burst!
Even though I do not have a stomach!
You! Shut up and eat!
What a funny skeleton!
Indeed, ah, excuse me.
Being able to eat to my heart's content yesterday, and again today... I think...
I might be getting fat!
"Even if I'm just bones!", right?! Shut up, you!
Skeleton, you're the best!
Hey, how can you move, anyway?
Oh, who cares?
We didn't even toast, but it turned into a party anyway, huh?
He's not waking up even with this much noise...
Even though he's usually the toughest one here...
Hey, Chopper! This...
Luffy!
...is Zoro's share!
Now, drink up!
Don't make him drink that!
What's with you?! Zoro likes this stuff, so it should make him better, right?!
What kind of medicine is that?!
I can't?
Then, how about meat?
Okay, okay! Thanks for the sentiment, that's enough!
Just the sentiment, okay?
There was a piano in this room?
Hey, weren't you a violinist?
I can play any instrument you like!
I see... You're pretty good.
Um, about that conversation earlier...
The truth is, I saw it all, too.
I was deeply touched by what the two of you did.
It sure is nice to have friends, isn't it?
Don't bother saying "the two of you"... I just ended up looking like an idiot.
No, you were just as prepared as he was.
Is there any song you'd like to hear?
If you have a request...
Huh? Anything goes?
Then, how about...?
Yo-hohoho, Yohohohoo,
What happened to asking for requests?
Going to deliver Binks' Sake!
"Binks' Sake"... I think I know this song from somewhere... It's very nostalgic...
Following the sea breeze! Riding on the waves!
Hey, Brook! I know this song!
Shanks and his crew used to sing it.
Back in the old days, every pirate would sing this song.
Through hard times, and fun times...
Say, you're gonna come with us... right?
You got your shadow back, right?
So even though the sun rises, you can still travel, can't you?
Speaking of that... there is one thing I did not tell you...
What?
I have... a promise I made with a friend.
First, I have to fulfill that promise.
Otherwise... I could not call myself a man.
Yeah... Laboon, right? I know. Franky told me.
Is that so? Laboon...
That is indeed the name of that whale...
He is waiting for me at that cape...
Like I was trying to say, Brook...
We met Laboon at the twin capes! It's true!
I already know that Laboon has been waiting for his friends to return there for fifty years now.
Hey, skeleton! What's wrong?
You're not playing the piano as quickly anymore!
It was a real surprise...
We never thought that the last surviving one of the pirates he was waiting for...
Would actually turn out to be you!
And... You still remember the promise, too!
Once he finds out, I'm sure Laboon will be really happy!
Wait... Wait a minute, please.
What a surprise!
Out of the blue... are you telling me you really... met Laboon?!
Yeah!
Even after fifty years has passed?!
Laboon is still waiting at that cape, even now?!
Is that true?!
Yeah!
We can vouch for it too! We really met him.
Yeah.
How was he doing?
He was doing great!
He was big as a mountain.
That I must see... back when we left him behind, you know...
He was still only the size of a small boat... He was rather cute...
He could be a little difficult sometimes,
but he loved music... he was a good kid...
Even now... If I close my eyes, I can see his face...
He is still there...
So, that's how it is...?
So, he is still fine?
I have never been so happy before...
What's with this whale? He's following the ship...
Must've got separated from his herd, huh...? Poor little thing... The ocean's a big place...
He looks so sad... And he's still just a kid, isn't he?
Well then, Captain Yorki... Shall we sing a song?
Brook! Great idea!
Hey, everyone, get your instruments!
We can bring a smile to even a crying child's face!
Let's show him what the Rumbar Pirates can do!
Okay!
One, two, three, four!
Rumbar Pirates
Musician, swordsman
Hi, good day, everyone! It's morning!
Brook
(50 years ago, 38 years old)
Let us start singing our morning song!
And the power-tune we will be bringing you this week is...
That famous song,
"Black Handkerchief of Happiness"!
Everyone, feel free to join in!
Oh, white handkerchief
Don't let him find you!
Run away
Oh, white handkerchief
Don't let the octopus get you!
Watch out for the ink! Look, there's a squid as well! That's the ink again!
P-Please stop making that noise so early in the morning!
We're getting up! We're getting up, Brook!
Oh, white handkerchief
Ugh, we're awake! We're awake!
It's the all inked Black Handkerchief of Happiness
Hey, Brook! Try playing that song as a ballad!
Understood! The captain's favorite song!
It's the whale!
Hey... you're that little guy from yesterday...
You still hanging around? Go look for your pod!
So cute!
Hey, how long is he going to keep following us?
I'm sure his mom is worried!
Here, have some food, Laboon!
Whoa, whoa, since when does the thing have a name?
We're under attack!
Are you alright?!
Help us! This guy has got a damaged leg!
Captain! An injured man fell into the sea!
Just throw out the life buoy!
We'll have to help him afterwards!
I suppose that is all I can do, seeing how I can not swim...
You saved us, Laboon!
Hey! We're fine!
Oh, Laboon!
Alright, everyone sing! We're singing "that song"!
You must be freezing, right?
Treasure! We found it, Laboon!
We're gonna have a real feast today!
We did it!
A sea monster appeared!
Protect Laboon!
Yeah!
He likes you most, doesn't he, Brook?
After all, Laboon loves music.
Nah, it's probably because your heads have the same shape!
Ah, I see.
You... can't you do anything about it?
We've all tried telling him, but...
He won't listen to us, it seems.
You understand, right?
I don't think we're strong enough to protect him if we take him any further...
He's just a kid.
We can't take him with us to the Grand Line.
Please listen to what I have to...
No, the song will have to wait.
We certainly are comrades, but you are just a whale...
The Grand Line is a dangerous sea! Really!
Listen, you're a big kid now...
but there are beasts out there like nothing we've ever seen here in West Blue...
Laboon, listen to...
No use. He refuses to listen.
It didn't work, huh?
Then how about a song first?
Let's sing that song.
That would only make it worse, I think...
This is no good... I know it's hard,
but we've gotta turn our backs on him, okay?
Until Laboon leaves the ship, we're not gonna sing or play any music.
We'll be thrown overboard at this rate, captain!
Look at that! That's our guidelight, pointing to the entrance of the Grand Line!
Can anyone see Laboon?!
No, we haven't seen him for a week!
I feel sorry for him, but this was for the best.
If he's lucky, he might be able to return to his family.
Men, are you prepared?!
Yeah! We're ready!
Then let's go! To the world's largest ocean!
Yeah!
I'm the lighthouse-keeper, Crocus. Good job making it over Reverse Mountain.
Welcome to the Pirate Graveyard.
Grand Line Entrance
Twin Capes
Hey, hey, this isn't some kind of show, you know!
Back in West Blue, I'm known as "Calico Yorki".
Sorry to bother you, Crocus-san, but...
Well, our ship got pretty damn beat up back there...
You may stay as long as you wish, but I'll ask you
to help with the food and drinks while you're here.
Man, you're something! Sponging off pirates, huh?
Sure, sounds fair. Why don't you join us in our celebrations?
Today, we're all gonna throw a huge party!
By the way, that whale that came with you, is that your pet?
Laboon!
Brook!
Hey, Brook! Let's sing that song!
Captain, you really love that song, don't you?
Yeah! It's the song of pirates!
Laboon! You love that song too, right?
Yohohoho, yohohoho
Going to deliver Binks' sake
Following the sea breeze, riding on the waves
Crocus-san. Do you have a request?
Far across the salty deeps, the merry evening sun
Anything goes, huh, Brook?
Pirates love singing!
Painting circles in the sky, birds singing along
Farewell to the harbour, to my old hometown
Let's all sing out with a DON, as the ship sets sail
3 months later
Please understand.
Laboon! Wait for us! Our ship is gonna sail straight ahead, and cross this sea.
It might sound strange, but we'll end up on the other side of the Red Line again...
And then we'll climb this wall once again, and return to this cape!
You just wait for that!
It should take about two or three years,
and after that, you'll see us all again!
When that time comes, you should have grown big and strong!
See you later, Laboon! Stay well!
Laboon! When that time comes, no matter where we go, you can come with us on our adventures again!
We're comrades, after all!
Laboon! We'll definitely travel around the world, and come back here!
Wait for us!
Three years later
The Florian Triangle
Hey, Brook! Your techniques are incredible!
Can you also teach me how to use a sword?
A tornado?! But it was clear and sunny just a minute ago!
Anyway, let's run! Common sense won't work on this sea!
Man... now that we're actually here, this place really is unpredictable... Can we really hold up?
Ah, but hey, a rough day just makes the sake at the end taste all the sweeter! Ain't that right, Brook?
Play a tune for us again, today! Play that song!
I knew you would say that! Well then, here I go!
Yeah! Do it, do it!
The mirror...
I see... So, I have become a skeleton...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Owowowowowow! That hurts, Captain!
Why am I getting punished too?!
Shut up! Stop fighting about such stupid things!
But Captain, this guy nearly killed me with a stray bullet in that battle back there!
But you're still alive, right? He's already apologized as well!
Stop fighting about stuff that's already in the past! It's pathetic!
That hurts!
That pain proves that you're alive!
That's right!
Stars... This vast, starry sky... I wonder if Laboon is looking at it as well...
What do you think, Captain?
Hey, everyone, come and see this! Brook's being sentimental!
P-Please stop! That is embarrassing!
They're from the Navy Headquarters! What should we do?!
Don't be scared! Get them!
Wow, look! The captain's bounty just went up again!
How's that?!
Let us sing a song!
Yorki~! Yorki~! May his name echo all the way back to Twin Capes!
Terrible news! Hey, it's the captain! There's something wrong with Captain Yorki!
An infectious disease?!
Yeah...
Nobody go into the room... There are ten others infected besides the Captain...
He may have got it in that jungle we passed through...
It's an undiscovered virus... I'm afraid there's nothing I can do!
This is a terrible situation...
If things go badly, it could kill this entire crew!
Captain... Captain Yorki...
Don't sound so damn depressed...
You'll ruin the good name of the Rumbar Pirates, who can make a crying child laugh.
I'll just be... leaving the Grand Line a little ahead of you guys...
You guys just leave this old ship with us and the virus...
You should... find yourselves a new ship, and keep on going!
Captain...
We'll do what we can... and see if we can somehow make it out of the Grand Line through the Calm Belt...
Well, it'll work out somehow. Sorry, you guys...
Give Laboon my best regards!
Wipe those looks off your faces, guys, and stand up straight!
Yes!
Brook...
Yes.
I can't take it...!
Captain Yorki... I will never forget those words!!
All right, Captain?! I have engraved them into my heart! Please... take good care of yourself... Captain!!
I shall be leaving this ship... But please... Live, and let us all meet again!
Just take off this mask!
Let us all sing together again...!
Hey, Brook...
Send me off with... My favorite song...
Going to deliver Binks' Sake...