Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
Translation & initial timing
Vegapunk Fansubs
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
Timing
Galaxy 9000
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Editing
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
General Zombie Night!
Thriller Bark's Mysterious Four
A Warlord of the Sea?
Is that true, Robin?!
Yes, Gekko Moriah is a man of many mysteries.
What's a guy like that doing way out here?
I'm not sure.
But there are other victims who have become lost in the forest like me.
There are others?
Yes...
The fact that you were all invited here as well... It's likely that Moriah has his eyes on you!
We creep about in this dark forest so we aren't caught by the zombies...
Too scared to run to sea and expose ourselves under the sun!
This old body doesn't even have the will to live anymore...
Before I die... just once...
Just once!
I'd like to walk under the open sun!
Is that true?! That's so horrible!
Alright! I'll help you! Don't worry at all!
You idiot, I'm not crying!
You're too compassionate! Don't get weighed down with this...
Seriously.
Hey, old fart!
It's a lady's privilege to cry for sympathy!
Stop getting carried away!
Well, still...
We were already looking for the shadow stealing guy, so...
If he's after us too, we'd kick his ass anyways, so why not save you along the way, old man?
Right?
Thank you for saying something like that! It's just a little, but somehow I can feel hope again!
We're counting on you!
Go for it!
Beat that Moriah guy!
You were listening in? You other victims!
Yeah...
Sorry, I got carried away crying too!
Meanwhile... at Hogback's Mansion
Usopp's Team
That's Hogback's laugh!
What is this room?
It's a lab!
It's almost complete!
My magnificent marionette!
Look, Cindry-chan!
This is art; the work of a genius!
I hope it fails when it's almost done.
What are you saying, Cindry-chan?!
You really don't hold back what you're feeling!
I made dinner.
Oh yeah, what is it tonight?
Soup spaghetti.
Watch out, the soup is falling off, Cindry-chan!
I wish that plates were extinct.
I know that!
But why do you pick foods that need them?!
There's lots of other things you can make!
Cindry-chan's there too...
Yakisoba for example, or... yakiudon or...
Fried noodles
Okay?
Maybe katsudon or...
Breaded pork on rice
Is she really the same girl who died in that accident?
I can't believe it...
No more soups or anything!
And this soup spaghetti?
What's that on the table?
It looks like it's a corpse...
Being in that colour, there's no way it's alive.
It's got a number on it just like the zombies in the graveyard!
He said it's almost complete...
So this confirms it.
That's a zombie he's in the process of reanimating!
All of the zombies here on the island were brought back to life by Hogback.
That's the only explanation at the moment!
But with medicine you only save people before they die!
No matter how carefully you fix a dead person's body,
you can't bring it back to life!
I don't get it either...
But maybe if we stay here and watch, we can figure out his secret.
How do you do?
If you wish to look inside, it would be so much better for you to simply enter!
"Yohoho"?!
B-Brook?
Who is it?!
You! Why are you here?!
What?! "Yohoho"?
Wasn't that Brook just now?!
But he wasn't a skeleton!
He had flesh and skin.
You guys!
They found us!
What did you all see...
I told you never to peek into the laboratory...
W-We didn't see anything!
I didn't see anything either!
I didn't either!
Really?
I-It's true!
Definitely not the zombie you're making!
Don't say that!
Well, fine then...
No matter what secrets you may have found so far, it's already too late...
In just a few minutes...
The night attack will begin.
Night attack?
The other guests lost on this island will have their guard down... the night attack begins...
To get buried again just before the night attack...
Itching, burning, pain. It's all in your head!
You're all dead already!
Now, wake up! Soldier Zombies!
Beaten and beaten, you will stand again and again!
That is the true terror of you zombies!
What a bother...
Hey! Stop being so lazy!
Stop goofing around, zombies!
Tell me who I am.
Our leader!
Our leader Absalom!
Leader! Leader! Leader!
Whose hobby is peeping!
Pervy-Leader!
Pervsalom! Pervsalom!
Pervy!
Pervert!
Shut up!
W-W-Welcome home! Lady Perona... Ladies...!
Shut up, Kumashi! {Gotta change everywhere the name to "Bearsy", or whatever one we're choosing for him.}
What's with that look?! I hate it when you do that! {She doesn't ask, but in English you'd probably put a question mark on the 1st phrase.}
I-I'm sorry.
If you're not cute then you're not fit to serve me!
Hurry! Hurry!
It's starting! It's starting!
It's time for the night attack!
It's midnight!
Master!
Moriah-sama!
It's time to get up!
Nin! Do it!
Alright! Wake up!
Master!
I was having a nightmare!
Isn't that the best, Master?
Since Moriah-sama has been sleeping since the last time we had a night attack four days ago...
We've prepared you four days worth of food!
The prey this time is pretty tough!
It's the group that brought down Enies Lobby last month...
Straw Hat Luffy's crew!
They'll certainly be of use to Moriah-sama!
It's really starting to pour...
Alright, should we just run to the mansion then?
Wait a sec!
I can see some huge thing behind the mansion.
It looks like a mark...
The fog is clearing up a bit...
Huh? A flag?
No.
Isn't that a sail?
A sail?
That's right!
You were still following us?!
It's just as he said, that's a sail.
Thriller Bark...
Is not an island, but the largest pirate ship in the world!
You can see that at the back of the mansion is the main mast.
That's where Gekko Moriah is!
Now, Soldier Zombie Unit...
The General Zombies will finish off the pirates!
Soldier Zombie & General Zombie
General
No matter how many times you go down, just get back up quickly and crush them with fear of the undead!
Absalom of the Graveyard
Wild Zombie & Surprise Zombie
General
Just now, the bell chimed.
Ghost Princess
Perona
Now it's time for us to really go at it.
Don't think you can escape from here, moronic pirates!
Is everything ready?! Zombies!
This is the realm of the undead...
Thriller Bark!
Be prepared to witness a nightmare!
Well, let's go!
Into the haunted house!
How is this zombie research, Hogback?!
You were experimenting here!
You've been resurrecting the dead, haven't you!?
H-Hey, Nami, saying it so bluntly...
From here on you're free to think whatever you like!
But what would make you think something like that?
I've seen that woman's obituary.
Victoria Cindry,
ten years ago, you died!
You guys! You went into that room?
Cindry-chan!
Samurai Ryuuma...
Cast these fools into a world of shadows, immediately!
W-Wait!
Into that shadow world where you will never see the light again!
The night attack has already begun!
Well, well! Now that I can see you clearly, you're quite a lovely woman.
Beautiful!
Would you please allow me to see your panties?
As if!
This conversation...!
It's exactly like with him!
The zombies you've seen up until now were on a different level.
He is a general zombie, and his body is special.
This man came from
Wano Country in the New World.
You may think I'm just exaggerating, but the story of how he cut down a dragon mid-flight is still told.
He's a legendary samurai.
This is bad!
Don't come!
There's no way to escape!
Cindry-san?
Could you please open up the door to that passage over there?
Also, I would love to have dinner afterwards.
W-What? I thought he was going to cut us...
That scared me! What was he trying to do?
W-Whatever, it doesn't matter right now! Now's our chance to run, the door is wide open!
Hurry!
Well done.
That's truly a master's swordplay. After humming and walking three blocks...
Only then do they truly realize they've been cut...
Three-Pace Hum:
Notch Slash!
Anybody home?!
Pardon us!
Just go in!
It's locked from...
Oh, it's open.
What're you calling "open", idiot...
Hey! Is anyone home?
Gekko Moriah!
Is that all there is to this mansion? Not even a single servant around?
What's with this room? It looks like there's just been a fight.
It can't be, Nami-san was involved...!
You have a lot of guts to wander this far, knowing our master's name.
Eh?! There's a pig growing out of the wall.
Let's welcome our guests!
Hey, hey, are these zombies too?
It seems whatever it is, on this island it's bound to be unusual.
Where are you...
hiding Nami-san!?
It's un-ladylike to open your mouth that much.
Even if you're quite pretty.
Eh? Really?
But you ruined it already once you leapt out of the picture frame.
Twist!
The spear broke!
What's with his body?! Is he iron!?
S-Stop it! What are you?!
Aren't you one of those other weaklings' friends?
Two Sword Style:
Double Slice.
Rice
Rice? Sounds delicious!
Flash!
It was awful!
This island is really fun!
You! You nimble, little bastard!
If you hadn't gotten in our way, we probably would've gotten along!
Rubber...
Bazooka!
R-Rugbear!
Alright, all done.
Oh, you're talking about those three!
They're fast asleep in the bedroom right now.
Aren't you glad?
They're safe!
Like we'd believe that crap.
But it's true! Go see for yourself! It's the passage just up those stairs!
Hey, wait a sec...
The curly-brow cook is gone...
Huh? He was here just a second ago...
Where did Sanji go off to?
Hey, stop laughing! They'll hear you.
They must've done something at some point.
We've lost an important man.
Hey, you..
But still, he's right. Sanji should be alright.
But in this zombie mansion, we should focus on rescuing the other three, shouldn't we?
You all... just because you're a little stronger, don't get cocky...
Now that you've lost a friend, you'll show your true colours! Just look!
Anyways, it seems we have no other choice but to go cautiously.
Hey, you guys! Really-
I don't think these kids' stories were true.
In that case, let's take this pig with us as a guide.
Go on, go!
Wait, you...
It'll do you good to learn how fearsome our master is.
Our real boss is one of the Royal Seven Warlords of the Sea Gekko Mori-
I can't say it! It makes my soul freeze over!
Wah, it's bloodcurdling just saying that name!
Your missing friends are in trouble.
One, then another. Your friends will slowly disappear.
You should turn back.
But before one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea Gekko-
No, our master's true might, the terror will keep you from saving anyone!
Shut up and stop babbling.
Then tell that idiot Moriah this!
If anything happens to my crew...
I'll knock him off the face of this island!
Anyways, we'll leave Sanji alone, he won't die.
Let's go.
Dear Master,
For some reason, some very formidable guys have gotten into the mansion.
From the surprised Surprise Zombies.
Everybody circle the mansion!
屋敷を囲めェ～
Let's Fiesta Night!
レッツフィエスタナイッッ
Not a single pirate will get away!
海賊達は一人たりとも逃がさない
Everybody! Zombie Night!
エッビッバァリィ～ゾンビナイッ
Round and round and turn and die!
ラウンド andラウンandターンandダーイ
Zombie night!!!
ゾンビナーイッ！！！
Now all of our prey has wandered into our territory!
Tonight you may rampage as much as you please!
Awaken! General Zombies!
Be revived! Ancient Warriors!
The Straw Hat pirate crew has eight members.
Catch them soundly and bring them to our master!
Let's move!
You horrifying General Zombies!