Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for... One Piece!
Compasses and the like will only slow us down
Translation & initial timing
VS
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
Quality-checking
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Even an old treasure map covered in dust...
Isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
Soundtracking
Halee
For our own storms, all we have to do is
Video editing
Sewil
Raw provider
SOFCJ-Raws
Ride someone else's biorythm...
And pretend that it isn't there!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
and go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Let's break the tight-fisted night!
We have no interest in treasure chests
A pocket of romance, and
We are!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Brook's Promise!
The Eighth Member
Ten years after their departure from Twin Capes
-The Florian Triangle-
I saw you taking off your pants!
Kidding! How embarrassing!
Having so much fun~! I'm alone, but I'm having so much fun~!
Hello~!
45 degrees!
Aha, look at this, someone! Ah, I am all alone...
Hey, Brook! How long are you gonna sleep, anyway?
Wake up, we've spotted an island!
It's a summer island! A beach!
Ah... Huh... Um...
Huh? Huh? No, what is this?!
What's wrong, Brook?
If you're not here, we can't start, right?
Ah... You are all here!
Huh? I am so glad... Huh...?!
How can you be alive? Why?
What're you saying? How long are you gonna keep dreaming?
If it hurts, that must mean this isn't a dream!
This is real! That other part must have been the dream! Thank G-
I wonder if Captain Yorki managed to get through the Calm Belt safely.
Well, I guess only the ocean knows that!
We have to carry on, for his sake!
Take this new ship onward, to where Laboon's waiting!
It is morning!
We're awake!
It's a huge storm! The sail's gonna be torn to pieces!
Hah! We just have to sing and ride it through!
Wow, Brook! Look at this!
You've got yourself a bounty!
Hmm? What's this?! Keep playing, Brook!
Yeah!! I was dancing with chopsticks in my nose!!
Please wait a minute.
Well...
Awesome~!
YOU CAN DO THAT?!
This is called a Tone Dial... I bought it from a merchant ship.
It's a very rare kind of shell that can record sound and play it back.
Oh, those things from Sky Island!
You are familiar with it?
When I meet Laboon again, I plan on letting him hear this. I always keep it on my body.
You've got something recorded on that?
It is a song.
It's the voice of my crewmates singing, back when they were still alive.
Something to let him know that we were all happy right to the end of our journey. A message to Laboon...
May I play it now?
Oh, I wanna hear it! I'm sure Laboon would love to hear it, too!
Well, then...
How... many of us... are still breathing...?
We're breathing... but it doesn't seem like there's any hope for any of us...
Looks like we've got ourselves wiped out...
Their weapons were... poisoned...
Seems like we're all gonna die, huh?
We're pirates, so we were prepared to die at any time, but...
we didn't think we'd all die at once...!
Laboon...
Brook... About that Revive Fruit of yours...
Who knows... I have never died before, but... I have an idea!
We will die anyway, so let us die while having fun...
Shall we sing a song?
If the power of the Revive Fruit really will bring me back to life...
then I will deliver it to him without fail!
The Tone Dial...
This song that Laboon, the captain, and all of us loved...
Waiting for us at that cape, not knowing whether we will come today or tomorrow...
Our comrade.... I will deliver it to Laboon!
Great idea!
Yeah... You guys... Let's not fall until the end!
Let him hear it...!
Let's give Laboon the Rumbar Pirates' once-in-a-lifetime performance!
Huh? If it's this song, then we'll all join in, too!
Binks' Sake
Going to deliver Binks' sake
Following the sea breeze, riding on the waves
Far across the salty deeps, the merry evening sun
Painting circles in the sky, birds singing along
Farewell to the harbour, to my old hometown
Let's all sing out with a DON, as the ship sets sail
Waves of gold and silver dissolve to salty spray
As we all set sail to the ends of the sea
Going to deliver Binks' sake
We are pirates, slicing through the seas
The waves our pillows, the ship our roost
Flying the proud skull on our flags and sails
Now comes a storm through the far-off sky
Now the waves are dancing, beat upon the drums
If you lose your nerve, this breath could be your last
But if you just hold on, the morning sun will rise
Going to deliver Binks' sake
Today, and tomorrow, our dreams through the night
Waving our goodbyes, we'll never meet again
But don't look so down; for at night the moon will rise
Going to deliver Binks' sake
Let's all sing out with a DON, a song of the waves
Doesn't matter who you are, someday you'll just be bones
Never-ending, ever-wandering, our funny traveling tale
What is wrong? Now, this is just a quartet...
Trio...
Duet...
Solo...
Why? Leaving just the accompaniment...
If you wanna join my crew, all I ask is that you love music!
This is the ship of the Rumbar Pirates, who can even make a crying child laugh!
Laboon! We will definitely return here!
Wait for us!
Laboon... You have waited there for fifty years...
But can you wait for just another year or two?
For I, too, have the true spirit of a pirate!
You are facing that wall and waiting for me... And just as we promised, when I meet you again...
I'll be coming over that wall!
Hey, skeleton!
Is the song over already?
Give us another one! Just one more!
The song I once sung with my comrades, who were so full of life...
Was the final performance of the Rumbar Pirates.
During the fifty years when I was drifting alone in that dark, dark, sea of mist...
How many times did I listen to this...?
On that vast ship, all on my own,
this song was the only thing that made me feel that there was life besides my own.
However, today, I have finally found new conviction in my heart...
So I shall seal away this Tone Dial.
Seal!
WHAAAAT?! SO YOU REALLY CAN DO THAT?!
I now know that Laboon is still safe, and waiting for me...
And I have gotten my shadow back, and can escape from these cursed waters.
This Dial, with everyone's voices recorded upon it,
is no longer going to be used so I can think back on the past...
It is a song for Laboon.
Every day was painful...
I was truly unable to see any hope.
But, now, Luffy-san...
I am so glad to be alive!
I truly am glad to be alive!
Well, sure!
Finally, this day has come!
Right.
May I join your crew?
Sure, why not.
WHAT?! JUST LIKE THAT?!
HE JOINED?!
But, whatever! We've got our musician! Hooray!
A musician! He's just bones, but he's our musician!
The musician we've always wanted!
He's so light, too!
That lightness is another thing that's great about you!
It's great!
Yes! Because I am just bones~!
He's so funny!
Just bones! Just bones! Just bones! Just bones!
I get it!
They certainly are very lively.
Why do we keep gathering up people like that?
I don't really understand, but they seem happy, don't they, Namizou?
I guess. Thanks.
I don't get it at all, but cheers!
We have no idea, but cheers!
45 degrees!
Laboon...
I will not turn back.
We always pushed on, straight forward.
That path was the only one we could take in order to come back to you.
To travel around the world was our goal, and you were waiting at the finish line.
Right? So I will not turn back.
I will carry on, and see you again.
Please wait for me!
It will just be a little longer...
What is it, Laboon?
You're in a really good mood today, huh?
Allow me to introduce myself!
A wanted-poster? You had a bounty?
I have still not introduced myself properly... I am "Dead Bones", and my name is Brook!
I am a wanted man... My title is "Humming Brook"!
My current bounty is 33 million bellies!
Once the leader of an escort convoy,
and afterwards, musician and swordsman, and eventually acting Captain, of the Rumbar Pirates!
I offer my services and my life to captain Straw Hat Luffy!
I hope not to be a burden to you all!
I shall work myself to the bone!
Alright! Let's have one more toast!
Two days later
Magnificent! Thank you so much, Franky-san, Usopp-san!
No problem at all! This was easy!
My design was a great success!
I picked the flowers!
What a magnificent grave...
After all, I couldn't possibly expect you to bring all those bones with you on Lion-chan.
Call it the Thousand Sunny next time, OK?
So strange that this Thriller Bark should have come from our own homeland, West Blue...
But here, in the earth of our homeland, they might at last be able to rest in peace.
Then, Brook, we'll be going now.
We'll be going on ahead.
See you later.
Yes.
Ah, that surprised me. So, you have finally recovered?
Yeah. I just overslept a little.
Is that...
It's a dead sword... Yubashiri.
I was gonna give it a proper burial.
Luffy is the man who is gonna be the Pirate King!
Um...
Ah, no...
Ah, that is right, I became a part of your crew.
Huh, is that so? Well, you've got bad luck.
This is a pretty crazy crew, you know.
It seems that way. I will do my best until I die.
Ah, but I am already dead.
OK! Now that Zoro's awake, let's head out to sea!
Let's head off to our next adventure!
YEAH!!!
Zoro, you took off your bandages again?!
Yeah, 'cause they're hard to move around in.
I put them there so you wouldn't move around so much!
Wait!
He sure recovered quickly. Are you already setting sail?
You can take Brook's ship.
I fixed the helm and the sail.
Thanks.
After all you've done, we're really indebted to you.
We couldn't thank you enough no matter how hard we tried.
Will you marry me?
You seem like a nice lady, but I'm afraid I'm far too super for you.
It's a real shame to see you guys go!
Couldn't you stay and party for just a few more days?
No way! We're going to Fishman Island!
I'm really excited!
I bet we'll meet some funny guys there!
And some beautiful mermaids! Ah, what I wouldn't love to do with one of them~!
I wonder if the mermaids will let me see their panties...
Hey, hey! Don't be ridiculous!
Mermaids don't wear panties!
While we're talking about how beautiful mermaids are...
I hear even the Pirate Empress Hancock was totally overwhelmed...
Mermaids~! Mermaids~!
Surely they have tails instead of legs anyway?
How do you guys know that, anyway?
Oh, well, about three years ago, before we came here, we went to Fishman Island! That place is the best!
Lola, you guys went to the New World?!
We didn't go there! We were born in the New World!
My mama was a pirate, too.
Ah, that's right...
This is my mama's Vivrecard. I'll let you have it.
Paper?
Wow! That's incredible!
Captain Lola's mama is a great pirate!
Take good care of it! It'll definitely be useful later!
What's a Vivrecard?
Huh? You don't know?
Captain Lola, they only make Vivrecards in the New World.
Ah, that's true...
This is no ordinary paper.
It's resistant to both fire and water.
What you do is you take a few of your own fingernails to a shop,
and they use them to make you a special sheet of paper.
That is the "Card of Life", the Vivrecard.
What you do, is you tear off pieces and give them to friends or family if they're going away.
Look at this.
This is the Vivrecard my mama gave me.
It moved!
No matter where in the world the Card pieces are, they share a connection.
So I can always tell in what direction my mama is!
Although you can't tell how far away.
Wow, so mysterious!
And they have lots of them in the New World, right?
It's quite convenient!
Here, I'll just sign this piece of my Mama's Vivrecard for you...
If you ever run into trouble, just follow this and go see Mama.
And be sure to tell her that I'm doing fine, too.
I think I've got one of those, too.
I just thought of that too.
Isn't this just like that white piece of paper Ace gave you back then?
This piece of paper will allow us to meet again.
So, that's what he meant...
Here it is...
But it's burning, and seems like it's gotten smaller...
Wait, you! Let me see that!
Yes, this is certainly a Vivrecard...
But I didn't tell you this yet... This paper also reflects the owner's vitality and life force!
This belonged to someone important to you, right?
Yeah! It's my brother's!
Lola?
I hate to tell you, but this person's life...
is fading!