Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Funimation
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality-checking
alasta
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Formatting
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
There.
Thanks!
Hating frills...
Men really are strange creatures.
Well yeah I guess so.
Thanks for taking it off!
Well bye!
I'll never feel relaxed until I find my friends!
You certainly are hasty...
As long as the others are still alive like I am that's all that matters.
As long as they're alive...
I can keep fighting again and again!
I'm gonna surpass all of those guys!
Alright! I'm gonna walk on my hands all the way to Sabaody Archipelago!
That'll make me stronger!
Could you give me a ship?
You really are hasty...
You don't have any ships?!
This is the Calm Belt?!
That's right.
Pirate Empress
Boa Hancock
This maiden island is surrounded by a giant Sea King den known as the Calm Belt.
Which is why sailors never dare come near.
Castaways will sometimes miraculously drift here but most of the time only as corpses.
But you said there's a pirate group here!
The Snake Princess's pirate ship Yuda is pulled by vicious poisonous sea snakes.
Sea Kings can't attack it.
It's the only ship on Amazon Lily!
Now what do I do?
There's no wind...
Should I build a raft and paddle all the way there?
That's ridiculous...
Okay! I'm gonna build a raft and paddle all the way there!
That's what you just thought up!
It's done!
That's terrible! It's already about to break!
I had no obligation to save you!
Are all men unable to swim even if they're pirates?
That was close!
Darn it!
If only Franky were here!
I dunno what to do!
I'm the one who doesn't know what to do!
You could've at least escaped to somewhere far away...
If we keep this up I'll only grow attached to you!
Whoa now! Stop!
What're you doing?!
Oh yeah! These arrows!
They were strong enough to destroy stone walls when I was being chased earlier!
They don't seem like special arrows though...
What are you talking about?
The arrows possess "Haki"!
Of course they're powerful!
Haki?
What's that?!
There she is!
Marguerite is all right!
Everyone!
The man is with her! Kill him!
Uh oh!
Halt!
Stop!
Marguerite! Are you alright?!
We need to hurry and finish the man off!
The Snake Princess has returned!
Calm Belt
The seas around
the Island of Women
You have real guts to lay anchor in the middle of monster-infested waters.
Yes. We were attacked only moments ago in fact!
The Sea Prism Stone in this warship may conceal our presence,
but staying anchored here for so long is bound to attract attention visually.
It's not, easy but the agreement between the Kuja and the government
forbids us from getting any closer than three kilometers from your island.
Consequently we're forced to wait in the middle of the monsters' den.
Have you heard?
They say the Kuja are specters that turn people to stone!
Get real!
Did you kill that Sea King?
Sea Kings are hardly rare in the Grand Line...
Impossible!
Not even cannons have an effect?!
That's...
The vice-admiral!
Allowing an entire warship to be food for a Sea King...
...would belittle the name of justice!
I have not come to hunt Sea Kings.
I would like to finish my business here and leave these waters quickly.
It looks like you have some skill.
I was growing tired of waiting!
At last you've returned Kuja Pirates!
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga of Navy Headquarters!
Warlord of the Sea and Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Show yourself! I've come for you!
So sorry but the Snake Princess isn't coming out.
She's sent many replies now!
That's men for you! Such unsophisticated creatures!
I haven't seen a live man in a long time!
Pirates and merchants always escape by boat when they see the Kuja flag!
Stop. That's a crude laugh.
We have received her replies...
"I will follow your orders to convene at once."
But she shows no indication of coming whatsoever!
This morning's newspaper.
A place and date has been decided for the public execution of Portgas D. Ace,
2nd Division Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!
There is no turning back now!
The World Government has issued strict orders
forcing the Seven Warlords of the Sea to assemble!
Refuse and the agreement is off!
Your title of Warlord of the Sea will be revoked!
Do you hear that, Boa Hancock?!
Who placed a kitten...
...in my path?!
M-My deepest apologies!
I'm the one responsible!
Be more careful.
Y-Yes!
S-Stop that!
So you've come out, Boa Hancock!
Don't let your guard down men!
That's the Pirate Empress?!
She's the definition of the most beautiful woman in the world!
Amazon Lily Empress
Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Warlord of the Sea –‘Empress’ Boa Hancock
So you've finally come for me...
What meddlesome people.
Youngest of the Gorgon Sisters
Boa Marigold
My recent replies were lies.
Second of the Gorgon Sisters
Boa Sandersonia
I will not go to war!
But...
I want you to let me keep my title of Warlord of the Sea.
And...
I also want all of the cargo on your ship.
What nonsense is this?!
You're not a selfish little child!
Do you honestly think we'll accept such outrageous demands?!
Hurry and haul it over!
What a beautiful woman!
I'll give her anything!
Why are you hauling our cargo?!
Come to your senses!
Oh no! I blindly listened to what she said!
Portgas D. Ace's public execution is in exactly one week from today!
Fire Fist Ace's life will be ended in the town square of Marineford, at the Navy Headquarters!
In other words Whitebeard will make a move within the next week.
Navy Headquarters, led by three admirals
is prepared to counter Whitebeard with full military force!
Will you lose the title of Warlord or accept the orders to assemble?!
Decide now!
Time is nearly up!
I like the title of Warlord.
I don't want it taken away.
But I hate the World Government.
I don't want to obey its orders.
How does this sound?
The marines who came to get me...
Had a mysterious accident on the sea
and were wiped out when they all turned to stone?
She's planning to do something!
Don't let your guard down!
I've heard about this before!
A ship was attacked by the Kuja pirate ship...
And when it was discovered later only strange statues were found onboard!
S-Strange statues?!
I already told you!
Your childish selfishness will not be allowed!
Big Sis has a terrible personality.
But she gets everything she wants.
Yes.
There is a reason for that.
Do you know why that is?
Because no matter what I do...
Even if I kick a kitten...
Even if I pull your ears off...
Or even if I kill someone, everyone in the world would forgive me.
The reason for that is...
Yes...
Because I'm beautiful!
Because I'm beautiful...!
Snake Princess!
We'll let you do anything!
After all you're beautiful!
Stop that all of you!
For being charmed by me your guilty consciences...
...will turn your bodies solid!
Love Mellow! {No idea what to translate her attacks as, thoughts? Original was "Love-Love Beam"}
Hanco--!
I'd expect no less from a navy vice-admiral...
I see.
You used pain to block out the evil thoughts.
You've much experience indeed.
However...
I can't say the same about your men.
Fools...!
It looks like you're the only one left now.
One and zero are not the same!
We will now return to the peaceful Amazon Lily!
Yes Snake Princess!
Boa Hancock!
I will wait here as long as I can!
I will not return empty-handed!
If you do not reappear in two days' time...
The agreement is off!
Do as you wish.
Open the gate!
The Snake Princess has returned!
Welcome back!
Welcome back Kuja Pirates!
Snake Princess!
Ran-sama!
Daisy-sama!
We had a big haul!
They're so cool!
I'm gonna join the pirates someday too!
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
Snake Princess! Snake Princess!
Welcome back.
Your Monkey Carriage is ready.
Has anything happened?
No. Nothing at all...
Iron ore gunpowder alcohol and crops from the north...
What a tremendous haul!
We plundered two merchant ships and one pirate ship.
The center sea people just offshore also gave us their cargo.
The Kuja Pirates truly are elite!
Ran. Any books at all?
Granny Nyon!
Let me think.
Oh! Those center sea people did give us a newspaper.
Here you are!
Amazon Lily
Kuja Castle
Welcome back!
Welcome back Snake Princess.
Thank you for holding down the fort.
Enishida. What is this?
Oh!
It's a clay model that children from the village worked hard to make for you!
They must have worked hard to paint it too.
The way they carefully carried it to the castle to prevent it from breaking was truly tender and innocent!
Oh I see.
So they made me...
...Out of mud and clay...
Snake Princess!
Don't bring such filthy things into the castle!
Throw it away at once and clean the floor.
Anyway Enishida...
Y-Yes?
I didn't see any of our defense warriors there to greet us on our arrival...
Oh, well actually...
A rather violent monkey appeared in the jungle and...
It was such a savage and crude beast that they all had to go after it...
A monkey?
Don't worry. They'll be back shortly.
I'm truly sorry they weren't there to greet you.
Well no matter.
Would you like something to drink?
White sake.
I think I'll have some too.
Granny Nyon.
This is my room. Why are you here?
G-Granny Nyon!
How did you get in?!
I can get in any way I want.
Throw her out.
Wait Snake Princess!
You forgot "please"...
"Please."
Pardon me. Please wait Snake Princess.
The center sea people's ship is anchored off shore.
They've come here to get you have they not?
They've ordered you into active duty have they not?
That's right. An invitation to war.
Why aren't you going?! You must go!
If you go the agreement will be upheld!
Certainly someone with your abilities...
...won't meet an untimely fate!
But...
I'm scared!
She's almost like a puppy!
Wait this is no time for that!
Granny Nyon...
This land is currently protected by your title of Warlord of the Sea!
Up until recently this island was protected from outside enemies
by the great defense network that is the Calm Belt!
However now the center sea people are using new ship-crafting techniques
to come and go through these waters as they please.
The fact that you're a Warlord of the Sea is the only reason they won't set foot on this island
to put a stop to the Kuja's pirate ways.
The island is also home to the very young and the very old.
If you lose the title and we return to being a regular pirate nation
only tragedy will await us!
Are you sure you're not just afraid?
My life could end at any time now.
Look closely at this crystal ball!
Let us shed light on your future...
"Go!"
Detestable!
Throw her out!
This instant!
Y-Yes! Right away!
Wait! Snake Princess!
Stop! What are you doing?!
I watched quietly
only for you to put on a pathetic act.
What are you trying to pull here?
Your era came to an end a long time ago...
You lost your place as Amazon Lily's empress three decades ago,
Gloriosa!
If my own selfishness should bring about the end of our kingdom, I would be forgiven for it...
The reason for that is
yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
There it is!
The Snake Princess's "Extreme Looking-Down Pose!"
You may have been the empress of this kingdom once,
and yet you abandoned the kingdom and set off to sea!
You Kuja traitor!
That's why I live quietly on
the edge of the village now!
Then you should continue
to live there quietly.
I will not have you interfering with me
the current empress!
Snake Princess!
Hey! Let go!
That said I can't help but admire your zeal.
You win.
You agree to what I said Snake Princess?
It really does pay to talk things through!
Thank you!
You'll go then?!
I lied. Don't get cocky!
Get out of my sight!
Curse you Snake Princess!
S-Snake Princess...
What have you done?! She's an old woman!
I don't know what came over me...
Yes! Yes! That sort of thing
happens to all of us!
Granny Nyon!
Aged as I may be I am still a Kuja warrior.
I have not grown decrepit!
The Snake Princess is about to bathe!
Leave the castle premises immediately!
Come on! Let's hurry!
I-I just started eating!
Hurry outside!
It's time for their bath!
Get ready!
The people in the castle are coming
so it's about to get packed in here!
Bath
For the next several hours
entrance into the castle
is strictly forbidden!
Say...
Why does everyone make such a big deal when the Snake Princess takes a bath?
How old are you now?
Eight.
Then I'll tell you.
The Gorgon Sisters' secret?!
That's right.
Gorgon was the name of a monster
that once lived in the center ocean.
Anyone who looked at this terrifying
monster would instantly turn to stone.
At the end of an adventure
the Snake Princess and her sisters
managed to slay the Gorgon monster.
But when the monster uttered its death howls
it placed a horrible curse
on the three warriors.
The monster's large eyes
were etched onto their backs
and everyone nearby who's lured in
by their charm and looks at them
is turned to stone and killed.
The Gorgon Sisters never remove
their clothes in front of people.
And when they bathe
they always post guards
like this to keep people away.
Island of Women, Jungle
Where did he run to?!
He went up the craggy mountain!
Don't tell me he went back into the village?!
He wanted a ship!
What?!
Now then, what now?
I'll get spotted again if I just sit here...
She did mention this island
has a pirate ship...
If I can just borrow it somehow...
No wait. Nami's not here.
I'll end up drifting around
if I go all by myself.
Oh I know!
Asking for a ride on the
ship is the best way!
I'll ask if they'll take me to
Sabaody Archipelago!
Which means...
I'll have to talk to someone important
and since important people
live in tall buildings...
I'm thinking so hard I might get a fever!
Okay! I'll just go into
a tall building first!
Hurry to the village!
The Snake Princess has
probably already returned!
If she finds the man
things will turn serious!
It's brittle!
What was that?!
The castle tower's roof collapsed!
What's happening?!
The Snake Princess is taking a bath in there!
More water?!
Ouch it's hot! Wait this is bathwater!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna drown!
My feet are on the ground. I'm safe!
Is this a bath?
A man!?
Hey...
That thing on your back...
It seems familiar somehow...
You saw it?!