Isn't that a warship?
Does that mean the Navy's here?
What?!  There wasn't anything here earlier!
There's somebody over there!
Huh?  Isn't that...
Hey!  Hey!
Imagine meeting you!  It's me!
Thanks for everything you've done for me!
Straw-Hatter...
He's...
the guy we met in the Human Shop on Sabaody.
Trafalgar Law.  But now, he's...
Right, Trafal... Traf!
That guy helped me escape
during the Whitebeard war.
And he even treated my injuries!
He did?
That's right!
He saved my life, just like Jinbe!
Hey!
I never thought I'd meet you here!
Really, thanks a lot for before!
Huh?
Where's the talking bear and those guys?
Bring Straw-Hatter over here!
I'm gonna take him away from this place!
Let me take care of him for now!
I'm a doctor!
Where is Ace?!
What'll happen if we just let him be?
Well, to put it bluntly...
Like I said when we came to this island,
if his wounds reopen, he'll probably die.
Straw-Hatter will need complete rest
for another two weeks.
Understood.  Thanks for all you've done for us.
I'm impressed that you survived, Straw-Hatter.
But there is no need to feel indebted to me
for saving you back then.
I was just acting on a whim.
We are both pirates.  Don't forget that.
Guess you're right.
If we're both going for One Piece then that makes us enemies...
but I still owe a debt to a lot of people after what happened two years ago.
How lucky that I got to meet you
right after meeting Jinbe!
Really, thanks!
Hey!  There's a collapsed marine over there!
Isn't... that...
Hey... Please save me, Trafalgar!
Smoker-san!
Don't tell me...
Smoker-san?!
Smokey!
The Navy?!
W-What?  Isn't that...
Hey, this isn't good, Luffy!  The Navy's here!
R-Right!
Captain-chan, what's wrong?
Smokey, are you alright?!
Smoker-san!
I knew it, it's Old Smokey and his group!
That sure takes me back!
There's a hole... in his...
Smoker-san!
In order to become a Warlord...
he delivered the hearts
of one hundred pirates to Navy HQ!
He's completely deranged!
How could you?!
How could you?!  How could you?!
Hey now, stop that.
I can't stand... such crudeness.
Tashigi-chan!
Dammit!  He got her again!
Even Smo-san is down!
What did he just do?!
You never learn, do you?
Don't get so serious.
Tashigi-chan!
Luffy, hurry up!  We're in danger here!
Oh, right!
Hey, Traf!  I wanted to ask...
Go behind the laboratory.
You'll find what you're looking for there.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
We both have something we want back.
He must mean me, thank goodness.
This is dangerous!  I'm a former pirate as well!
Alright, Luffy!  We've gotta get away from the Navy!
I wonder if Smokie's group will be alright?
Were they defeated by Traf?
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Fire!
Stop it, this isn't the time!
Smo-san and Captain-chan are...
Even though it's deadly cold...
Mountain Outside of the Laboratory's Backdoor
- Sanji's Group -
I don't care!
I don't care about the samurai or the kids either!
Whaaaat?!
Isn't there a camera around here?!
I've gotta take some pictures
before I'm turned back into myself!
What kind of pictures?!
Also, stop having nosebleeds with other people's bodies!
Never mind that, Nami!
You shouldn't button up my Hawaiian shirt!
Are you alright?
You're freezing, right?
Hang in there just a little longer!
The swirly guy's being so nice, it's creeping me out!
What's going on?
Did your souls get swapped or something?
I didn't think it would be so cold in a human body.
Everyone, stop!
It's freezing...
It's hopeless... I can't go any further...
Me neither!
I'm gonna freeze to death!
Dammit!  Taking them out of there without a plan was a bad idea!
Though, I'm not cold at all in this body.
Alright, I'll cut off my fur and give it to them.
Stop it!  That's my body!
So you say, but there aren't
any other warm coats around here.
I wonder if there's a mountain hut nearby?
Oh, a camera, a mirror...
and a s-shower!  A mountain hut would have those!
I'm gonna tie you up!
I see that I have no other choice!
Put a leaf on each of your heads!
Huh?!  This isn't the time for nonsense!
The kids are about to collapse from the cold!
Besides, there isn't a single plant on this island!
So there aren't any leaves!
Then use rocks or something else, it matters not.
Make haste!
Fine... It seems like you got some sort of plan here.
I'll find rocks for the kids!
We've done it.  So, what's up with this?
If this is just some silly superstition to make the cold go away,
I'm gonna flatten you!
Alright!
Doron!
Whaaaaat?!
What's going on?!
We've got coats!  And shoes too!
How?!  What did he do?!
Gloves!
It's warm!
It's so warm!
The truth is, I consumed a rare kind of fruit,
and ever since, I have been able to use magic...
to change any object into a disguise!
I am not familiar with clothing from foreign lands, but will these do?
Though I must warn you that it's magic,
so the clothes will vanish if you remove them.
Yay, thank you!
Hmph, don't go overboard!
You've got Devil Fruit powers?
But you know...
If you could do this...
why didn't you do it right away?!
But... it's such a waste to conceal those breasts.
Idiot!
T-That itches...
That itches, it does!
You just can't bring yourself
to say that you're hurt or that it's cold, huh.
It's because I'm a warrior.
There they are!  Hey guys!
Heeeey!
Heeey!  Heeey!
What are they doing here?
Everyone, are you alright?
Oh, it's them!
It's Luffy's group!  Zoro!  Usopp!
Robin!  Brook!
I'm so glad you're here!
Why is that idiot cook so enthusiastic?
Is he trying to stay warm?
What's that?  It looks like a bunch of giant kids, but...
Huh?!  Hey!
What're you doing?!  Cut it out, Franky!
The Straw Hats' Shelter
We're here!  This place will do.
This equipment looks like the stuff in the laboratory.
But it's all in pieces.
Maybe there was some kind of big explosion.
Well, as long as they shields us from the blizzard,
it doesn't matter.
So, where do we start?
That's gonna leave a scar on my fragile body!
I'll take care of you right away!
Wait, Sanji-kun!  What are you doing with my body?!
I'm Chopper!
My lower half has returned to me, it has!
Legson... My hind-legs...
I told you, there's no such creature!
This is quite surreal.
What an odd fellow.
The skeleton...
Is talking!
Hey, do the tank thing!
Can you shoot another beam?
C'mon!
Shut up!
Who is he on the inside again?
Huh?  Are you sure?
You're having a hard time dealing with this, right?
Let's just calm down and talk this over, everyone.
Alright!  So, who turned into who?
First off, I'm Franky!
Don't come to me if you get hurt!
I'm Chopper!
If you get hurt, I'll treat your wounds!
I'm Nami.
I'd rather die than fire a beam!
And... We...
are Nami-san!
I've been waiting for this!
I think Nami is being too crude.
I won't do it again!
Please, don't hurt Nami-san any more!
Don't do it, Nami!  You'll kill yourself!
If you touch my body,
it'll cost you 200 thousand beli!
Peeping will cost you 100 thousand!
How will I survive?!
How long are you gonna keep laughing?!  Stop acting like this doesn't concern you!
So, to start at the beginning...
this is the samurai from the Wano Kingdom
that we've heard about.
The distress call that we received
was meant for the Crocotaur they called Boss.
It came from one of his subordinates.
This is because the samurai
was relentlessly attacking the centaurs.
However, I was only attempting to find and rescue
my missing son, Momonosuke.
I merely cut down those who stood in my way.
And behold!
All these children were imprisoned in that facility.
Momonosuke must be in there somewhere as well!
Yeah, we weren't the only children.
We hadn't even learned all of the new kids' names yet.
But the question now is,
what happened after they sent the distress call?
It was the man from earlier.
They referred to him
as one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
What?!
Traf... is one of the Seven Warlords now?!
Indeed.
He joined their ranks during the past two years.
Before I knew it, I had been cut into three parts...
My head was thrown inside the facility.
My torso was simply abandoned.
My legs seem to have been used as monster bait.
I was running around, relying on my senses,
when I must have become stuck to something.
It was the back of the dragon's head.
Come to think of it, you were talking about that "Damn Warlord" earlier, right?
What?  It was just a pair of legs, right?  How could he have talked?
That's a good question.
Ah, that...
was me farting.
It is a talent I have possessed for a long time, it is.
You were farting?  That's disgusting!
Indeed it...
Ah!  The place is starting to stink!
In any case, it is quite comical
how you're just legs and a head!
I, on the other hand,
encountered someone who was just a torso!
That obviously must be this guy's torso!
Oh, you're right!
Did you see it?!  Where?!
Where did you encounter my torso?!
Ummm, are you alright...
without a heart... Tashigi-chan?
Yes, strangely enough.
She's acting really shy.
The ships that were hidden near the laboratory...
had "CC" written on them.
Huh?  Really, Vice-Admiral Smoker?
Yeah.  Had they been the same ships that were used here in the past,
they should have said "PH" for Punk Hazard.
If we assume that someone above Law
is pulling his strings, and that "CC" is their initials...
then I have a hunch who it might be.
If he is on this island...
then it would explain quite a lot.
Doctor Vegapunk's former associate...
the scientist...
Caesar Clown.
What do you think you were doing, Law?!
I should be the one to complain...
Caesar!
Something has been bothering me.
What?
If my memory serves me correctly...
a lot of children have been abducted in this region
over the last few years.
Abductions?
Yes.
But more importantly,
I can't get used to this new Captain-chan!
I can't help it.  Please try to deal with it!
Tashigi!  What are you talking about?
I haven't heard a damn thing about kids being snatched.
Please button your shirt, Smoker-san!
This "open" Captain-chan looks great, but she's horrifying on the inside!
Cram it!
There haven't been any reports from this region,
except for the occasional shipwreck.
But now that you mention it,
it does seem like a lot of kids die in this sea.
Yeah, that's right.  Right?
Right!
According to the communications division...
Oh, I don't have my glasses.
...many reports of kidnapped children have been made to G-5.
But in the newspaper, they're all announced as shipwrecks, piracy, or missing persons.
Of course, it's possible that
the reports were originally wrong and then corrected.
But... But it is also possible that...
Looks like you're hesitating, Tashigi.
If you have an opinion, then state it plainly!
Based on the number of children that we just saw...
you think that the reports of abduction were correct...
and the kidnapper could be on this island, right?
But in order for that to be true...
a member of G-5 would have to be
covering up the kidnappings by lying to the media.
So that means that
someone inside G-5 is helping the culprit?
Hey Smo-san!  I can't believe you're doubting us!
We may be the outcasts of the Navy,
but we still have our pride as Marines!
Shut the hell up!
She is scary!
Idiots like you aren't even worth suspecting!
What?
But don't let yourselves
have the wrong idea about the Navy, either.
All organizations contain multiple people,
so none of them can ever be perfect!
You'll overlook enemies if you let yourself think that the Navy's perfect!  Don't be deceived by appearances!
Yes Ma'am, Captain-chan!
You guys... Whatever.
I-I'm the captain!
Oh!  That's right!  We were deceived by appearances!
But Smoker-san, I'm still not entirely convinced.
Don't worry.
It's just a theory that we should keep in mind.
In any case,
my body and heart has been taken by Law.
We can't leave the island.
A third of you guys will go to the ship and report this.
What are you talking about, Vice-Admiral?
The ship's been sliced to pieces.
I said there were other ships, didn't I?
Go steal one.
Oh!  That was your plan!  You're a villain!
Be careful.
Before this situation gets any worse,
I'm gonna get my heart and body back...
and then I'll expose
the one who's pulling the strings on this island!
Former Vegapunk Lab
Laboratory #3
I finally got through to him.
We have permission to kill them all.
The Straw Hat Pirates, G-5, and Foxfire Kinemon.
No matter who dies on this island,
Joker can make it look like an accident at sea.
Capture as many of them as you can!
The more test subjects we have the better.
Yes, Master.
But if they make trouble for you,
then feel free to kill them with gas.
Where's Law?
He left the room a while ago.
No matter.
It seems that
one of them has a bounty of 400 million.
Don't push yourselves too hard.
In addition, the crew has bounties from 120 million down to fifty.
The total bounty for the Straw Hat Crew
is 800 million and fifty beli.
But for two years,
they've vanished off of the face of the planet.
Their bounties haven't changed in all that time.
Their actual strength might be higher than the numbers indicate.
You're always thorough with your research, Monet.
Master!
What happened to you?
Were you in the freezing cold without a coat?
It was stolen by pirates.
But more importantly,
they took Boss Brownbeard!
Please, save him!
Oh my, what a pity.
Don't worry about Brownbeard.  I'll definitely get him back.
Hurry now and go to the inner chamber.
You're very lucky.  I just finished a new medicine.
Something that will warm your body
and heal your wounds.
Really?  You've saved me.  Please help the others too!
Of course.  But first, you need to save yourself.
Thank you so much!  Thank you so much!
Hey!  What is this, Usopp?!
This is pretty super!
I give up.
Thanks, Usopp!
It detracts from Nami's beauty!
Stop complaining!
Without these, we'll get totally confused!
Brownbeard?
That's right.  Surely you've heard the name?
The whole world used to know me by that name!
Never heard of ya.
What the hell?!
What's happened?  Until recently,
you weren't willing to open your mouth...
but now we can't get you to shut up.
It's because you're going to be dead soon.
Law is going to come and save me.
I hate all the pirates from your generation, but Law is different.
What do you mean by "our generation"?
Don't you know?  Fool.
The eleven rookies worth over 100 million beli...
who met at the Sabaody Archipelago two years ago, and Blackbeard.
People are calling you "The Worst Generation".
You're problem children born into the gap between
two eras, forced to live in the chaos that entails.
After the death of Whitebeard, you stormed
into the New World and caused havoc on the seas.
Every time there's a major incident,
it's always someone from your generation.
Blackbeard, Kid, Law, Drake, Hawkins.
My very own Brownbeard Pirate Crew
was broken by Basil Hawkins!
Because of him, I lost my legs
and had to give up being a pirate.
We just barely managed
to escape with our lives and crawl to Punk Hazard.
Don't you know what this place is?
Hmm?
This place... This island...
It used to be filled with verdant forests,
overflowing with life.
This place?
I can't even imagine it.
The government scientist, Vegapunk,
used to conduct his experiments here.
He performed many experiments with weapons and medicine here.
They say that there were prisoners who never went to jail.
Instead, they were brought to this island
and used as human guinea pigs.
Then, four years ago, one of Vegapunk's
chemical weapon experiments went horribly wrong.
Two of the three labs were destroyed.
These are the ruins of one of those labs.
I see, the explosion must have been huge.
No wonder it's all torn up.
The explosion created a wave of burning heat that spread poison across the entire island.
It wiped out all natural life.
When that happened, the Government just abandoned the prisoners who were used as test subjects.
Fleeing the island, they sealed it off behind them!
The abandoned prisoners shut themselves
into the only lab that remained intact, Lab Three.
It was the only way that they could escape the poison gas that enveloped the island.
Due to the nerve gas, those who didn't die
almost always lost the ability to move their legs.
They had given up all hope.
But after a year,
our generous Master descended upon this island!
With his special power,
he cleansed the gas from the island.
And he used science to help the prisoners who couldn't walk and took them in as his subordinates!
Oh!  Master!
Master!
Master-san!
I arrived on the island a year after he did,
two years ago now.
There was still some remnants of the poison gas left.
Breathing it made you nauseous.
I didn't have the strength to live.
I had given up, thinking I was surely at my end.
That was when I saw them, the former prisoners who had lost their legs like me, and Master.
And just like them,
my life was also saved by Master's kindness.
If Vegapunk, who stole my comrades' legs, is a devil,
then Master is the kind-hearted god of salvation.
And then a few months ago,
another god of salvation, Trafalgar Law, a new member of the Seven Warlords, came to this island.
With his ability,
he gave legs to those of us who couldn't walk.
The legs of animals!
We, who thought we'd never walk again,
cried tears of joy.
What a great story!
I knew Traf was a great guy!
He saved me, too!
I didn't know Vegapunk was such a cruel man.
So the sheep-people we saw in the lab
were created by Law's powers.
I guess that explains the centaurs and the bird-lady too.
But wait, what about the dragon?
Oh, you saw the dragon?
That's an artificial creature that Vegapunk created to protect the island.
He can adapt to any environment.
One of the Celestial Dragons
took a liking to it and gave it a name,
but I forgot it.
If you see it again, just run away.  It's very violent.
Got it.
Even though I already ate it.
Anyway,
do you understand who's in charge of the island?
We won't allow anyone else to invade.
This island, Punk Hazard, belongs to our Master.
Rejoice!
Even now, Master is continuing his research for the benefit of the future of mankind.
He needs but a few human test subjects, and you get to become those subjects!
You can't escape!
Hmm?  What's happening?
Master!
The pain...
What...
What kind of medicine is this?
Master!
Let me out of here!
Try to endure it for a little while longer.
How do you feel now?
Nausea?  A cough?  That's fine.  Do you have a headache?
My head!  It's gonna split in two!
Oh, I see.
Huh?!  It wasn't Vegapunk?
Then, who was it, Smo-san?
Who was actually behind the giant explosion?
The one who made the weapon, and the one who blew it up,
was Caesar Clown.
At the time,
he was the number two of the science division,
but his methods were inhumane
and he was always challenging Vegapunk.
M-Master!
S-Save me!
What do you see?
Are there any hallucinations?
T-There's a giant snake in here!
Of course there isn't!
I guess that's enough.  Time to end your pain.
Vegapunk took the blame for the accident, but that's just because he was in charge.
Of course, it's a crime to develop a weapon of
mass destruction that covers an island in poison gas.
Once we figured out
the cause of the accident, we captured Caesar.
But his power proved to be too strong
and he escaped from the prisoner transport ship.
He's been in hiding ever since.
If he really is continuing his research on this island,
we've got to stop it quickly.
Before he commits another heinous crime!
I'll have to try again.
Another failure?
Failure?!  Watch your mouth!
Former Government Scientist
Bounty: 300 million beli
Master Caesar Clown
My experiments never fail.
The one four years ago wasn't a failure, either.
The World Government spouted such nonsense!
A failed experiment?
I showed how my weapon could kill an entire island!
Where's the failure in that?!
When it comes to killing enemies, I'm the best in the world.
And I've also tracked the progress
of every single one of the survivors, without fail!
Just you watch!  I'll show them
who the number one scientist in the world is!