Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
Translation & initial syncing
Yibis Fansubs
Syncing
Galaxy 9000
Sync-checking
Sewil
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
Quality-checking
Sewil and Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
Halee
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
Video editing
Sewil
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Luffy and Law's All-out Attack!
The Takeover of the New Era!
Soldiers of Punk Hazard, please listen to me!
You must be watching this somewhere, aren't you?
You're all being deceived!
Everything Caesar has told you is a lie!  You'll all be killed if you stay here!
What's he on about?
Did he go mad after being captured by Straw Hat?
Brownbeard is right below us,
on the first floor of Building R.
According to Master's plan, the Straw Hats and the marines should be there soon.
Should we call Brownbeard up to the second floor?
Let me tell you who Caesar really is!
No.  I will go down to him.
Then we're going with you.
Caesar!
Oh, my loyal subordinate, Brownbeard!
You seem to be in a rather foul mood.
What's wrong?
Return my men to me!
We were attacked and robbed
at the center of the island, but they weren't dead!
They should be back here by now!
Hey, he's provoking Master!
What?  Oh, Brownbeard's men?
Master, there are marines by the front gate,
and the doors are closed!
We can't get inside!
Please, help us!
I see, that's terrible!  I'll take care of it
right away!  Stay where you are!
Master, how do you plan to let them in?
Just leave them.
Shinokuni will reach them soon enough.
I wonder, what happened to them?
I haven't heard from them for a long time.
If they haven't returned,
then that must mean they're...
Are you worried?  Well, I guess you would be.
If they were outside, Shinokuni
would have killed them long ago, after all.
I can never trust you again!
What's gotten into him?!
What did he just say?!
You're my friends, too.
We've lived on this island for two years.
You have to get off the island right now!
Do you know what this man
has been calling you behind your backs?!
I'll tell you!
This is what he called you...
Ginnafibs!
Ginnig...
G-Ginns...
What are you saying, Brownbeard?!
Speak up!
Is that meant to be some sort of spell?
What a funny guy!
Ginnigigg...!
They will continue to obey me,
believing that I am their god of salvation!
They're merely being kept alive
so I can use them as human guinea pigs!
He called you guinea-pigs!
What's this?!  My mouth won't move!
You did something to me, didn't you, Caesar?!
What is it now?
What sort of play is this?
This is a muscle relaxant.
You can no longer speak, let alone move around.
Oh right.  I just remembered, Brownbeard.
About your former men, I remembered...
that I abandoned them.
You... damn freak!
How... How dare you kill my men?
Oh, and while we're on the subject...
I guess I'll tell you one more thing.
The weapon malfunction
that left everyone near death four years ago...
That was my doing.
It wasn't Vegapunk?!
So you almost killed them all yourself,
and then just pretended to save them?!
Hey, stop!  You have to stop!
Please help me!  Brownbeard has gone mad!
This island was made into hell on earth
by Caesar himself!
Run!  He is a devil disguised as a man!
Hey, Brownbeard!
What are you doing to our savior?!
Oh no!  Brownbeard is dangerous!
We're too late!
Straw Hat must have messed with his brain somehow!
Shoot!
And here comes the killing blow.
Gastan-
Master!
Th-That was close!
It grazed me!
Shit!  Who's there?!
It's Straw Hat... Luffy!
Just like them,
my life was also saved by Master's kindness.
Master is the kind-hearted god of salvation.
Get back to the second floor, my men!
The Straw Hats and the Navy should be here any moment!
Prepare to resume the experiment!
Yes, Sir!
Make sure all our brokers get the footage!
All of them will probably be dead within five years.
Luffy!  That is him!
He is the one
who caused the kind-hearted children to...
Who caused them to...
I know.
You've tricked everyone here, huh?
What is this island?!
Ah, of course.
This place is like gas or air.
A seemingly non-existent island!
That is why it has such close ties to the underworld.
This is a base of underworld science.
I can perform illegal experiments or obtain experimental subjects.  I'm free to do whatever I want!
I have powerful backers that completely erase everything that happens from the records!
Officially, nothing never happened!
No matter how much you cry or whine, no help will ever come here!
You know nothing about this island, Straw Hat!
If you go off half-cocked and interfere here,
you won't live to tell the tale!
The same goes for your alliance with Law.
He's trying to interfere with the SAD production.
I'm the only one who can make it, so he's using you to kidnap me.
At the factory owned by Donquixote Doflamingo,
the most dangerous member of the Seven Warlords,
it is transformed into a fruit called Smile.
Smiles are artificially created Zoan-type Devil Fruits!
It's a fruit that anyone seeking strength would want to get their hands on!
Doflamingo is using the Smiles
to make deals with the big shots in the New World.
I heard that one of the Four Emperors is already using them to form an army of hundreds of Devil Fruit users!
It sends chills down your spine, doesn't it?
Now do you understand what you're meddling with?
Do you see how many big shots you'd piss off by interfering with Doflamingo's business?!
If those big shots move against you, the world itself will tremble!
And Law is trying to make that happen.  The fool!
Someone at your level
would be completely obliterated.
You can try to capture me, but I am protected!
By Doflamingo!  By the Four Emperors!
Do you have the guts to pick a fight with them?!
I've been picking those sorts of fights the whole damn way!
M-Master!
Damn, what the hell do you think you're doing? {Xemnas: He says digijo instead of jikushou so it's a mispronunciation on Caesars part, dunno if you guys wanna put it as a mispronunciation in English or not so I'll just leave it.}
You bastard!  Didn't you listen to a word I said?
Don't think that you'll get away with this!
I have the support... of a notorious lunatic pirate!
One of the Seven Warlords, Donquixote Doflamingo!
He controls the New World's black market.
Weapons, artillery, drugs!
All dangerous goods have to go through him first!
In other words, he's the very root of evil...
and connected to every big shot in the underworld.
B-But, if you apologize now...
I'll be willing to forgive your ignorance.
T-Think carefully about all the horrifying monsters
you'll anger by harming me!
Gastille!
Take that!
There it is! {I split this into two lines because the first sentence is said by both of them whereas the second sentence is just spoken by one of them. -Starfish}
His Gas Burner can even melt steel!
Did he melt?  Or maybe he was blown away?
Th-Th-Th-That's right!
You're a rookie who only just arrived
in The New World, so you might not understand yet...
but there's a monster in this laboratory right now!
It's Vergo!
No one can withstand his Color of Arms!
Both Smoker and Law are going to die.
Your entire crew is going...
I don't care!
Shinokuni, a deadly gas
that petrifies people and leeches their life,{Excuse me, wouldn't placing a period at the end of this line make it a sentence-fragment? Which, when last I checked, was generally regarded as something to be avoided? -Starfish}
has been leaking into the laboratory.
What are you doing?
We would've caught up to the children already if you just ran in a straight line!
Shut up!
Try and run faster everyone, we have to hurry!
I feel dizzy, like I just woke up from a dream.
Don't worry, there's nothing wrong with you.  It's just an aftereffect from the sedative.
Most of the survivors
are heading for the only exit off the island.
Located on the first floor of Building R,
where Luffy and Caesar are currently fighting.
But Kin'emon continues to search for his son,
Momonosuke.
What a terrible mistake I have made, Momonosuke! {Added "I have made" here because otherwise it looks like he's scolding Momonosuke for making a mistake, when what he's actually getting at is "Momonosuke turned into a dragon. I just killed a dragon! IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN HIM! D:"}
What?
Momonosuke transformed into a small dragon?
Oh no!  I might have cut down my own son!
Momonosuke!
I have done something unforgivable! {Xemnas: He actually said "I have done something that cannot be taken back", but I went with this translation.}
Kin'emon-san, you mustn't run in that direction!
That area is filling with poisonous gas!
It's a sneak attack!
Why does this always happen to me?
What are you trying to do?
Against a superior Haki user, turning into smoke just increases the size of your body.
It makes you an easier target!
Why do you insist on using your ability?
Have you lost your head?
This fighting style isn't like you at all, Smoker-kun.
Demon Staff!
You may want to punish me for dishonoring the Navy...
but you lack the skill, Smoker.
Bravery alone will not protect your subordinates.
Smoker, thanks for returning my heart.
So that's what you were up to.
My debt to you has been repaid.
Hurry up and defeat him.
You really hated
that you were indebted to a pirate, huh?
It's an embarrassment as a Marine.
I'd never be able to face my subordinates.
Well, I suppose it's true that you helped me.
This is the end for you...
Vergo-san.
You brat,
you finally remember how to speak to your superiors.
If that's what you want to believe.
Don't think that you can stay on your high horses forever, you two!
I know you can hear me, Joker!
Vergo is done for.
You've lost your most important subordinate,
and Caesar will be taken down by Straw Hat.
Which means, you will lose all your SAD.
It was your own overconfidence
that blinded you to this possibility.
Go ahead and look down on us and laugh as usual
while you think of your next move.
But you won't be laughing for very long...
because we're going to keep on surprising you.
You're acting really tough for a little shrimp.
But are you sure you can back it up?
I would suspect...
that you've upset Vergo.
Do you remember what happened last time?
Remember?  Remember what happens when you push Vergo too far?
It must have traumatized you.
There's no way you could ever forget...
the terror that Vergo put into you.
Your cutting ability may be powerful but...
his Haki will easily block it.
You are no match for him,
in neither strength nor position!
It's been two years since the Great War.
Who set what in motion back then?
All you did is protect the position you've grown comfortable in.
All Whitebeard did was end an era.
Navy HQ has put together a new military force...
but the major players haven't made a move.
It's as if they're preparing for something.
Indeed, that war was nothing but a prologue.
You always said that an unstoppable wave is coming.
One that brings a new age for the strong.
I've destroyed the gears.
And now, there's no turning back!