Having left Fishman Island, the ship is finally ascending toward the New World.
Things are going great!
It's going so well, it's almost scary!
Ah, this feels great.
What do you think of my Shower Tempo?
Want to join in?
Who, me?
I'm fine.  I washed myself two days ago.
I'm more interested in that cloud that looks like cotton candy.  It looks delicious!
It isn't edible.
Really?  You mean it isn't sweet cotton candy?
What?  There's something sweet and tasty
in the shower room?
It's true.  It really does look sweet and delicious!
Please, Nami-san!
Turn this way!
Chopper, don't get too close to that cloud.
Scary!  I don't want to eat that cloud after all!
This is so relaxing...
How I've missed Sunny's bath for the past two years!
Taking a bath and looking at the deep sea,
which looks like the night sky...
This is the life!
Will they be alright on deck without you?
I'll get out of the bath
before we enter the rising currents, so it'll be fine.
If any sea monsters appear,
I'm sure they can handle them.
Hurry, Usopp!
Now, wait just a minute!
We're up against giant fish!
A weak rope wouldn't be able to hold 'em!
Oh my, you seem to be having fun.
I didn't think of it on the way down
because I was too excited about Fishman Island...
but if we catch a deep sea fish and pull it up to the surface...
Sanji can cook it up for us, right?
I hope it'll go well with cola!
Cooking, huh?  Great idea!
I'm looking forward to having a drink
to celebrate our entry into the New World.
So, which one should we go for?
I want one that looks delicious.
Perhaps we should fry that one and eat it with salt?
Fried fish with salt, huh?  Sounds great!
That one might be nice grilled in sweet soy sauce.
Grilled fish, huh?
Oh!  That looks good, too!
If we put mayonnaise on it, it'll definitely taste nice!
Huh?  Which one?
No, there's no way.
That one will taste nasty no matter how you cook it.
Really?  Well, any one will do.
Sanji can cook anything and make it tasty!
You want to eat that one after all?!
Wait, isn't it a bit too big?!
Quick!  Get it!
Sure-Kill Capture Star
Alright!
We caught ourselves a deep sea fish!
I wanna eat it soon!
Still, is that even a fish?
Maybe it's just some old guy?
Old guy?
It got turned into bait!
Hey hey hey!  Again?!
They just keep coming!
Hurry and reel it in, Usopp!
Huh?!  No way!
The ship's gonna capsize!
The fish just keep coming!
They're like matryoshka dolls!
Did something happen?  The ship's swaying.
And they're really noisy out on the deck.
I guess leaving them alone was a bad idea, after all.
One Sword Style
360 Pound Cannon/Phoenix of 360 Earthly Desires
Great job, Zoro!
What's all the fuss about?
Hey, Sanji!  Look at this!
I see, great idea!
Cooking a deep sea fish, huh?  I'd love to try it.
More importantly... Why are you cooked?
And you should be even more excited!
Because there are two more fish inside it!
Anyway, are we still moving up toward the surface?
I have a bad feeling, like we're sinking.
You're probably just imagining it.
W-What's that?
A giant sea snake!
Right!  Move us closer!  We're gonna eat that too!
We can't pull that with the ship!
Wait!  Could that be...
The Whitestrom?!
A giant white maelstrom, which appears underwater out of nowhere, just like a living dragon!
What?!
An underwater maelstrom?!
Sheesh, those guys are just...
What?!  This is bad!  Is that the Whitestrom?!
From what I've heard,
any ship that gets caught in this vortex...
reappears days later in an unbelievably distant sea,
with no trace of the crew!
That must mean that everyone dies!
This is really bad after all!  Let's get out of here!
The ship is carried to an unbelievably distant sea?
So... this is like one of those super cool warp zones?!
No, you moron!
Everyone!  Get us away from that vortex, quickly!
Hey!  Here comes the navigator!
We're getting out of here, you idiots!
What's with that fish?!
Oh, we caught it!
What are you doing?!
We can't move with that thing attached to the ship!
See?  The fish is getting sucked into the vortex!
Crap!  Get it out!
Aye!
No!  Cut it loose!
What?!  But what about our cooked deep sea fish?!
Which is more important, the fish or our lives?!
I only left you alone for ten minutes!
How could you get us into this much trouble?!
Franky!  Use the Coup de Burst!
No, it's super-too late!
Right? { tlc: Franky: Nope, it's way too late!  Franky: Isn't that right? Nami: I told you to do it! }
I told you to do it!
We're getting sucked into the vortex!
This is quite the predicament!
This is awesome!
Nooo!  We're done for!
I don't wanna die!
Grab on to the ship!
We stopped!
What's this black wall?
That wailing... Is it...
Oh, that scar!
I'll come see you again!
And when I do, let's have another fight!
Laboon?!
Laboon!
We will definitely sail around the world
and come back here!
Wait for us!
Laboon!  You've grown this big?!
Don't be ridiculous!
Laboon is in the first half of the Grand Line!
He's so big, he couldn't even make it through
the hole in the Red Line!
Amazing!
It's like a miracle.
I never thought we'd see a pod of Island Whales.
That one has wounds on its head that look just like Laboon's.
Yeah!  The scars are exactly the same!
What a shock!  It really isn't Laboon?
We're going to deliver Binks' brew...
Laboon!  Stop!
Listen to me!
It's me!  I was part of the Rumbar Pirates!
It's me, Brook!
Come to your senses!
I told you, that's a different whale!
Laboon!
This is no time to be calmly admiring them!
Even if we're out of the maelstrom, we're still in danger!
First of all, we have to do a headcount to make sure nobody got thrown overboard in the vortex!
Nami-san!
Yes!
Robin-chan!
I'm here.
Okay.  We've gotta get out of here in a hurry!
If we collide with these gigantic whales, the ship will take major damage!
Count us too!
Sanji-kun!  It is my shame to admit that the other six crewmates have not yet received honorable deaths!
Nami-san, what are your orders?!
We can stay where we are.
That's right, we're doing just fine, you idiots!
Resume whale watching immediately!
What the hell?!
This enormous pod of whales
is creating its own ocean current.
Trying to resist it will just put us in more danger.
Make sure the sails are open!
Turn the ship in the same direction that the whales are moving!
Aye!
Of course... This must be Laboon's homeland.
Are any of his relatives here?!
That's dangerous, Brook!
If anyone here is looking for a small whale
who got separated from the pod fifty years ago...
then don't worry!  He's doing fine,
in a sea on the opposite side of the world!
According to Luffy-san, he has grown big and strong!
Please, don't be concerned!
Ride the ocean current!
Right!
We're going to deliver Binks's brew,
entrusting ourselves to the whims of the ocean breeze and waves.
Beyond the tides, even the evening sun is cheerful.
The song of birds, drawing circles in the sky.
Farewell to the port, to the old hometown.
Let's sing a song with a DON, a song for our departure!
The waves of gold and silver turn to splashes of water,
as we set off for the edge of the sea!
We're going to deliver Binks's brew.
We are pirates, crossing the seas.
The sea is our pillow and the ship is our mattress.
The skull is emblazoned on our sail and flag.
A storm is coming from the distant sky.
The waves are dancing, beat on the drums!
Hey!  You're letting us ride you!
We can let them carry us like this.
If you're caught by a treacherous wind, this could be the end,
We all seem to be riding the same rising current.
but the sun will always rise in the morning!
Luffy?
I see it!
Let's go, men!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
We're here!
In the New World!
We did it!
We finally made it here!
The weather's the worst!
Thunderclouds in the sky!
The wind blows fiercely!
The sea is raging!
The compass needles are out of control!
Go!
Yahoo!
What's that?
What?!  Impossible!
A red sea?
Look!  A volcanic eruption!
Listen up, Luffy!
None of the three compass needles point to that island!
It's an anomaly, even in the abnormal New World!
Another eruption!
We can see it right there!
Who cares about the needles?
We're dropping anchor, no matter what you say!
No way!  We can't get any closer than this!
I mean, it's a sea of fire!
I don't get you!
The fire...
It's only a matter of time before the ship catches fire!
No!
The Sunny is super-fireproof!
Even if it shouldn't burn,
there's something wrong with this sea!
Look, the fish are nothing but bones!  Bones!  Bones!
What?  Did you call me?
Hey, what's this?
The Snail Phone is crying.
Hey, what's wrong?!  Does your stomach hurt?
You idiot, that's an emergency signal.
Someone's calling for help.
So, if I pick up the phone,
we can communicate with them?
Wait, Luffy!  Less than fifty percent of emergency signals are real!
The Navy uses this kind of trap all the time,
so that's probably what this is!
If you pick it up and they've got the line bugged, then they'll know we're in the area!
Good point, Robin!
Listen, Luffy,
we ought to think this through carefully bef-
Hello?  My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
You answered too soon, and you're saying too much!
Please, help me!
What's wrong?!
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
No, I'm not your boss.
It's cold, you say?
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
Samurai?
Hey, what's your name?!
Where are you?!
It doesn't matter who I am, just save me.
I'm on...
Punk Hazard!
He was killed!
I-Is this...
I suspect foul play.
Of course it's foul play!  He was just murdered!
The New World is scary!
He could have been acting.  It still might be a trap.
She keeps her composure!
C'mon, Robin-san!
He said samurai, Brook.
Yes, it must be one of those samurai...
The name of the swordsmen from the Wano Kingdom.
The Wano Kingdom is an isolated nation, which never lets outsiders enter.
It doesn't even have any ties to the World Government.
Apparently the swordsmen called samurai
are so strong, even the Navy won't approach them.
The Named Sword Shuusui,
once wielded by a legendary samurai.
If you are its master, this blade should be satisfied.
How frustrating, for this samurai body to fall.
A kingdom like that exists?
But he said he was in Punk Hazard, not the Wano Kingdom.
Did he mean that flaming island?
If he was using a Baby Snail Phone,
then that island is the only one within range.
Alright!  Let's go save that guy!
No!
Luffy, think about it!
Chances are, we're already too late!
Samurai are scary!
I'm scared too!
It doesn't matter who I am, just save me.
I'm on...
Punk Hazard!
Smoker-san, wasn't that...
Damn it!  What route did they take?!
First there was the incident on Fishman Island,
then the uproar after that...
and if I project their route from that point...
Punk Hazard, huh?  Makes sense.
P-Please stop!  I'll do anything!
I'll do whatever you want!
We want you to burn!
Hot!
Stop it, you brutes!  Stop torturing the pirates!
Tashigi!  We're heading for Punk Hazard.
But Smoker-san, Punk Hazard...
has been uninhabited since it was sealed off
after the incident four years ago!
It makes no sense for people to be there!
True, it shouldn't be possible
for any creatures to live there.
But it's worth a look, regardless.
We're setting sail for Punk Hazard!
Huh?  But Vice-Admiral Smoker...
That place is forbidden, didn't you know that?
Don't try to tell to me about the rules, scum!
Right!
That settles it.  The ones who'll go are...
Us.
How exciting.
How depressing.
Oh, you won?  Lucky you!
No, I lost!  Someone trade with me!
Here, have my special giant shellfish lunchbox.
Can't wait to taste it!
Awesome!  She made a pathway of clouds!
Did you learn to make that stuff
they used back on Sky Island?
It's just clouds,
so you better cross it while it's stable.
Got it!
Alright!
Here goes the scouting party!
We're counting on you, Mini Merry!
Hang in there, you all!
You're so lucky at drawing straws!
We'll be able to go later.
Take care!
Usopp, good luck!
Trade places with me!
This giant shellfish is delicious!
Hey, why are you eating that already?!
Oh, we've climbed above the flames!  This is fun!
Now we can get past the sea of fire!
Will these clouds last until we head back?
Good thing the rain stopped.
Perfect weather for scouting.
But it's so hot!
Nami-san,
does that cloud reach all the way to the island?
I don't know.
I'm so glad I didn't have to accompany Luffy.
I can't stand the heat!
I couldn't let him go alone, after all.
They'll come back
once they see that there's nothing there!
You've thought this through, haven't you?
I'll make a cold dessert out of the giant shellfish for our kind Nami-san right now!
Yay!
See?  That's definitely the entrance!
Now listen, people might have lived here before...
but there's no way they could live here now!
The Snail Phone must have
picked up a transmission from some distant island!
Right, Robin?
It doesn't look pretty, but this is surprisingly tasty.
You too?!  Why are you eating it now?!
Aren't you not gonna eat?
I couldn't swallow anything right now!
Ah, I'm having an unexpected relapse
of my disease from two years ago!
Hey, you guys... Honestly,
I've got the "I can't enter that island"-disease!
I know.
No doubt about it.  This is the right place.
So this is Punk Hazard?
Let's get the Merry onto the island.
So the emergency signal
came from this place after all?
Looks like it's forbidden to enter this island.
Luffy, look at that!
Danger... Keep out?
See?  The logos of
the World Government and Navy are here!
So basically, even if someone is inside,
it'll be someone on the Government's side!
This was a waste of time.  Let's go back!
Gah, so hot.
Hey, you guys!
Breaking and entering is a crime, you know!
Oh wait, pirates are criminals.
Don't blame me if you end up
in a fight with the World Government!
Oh wait, we already did that.
H-Hey, wait!
It's so hot... But, anyway...
This whole place is on fire.
It doesn't look like this was always a burning island.
Was there some kind of disaster?  Or an accident?
Hey, Luffy!
Those probably weren't people's houses.
This must have been a government facility.
So was this place sealed off
after it caught fire and became too dangerous?
Or was it a dangerous facility to begin with?
The fact that the Log Pose
isn't pointing to this island bothers me.
Hey!
Guy from earlier, are you here?!
We've come to save you!
Hey!
Come out!
Samurai!
Don't call the murderer!
Did your appetite return?
Shut it!  I'm drowning my sorrows!
Oh yeah, and this has been bothering me for a while...
The guy on the Snail Phone said he was freezing, right?
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
You've got a point.
It's so hot here, yet he said it was cold.
Maybe he was an idiot?
What kind of reasoning is that?!
Could there be any cold places on this burning island?
Or did he mean that he was so scared that he was getting the chills?
Nami, is something wrong?
Well, the clouds...
The sky above this island is really weird, now that I take a closer look at it.
It almost looks arctic on the far side.
That's impossible!
A giant!
No.
This is way bigger than a giant!
Is that...
W-What?!  D-Do these things really exist?!
No, they're fictional creatures!
How could they exist for real?!
But just look at it!
What else could you call it?
A dragon?!