Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
Translation & initial syncing
Yibis Fansubs
Syncing
Galaxy 9000
Sync-checking
Sewil
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
Quality-checking
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
Video editing
Sewil
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Dragon Named Momonosuke and
the Menacing Snow Fruit User!
Momonosuke?
Building C - Underground Garbage Dump
That would be my name.
I've heard that name before...
Where did I hear it?
As if I'd know.
You have probably mistaken me for another person.
More importantly, do you...
Stop drooling!
I am not food.
I would rather eat you than be eaten by you.
Restrain yourself!
Momonosuke (Dragon)
Huh? Momonosuke must be stuck here somewhere, talking with his farts!
Hey, where are you!
W-What do you think you're doing?
Huh?! An eel's talking to me?!
Stop drooling! I'm not an eel!
You're pretty hungry too, aren't you?
Don't be a fool.
As if a mere ten days without food
would cause a warrior's stomach to growl.
Ten days?!
Who are you, and what are you doing here?
I'm Luffy, the man who's gonna be the Pirate King.
P-P-P-Pi-Pir...
Stop lying.
A pirate would be bigger
and weigh at least 300 kg.
They would be a lot stronger and fiercer as well.
I really don't care. But Eel...
How do- { def: manga has Luff calling him an eel here, which is necessary for the next line to make sense }
My name is Momonosuke!
I see, so you are a fellow outsider.
All that I have learned about this place
is that it is home to many ill children.
I don't know what kind of island this is
or what has happened to me.
This all began when I stowed away aboard a certain ship.
I did not want to involve myself with those children, yet they treated me with such kindness.
We're getting fed now. Aren't you gonna eat?
I am a samurai, I do not accept charity from others.
Even though they were so nice to me, I was on edge so...
I have your food here.
I told you I have no need of it!
You should eat something. We've all left our parents behind.
As if any of you could understand my feelings!
We should get alo-
I am Master Caesar.
Now, go inside.
From now on, this will be your playground.
Hey, what's your name?
I have... no name!
Here are some snacks.
Help yourself.
I have no need of them!
How about some candy?
I have no need of it!
What? One of the kids has escaped?
Yeah, but according to the name list,
there's no one missing.
That's weird.
Hey you.
Hmm, so you're Momonosuke-kun?
This is the secret room.
You're not supposed to be in here.
Stop interacting with me. You are causing me trouble.
I am searching for a way out.
I am getting out of here.
There is something that I need to do.
It must be hard, but it's the same for all the kids here.
They all want to go home to their parents
as soon as possible.
We've gathered from different islands to get our disease treated. We all feel the same way.
I have a lot of things I want to do when I go home too.
Everyone gets along
and has heaps of fun in the Biscuits Room.
We can forget about all the painful stuff.
So you have to eat properly too, Momonosuke!
But I...
The door to the secret room is open.
Oh no! Someone's coming!
Let's go, Momonosuke-kun!
Is someone in here?
What's going on?
Who's that?
A-A dragon?!
What's going on?
M-Momonosuke-kun has...
Look at this.
The artificial devil fruit that Vegapunk made
was inside this case.
Wasn't that a failed experiment?
Yeah, that's what I heard.
In other words, I am human.
So that's it. It's a devil fruit.
An eel-man?
Then why don't you just turn back into a human?
Huh? I can turn back into a human? How?
I dunno. I'm not a Zoan type.
But damn, how high is the roof?
I can't see the hole that I came through.
I want to get out through that hole
and inform the children of what I know!
I overheard...
...what that man called Caesar is truly planning.
Another bunch of well-behaved, obedient kids!
And the other kids are growing quite nicely.
However, this experiment tests
the limits of tolerance to this drug.
They won't last much longer.
All of them will probably be dead within 5 years.
Then we'll have to gather some more kids.
But then again,
there are failures in every experiment.
It's an unavoidable sacrifice.
I thought he was a doctor,
but in fact, he is a terrible man who intends to let the children die!
I was on my way to tell the children,
but I fell down here whilst hiding in a trash can.
Caesar!
Alright, Momo!
I'm getting out of here, and I'm taking you with me.
But how will you get all the way up there?
I'm gonna climb the wall. Hold onto me.
The kids are fine.
My crewmates have already gone to save them.
Is that true?
They'll be able to handle the job.
There's no need to worry.
I see. You clearly cannot be just a mere...
pi... rate.
What's wrong?
Are you really that hungry?
Hey! Get a hold of yourself.
Get a hold of yourself!
We're flying!
Building B, 2nd Floor - Inner Area, Corridor To the Examination Room
Do you think they'll be okay without me?
Then again, Zoro's with them, so they should be fine.
Hey Brook, tell us if you find
those Sea Stone handcuffs that Robin wants. {Starfish: They're both the same thing, aren't they? So by all means, if you think "shackles" sounds better then I have no objections.}
Forgive me for having to rely
on your sorcery, Sir Corpse!
Just leave it all to me.
Building D - SAD Manufacturing Room
Building B - Near the Biscuits Room
Everyone, this way to the kids in the Biscuits Room!
That hurts, bro!
Stop being a crybaby!
Stop being crazy!
Hurry it up! If you want to save the kids, then hurry to the Biscuits Room!
Building B, 3rd Floor - Biscuits Room
It's cold! There's a blizzard in this room!
As soon as I take my coat off
I run into the Snow ability?!
Damn that snow-woman!
Stop, everyone!  You can't eat that candy!
Run, Mocha!
Stop running and give us the candy, Mocha!
No, everyone come to your senses!
Stop trying to hog it all for yourself.
Stop running!
I only need to slow them down a bit.
Don't interfere.
Robin!
You guys go and stop the kids!
The enemy is a Logia.
I'll fight her!
Are you okay, Robin?
I'm okay, it's just a scratch.
Let's hurry and stop the children.
Yeah.
Nami, the children are about to leave the room.
Wait up, Mocha!
I promised to stop them,
and if we don't, it will put Mocha in danger!
Stop running!
Give us the candy!
I won't give it to you guys.
Chopper-chan told me what kind of candy this is.
You can't eat this candy.
Everyone, please return to normal!
It can't be helped, Mocha.
We're sick.
Adults will die if they catch our disease.
You'd be even sadder if your parents were to die, right?
They said that they'd treat and heal us in one year.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Caesar Clown.
Call me Master.
You are my first generation of patients.
I'm happy to be working with you.
I once lost my only son to this disease.
I never want to see a child suffer from this disease again.
Nor do I want to see a fellow parent grieving over the loss of their children.
Ah, forgive me. How embarrassing, that you would see me cry.
Are you okay, Master-san?
Thank you, you're such a kind child.
That's right, I still haven't introduced you to the other sick children from other islands.
I'm Uzu, pleased to meet you.
Candy...!
I'm Doran.
Wait, Mocha!
My name is Konbu.
Give me some candy!
Some new friends have arrived today.
Make sure you all get along!
If anything happens, you can tell me.
Okay, Monet-san!
Even that kind Monet-san was lying.
It was all a lie!
This is a reward for doing so well in your treatment.
Some candy from Master.
Let's all escape from here,
so please just return to normal, everyone!
We have to catch up to the children.
I'm counting on you.
You bitch!
What the hell are you playing at?!
Just wait a second!
Why are you coming over here?!
Wait, Nami! Stop!
Stop using me as a shield!
Darn, I missed.
Why are you targeting the weak ones?
Out of the way, Zoro!
Heat Egg!
So heat works.
Don't come over here anymore!
The Cat Burglar, with a bounty of 16 million belly.
Dammit, she dived into the snow again!
Do you even want to fight, you damn snow-woman?!
The exit!{ Btwb: The "Huh?" was said a while before she says "The exit!", so I just removed it. Someone else can time it back in, if so desired. }
Oh no!
Snow Fence!
Perpetual Snow!
Nami!
The snow...
It's so cold, I can't move!
She went after them again!
Look out, Chopper!
Cuatro Manos!
Four Flowers
Spank!
Nami! {This line is super short but it goes from the end of a scene to the start of the next D: -Fadeout4}
That was scary.
How troublesome.
Those children are Master's precious guinea pigs,
and my mission is to protect Caesar and his experiment.
Who was the one who made Mocha rebel against us?
What did you say?
Those children asked us to save them!
Get out of the way, you guys!
Get going.
Let's hurry.
Yeah.
Mocha, just hold on a bit longer!
Such uncivilized people.
Day after day, we treated them kindly,
and gave them a life with no problems.
And here you are, trying to rob us, their guardians, of the very thing that matters the most to us.
You people are just like pirates.
It seems like we're on the same page.
I told you it's uncivilized.
Stop interfering with my mission.
Sword Snow!
Skin Sword!
You've only been blocking my attacks.
Why won't you attack me?
To be honest, I didn't think I could win against you.
But that might not be the case.
There's another room in the back!
Let's find the kids and get out of here!
Isn't it kinda cold in here?!
The Navy?
Let's go through that door back there!
Everyone's trying to steal the children.
I won't let anyone take them.
Charge!
Why the hell are you leading them?!
Hey bro, the kids aren't here, but Pirate Hunter Zoro is.
He's one arrogant bastard.
Alright, guys.
Pull down your lower lip and make fun of him!
They should all slip on the snow, hit their heads and die.{ Btwb: Not a technically correct sentence, but I'll let it slide since it sounds like something Zoro would say. }
Hey, Nami and Robin are through that door.
You're in the way, so hurry up and get going.
Wow, you may be an idiot, but that was some good information.
Alright, let's go, you g...
Is what I want to say, but there's a beauty right here!
Seriously?!
She's so cute!
You guys are annoying! Hurry up and go on ahead!
But take a closer look. She doesn't look human.
A human-faced bird?
It's a Harpy!
B-But...
besides that, she's damn cute!
In fact, it makes her even cuter.
Man, she's sexy!
Why are you weak to compliments?!{Starfish: Despite being the one who wrote this, I do not like this phrasing. Plz do something about it.}
So, why is it snowing in here?
No matter who they are, I won't let anyone take the children away.
What's happened to my shoulder?!
You bitch!
S-She's a Logia!
Damn that woman.
A swordswoman that uses Haki?!
Captain-chan!
I temporarily stopped the gas from entering this room.
But, it might leak in from somewhere else.
We don't have much time.
Everyone go after the children!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to stay here.
I figured I'm needed here!
Huh?!