We will raise up our feelings for you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
We will rise up with our boundless strength
kagirinaki chikara umareru
No matter where we are,
we will obtain it
motomeru naraba dokomademo
We will move
with our unchanged bonds
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
It's always a pleasure that
I've been really wanting to meet you now
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
It's always a shame that
we have all of the laughters and tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
It is connecting between the winds Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We will soar up high into the skies
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why are you giving up on searching
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why keep on fighting by yourself
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Hey don't hide out your future
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Your dream is in your grasp
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Just close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
If you want to find your answers
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
We will always keep on our path
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo
To the sea that we haven't seen yet
mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
Through the end of this wide blue world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
You will come back to your place
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
Together forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
We've decided this so long ago
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Luffy vs. Sanji
Fly away...
... to the end of the New World!
Cannon Ball!
Mama, Smoothie-sama of the
Three Sweet Commanders has arrived!
Whole Cake
Chateau
Okay.
Sweet Commander Katakuri-sama
will be here soon, too!
Oh, it's been a while since
they all got together!
What about Cracker?
Is he home yet?
I bet he'll be back soon
with Straw Hat's head as a present!
I can't wait!
Hm? Is that...?
What happened?
What is it?!
Big Brother!
Big Brother Cracker!
This can't be happening!
He's one of our Three Sweet Commanders!
Who did this?! I'll kill the bastard!
Charlotte Mont d'Or
19th Son of Charlotte, Minister of Cheese
Charlotte Opera
5th Son of Charlotte, Minister of Cream
Where did he fly from-fa?!
I think he went to the woods...
Charlotte Galette
18th Daughter of Charlotte, Minister of Butter
... to take care of Straw
Hat Luffy last night.
That means...
Straw Hat Luffy must be somewhere near-fa!
Put out an emergency alert!
Evacuate!
What happened?!
Sweet Commander Cracker-sama was defeated!
What?!
The Seducing
Woods
Luffy! Are you okay?!
I ate a lifetime's worth of biscuits...
But you shrunk back down a lot.
Gear Fourth takes so much energy.
Pound!
Where were you?!
Well, I'm sorry for running away.
I thought you were going to lose.
You're being pretty honest!
Because that guy was one
of the Three Sweet Commanders...
Well...
Anyway, we won!
We did it! We did it!
Yay! Yay!
Lighten up!
We beat one of the Emperor's top officers!
I... can't even move...
What have we done...
We helped them defeat Cracker-sama-ju.
Everyone knows that we Homies
cannot resist the power of Mama's Vivre Card!
That is why even Mama's
children aren't allowed to carry one!
Why do you have it?!
Is that true?
So it's really quite a valuable thing.
But you're in big trouble.
Why?
When Sweet Commander Snack was defeated...
The vengeful Cracker's
fleet blackened the sea
and the angry Linlin created a storm...
I heard it sank the enemy
ship in the blink of an eye!
Storm?
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
Weather?
On her left hand, Zeus, a thundercloud!
On her right hand, Prometheus, a sun!
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
Before she hears about this,
you'd better run!
I don't care if she gets mad!
What?!
I'm the one who wants to get mad!
First of all, Sanji, that fool!
To my buds, I've gotta
see a woman. I'll be back.
How could he disappear leaving
a note behind suddenly!
Without telling us why!
This is my problem.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Thanks to Pudding's map,
we made it this far,
but Pekoms went missing.
And although Pudding said
that she'd bring Sanji,
no one was there
at the rendezvous point.
We wasted a lot of time while we were lost in the forest!
When they get married,
Sanji will Big Mom's subordinate, right?!
We gotta get moving!
Yeah! When is the wedding?
Cracker said the Vinsmokes will enter...
a castle today, where the
wedding will take place.
What time is it now? We've gotta stop them!
A-Are you serious?
If you don't run away, you'll really...
I'm not gonna run away!
Hey, tree!
You know where the castle is, don't you?!
Well...
Carry me to the castle!
No way-ju...
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
Nami, can you hear me?!
Chopper!
How are you guys?
We're okay!
If things go well, we'll see you guys and Brook...
What?
That doesn't look okay! Chopper?
Either way, we can't be saved from the outside!
Just keep...
Chopper?!
Nami, don't worry! We're fine...
How can I not worry?
Right, we're gonna go to the castle
to find Sanji-kun!
Okay!
Once you rescue Sanji,
let us know through this mirror aga...
It broke!
Hey, Chopper?! Carrot?!
It turned into a normal mirror.
Are they okay?
Has he gotten smaller than before?!
Whoa... What?
What's going on?!
Whoa...
He's almost back to normal!
Is that humanly possible?!
– Meat...
– Meat?!
Hey, young girl.
You're lucky.
Why?
There they are.
That's Germa 66.
Can you see Sanji?
Is that it?!
Hey, Sanji!
Your Majesty, something
is charging towards us.
It's been a while!
What?! That idiot made it this far
into Big Mom's territory?!
What is the big tree behind him?!
It's running!
Hey!
Sanji-kun!
I'm glad that we made it in time!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Why are they... here?
Is that Straw Hat Luffy?
Hey! We're here to pick you up!
Sanji!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
Let's go, Sanji!
You said you'd be back in the note
but I didn't wanna wait.
Banquet!
I was gonna come by myself, but...
You said your hands are important to you.
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
If someone declines Mama's invitation...
... So, Zoro and the others must've gotten
to the Wano Country...
We'll chop this guy's head off.
... That's why Nami, Chopper, Brook and I came
to pick you up. And...
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed...
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll chop off my own head as well!
Sanji, I'm hungry!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
That's how a parent pays the price.
– It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
– Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't catch a cold.
... And I had no choice, so...
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
I'm a prince...
of the Germa Kingdom!
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
I thought that it would drive you to grief.
The difference between our standings
couldn't be clearer.
If I stay here, I can spend money
and use soldiers and servants as I like.
Going back to that crappy ship
with you and your friends...
... or staying here,
marrying Big Mom's beautiful daughter.
It's pretty obvious which is a happier life.
Don't take the note seriously.
I won't go back with you!
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Get out of here... I forgot your name.
Screw that! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
Sit back!
I'll...
... send them away!
What do you mean by sending us away, Sanji?
Get packing.
There is no other meaning.
I don't know what made you come,
but I appreciate
that you took the trouble.
Having said that, if you really think about me,
you should've done the opposite.
Rather than being with you guys
who are poor and weak,
it'd be better to be part of
the rich and powerful Big Mom Pirates.
I'll be happier.
I'm not so sure about you
becoming the King of the Pirates,
to be honest.
It's only human nature
to jump on the bandwagon.
Stop joking, Sanji-kun!
What are you talking about?!
Then, all this time,
you've been fooling me.
Yeah, that's right.
I've actually been looking down on you.
What is that glow? A flame?!
This ought to be fun to watch.
I bet you didn't see it coming,
so it's hard to accept.
I'll prove it to you. Get ready.
Diable Jambe...
No, Sanji-kun!
Joue Shot!
Cheek Shot
Luffy! You're bleeding!
Sanji-kun, did you really...
Get ready to fight.
Use your Haki or you're gonna die.
I just wanna talk to you.
Why do I need Haki?
I'm not gonna...
... fight you!
Then...
... go away!
I'm not gonna do that either!
You've always...
... been selfish!
Hey you, cook!
Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Please stop, Sanji-kun!
We just came to pick you up!
Luffy has...
... fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
So his body is...
Cut it out, Nami!
Stay out of this!
This is...
... a duel!
You call this a duel?!
Sanji-kun!
Get out of my sight now!
Luffy!
Go away!
Get out of my face...
... now!!
I refuse!
Luffy!
Sanji-kun!
Here we go!
Sanji-kun... Please stop...
That's enough! Stop, Sanji-kun!
We'll leave!!
I won't!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Concassé!
Crush
Luffy! Luffy!
How strong...
After all, he's a Vinsmoke.
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Hey! Stay with me!
Luffy! Luffy!
Hey, Sanji!
Goodbye!
Sorry...
... we should never have done this!
Oh! A bitchy girl! How hot!
The superfluous ties have
finally been severed.
Thanks for waiting.
– Let's go.
– Yes, sir.
Luffy!
Wait!
Sanji!!
"Low-class pirate"?!
I know you were just saying
things that you didn't want to!
Stop lying!
Did you think
that you could send me away that easily?!
Screw that!
No matter how many times you kick me,
you're the one...
... that gets hurt!!
Luffy! Why?!
Whatever the reason is, he can't do this...
Shut up!
Should we stop, Sanji?
Keep going.
Say...
do you know about the All Blue?
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
Our journey...
... isn't over yet!
I'll be here waiting!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
... starving to death!
You're the cook of my ship!
He was making food for rats again!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
Editing:
Feeso,
Galaxy 9000
Timing:
Halee
Quality Assurance:
Galaxy 9000,
Grug,
Mr. Luffy,
Pepperjack
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Translation:
Crunchyroll