It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
can!
can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
chou
chou
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all!  Now, yes, we can!
can!
can!
a
you
nk
can!
Yes, we can!  You can!  This moment...
yes
n
we
can!
ca
you
ny
can!
can!
o
I
k
can!
a
ko
We can!  I can!  With this feeling of freedom...
can!
n
can
I
can!
Now...  Now, oh yes, we can!
i
yes
we
can!
can!
swe
yes
we
can!
Yes, we can!
yes
ye
we
w
can!
ca
Seems like there's nothing wrong.
Yep!
I'm kind of hungry again!
Don't worry. We'll see an island soon.
Let me give you
some extra information while I can.
There are a total of 34 islands
surrounding Whole Cake Island.
That many?!
There are 34 ministers, one for each island,
to run the place.
They call this vast marine area...
... Totto Land!
Totto Land
Mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm, I see. I'm sorry.
I thought it was an enemy ship.
Yeah, I hijacked the ship from a pirate group.
I'll present it to Mama myself.
Oh!
Do you have something sweet in that ship?
– Of course.
– Mama will be happy then!
It's a surprise.
Don't report to her about that ship.
Oh, that's wonderful!
Understood! Pekoms-sama, that's very cool!
Look at that!
Bricks and houses and everything...
They're all...
... made of chocolate!
A chocolate town!
It's like a dream!
Wow! There are so many kinds
of people and animals!
What the...! What the...!
What's with this town?!
Look! Chocolate is pouring out!
Oh, I knew you wanted to start
with the fountain of chocolate!
The chocolate spout!
Chocolate Bathhouse
"Chocolate Bathhouse"?!
A chocolate bath?!
– Chocolate clothes?!
– Can you eat them?!
I managed to cover for us,
but we should not stay long. Grr!
We gotta do what we have to do and just go...
Are you done?
Wow! This is cute!
Oh, Nami, you look great!
Thanks!
Hey, look! My costume looks
quite nice too, right?
Yeah, that's really gorgeous!
How's this?
Do I look like a pirate, Broo...
What?
Do you want more?
It will take one more day to
get to Whole Cake Island, where Sanji is.
Go food shopping.
Okay! Yay!
Pedro, do you have binoculars?!
Thanks! Let's see...
Wow! It's so diverse here, Pekoms!
I see Minks, too!
It's like a wonderland!
Yes, that's exactly what
Mama's dream is.
Humans, Minks, Fish-men,
Longarms, Longlegs, Dwarfs...
A country where all races in the world
can live together without discrimination.
No, I mean everything in the world!
Everything in the world?
Yes, that's Mama's ideal world, Totto Land!
Realize you're already deep
into a great territory!
This island is Cacao Island, and is
ruled by the Minister of Chocolate.
The name of the town is Chocolat Town!
Chocolat Town?! What a wonderful name!
Everything in this town is made of chocolate.
What?! I love chocolate!
Am I allowed to eat it?!
Grr! In this town,
you can eat chocolate all you like!
Yes!
But be careful!
It's against the law to eat
the roof-tile chocolates.
Because they won't be able
to keep off rain or snow.
Window glass is the Minister
of Candy's jurisdiction
and construction posts are
the Minister of Biscuit's.
And everything else other than chocolate is
private or public property.
Looks delicious...
Hey! Were you listening?!
I couldn't understand at all.
Say, are their panties
also made of chocolate?
Of course, they are.
I can't wait to see chocolate panties!
We're not here to take a break.
Come back as soon as you
finish food shopping. Grr!
I'll stay on the ship, since they know my face,
but I love chocolate.
Get me some!
Okay!
Hey, Straw Hat!
If you're gonna go,
stop wasting your time and put on your disguise...
Luffy and Chopper have
already gone to the town.
What?!
Hey, what do you think will
happen if they find out
I brought you guys here?!
Act cautiously!
Don't worry!
We'll know where they are soon.
Somebody ate a cafe!
There they are!
Screw you!
If it were just the chocolate
walls they could be put back later,
but the whole cafe is gone!
You guys ate candies,
marshmallows, almonds and jelly beans!
That's a crime of Snackalism!
I need to question you!
Come to the station with me!
But, old man,
there is a good reason for this.
Yeah? Out with it!
It was too delicious!
Okay, well said, idiots!
Come with me!
Oh, no! They're gonna get arrested!
Don't make a scene, Pedro-san!
Wait, Chocopolice-san!
Carpet! Carpet!
The carpet is flying...
Oh, you're the... owner!
Oh, more trouble!
The owner of the cafe came!
Look what they've done to your cafe!
I can't believe this!
The Owner of the Caramel Cafe
Nitro the Jelly
Rabiyan the Carpet
How could you leave this much?
This isn't what we agreed to! Gee!
You have to finish it properly!
Hey, do you know her?
No, I don't. Who is it?
And what's that thing on her shoulder?
I thought the combination of jam and biscuits
and chocolate here was delicious!
Here! Try this!
How is it?
It's good!
Chocopolice-san, I'm sorry.
The cafe will be expired soon,
so I asked them to eat the whole building!
Oh, pardon me! I didn't know
they were a demolition crew!
Come on, guys!
You should've had a sign out
when you were working.
There were still some customers too.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Yes, thank you!
And I'm sorry to disturb you, everyone!
So it was nothing serious.
Oh, we were so worried.
Oh, yeah!
Congratulations on getting married,
Pudding-sama!
Your wedding day is approaching
and you're checking in on your cafe?
Don't work too much.
We all wish for your happiness!
Thank you!
She saved Luffy and Chopper.
She's so kind. I wonder who it is.
They're so lucky!
This is how fortune favors
the future Pirate King.
Oh?
Captain Pedro?!
You're Captain Pedro, aren't you?!
I thought so! It's been a while!
Why are you here?
I'm just sightseeing. Don't tell anyone I was here.
O-Okay. It was a pleasure to see you.
You know people in this town, Pedro?
I'll tell you later.
So your name is Pudding.
Thank you for helping us!
No, no! I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
Why?
Because you said...
"It was too delicious"!
That chocolate at the cafe is a
new blend that I came up with!
Did you like how it melted in your mouth?
I added milk to cocoa butter
and highly-pure beet sugar
and kneaded it for three days
straight at 29 degrees Celsius!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but it was so good!
It was!
You said it was delicious,
and it really makes me want to cry!
Thank you! I'm so happy to hear it!
Wh-wh...
What a nice girl!
Do you like making chocolate?
I love sweets!
This town smells like chocolate
and it's like heaven!
Even the table is chocolate!
It's nice to know that!
We really want to stay
and thank you, Pudding,
but we need to go...
Yeah? That's too bad.
Before you go, would you like a cup of tea?
I guess you have a sweet taste in your mouth.
Tea sounds good!
Okay. I'll be right back.
Oh, what a nice girl!
She's really a nice girl!
I haven't asked your name, have I?
I'm Luffy.
The future Pirate King...
Hey!
What?
Luffy?
Whole Cake Island
How long do we have until the tea party?
Three days, Mama!
Flower! Flower!
I see...
What about Germa's son?
He's here, Mama!
Furniture! Furniture! Furniture! Furniture!
There will be a wedding!
How is the cake?
The wedding cake!
– The design?
– Okay!
– The budget?
– Don't be stingy!
Ingredients must be carefully selected
Kill the people and rob them!
Eggs!
I got them.
Flour!
I got it!
Fruit!
I got it.
We'll make it taste good!
Let's eat a delicious cake!
Sweet dealings!
The tea party from hell!
– Is this strawberry jam?
– Or somebody's blood?
I don't care either way!
If you're invited, be there at any cost!
A sweet moment!
Sacrifices to the Devil!
This is a dream land for everyone....
All kinds of races come together...
Totto Land!
Mmm, I can't wait!
I heard he is here.
Yes, he is here.
Straw Hat!
Chocolat Town, Cacao Island
Luffy is...
Oh, no!
Now that I look closer, you look familiar!
Straw Hat Luffy!
That's right! I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
We're totally screwed.
Are you people really
the Straw Hats, the pirates?!
Yes, we are!
Sanji-san's comrades?! You're kidding!
I'm not kidding! Sanji is our buddy!
What? Do you know Sanji?
What?!
Are you daughter of Big Mom
who's gonna get married to Sanji, Pudding?!
Mm-hm.
Sanji's fiancée...
I'm jealous! She'll be such a beautiful wife!
W-Wife?!
Oh! But why?!
You people aren't even Mama's allies!
How did you pass the TARTE security?
Why did you come?!
Y-You're gonna be killed!
You're already in Mama's territory
and she's a very scary pirate!
But I know you people are scary pirates too!
No!
Wait! Calm down!
We won't get rough with you!
Luffy, what should we do with her-gara?
Don't get rough, Pedro!
So you came for Sanji-san...
To take him back.
I knew he didn't consent,
since Mama is so self-centered.
She even uses her children's weddings
to strengthen her pirate crew.
We've given up on marrying someone
freely out of love.
We only have two choices; give up or run.
One of my older sisters that I loved very dearly
went out to the sea looking for love.
To seek a match.
Just out of curiosity,
... We have heard that you're the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family.
Does Big Mom have 35 daughters?
Yes, she has 39 daughters and 46 sons.
We're 85 brothers and sisters.
Oh, my!
Wow! That's so many brothers and sisters!
We have different fathers.
Mama has 43 husbands, so we're a family of 129.
What... 129?!
Some of my older brothers and sisters
already have children,
so if you count them in, there are more.
The Big Mom Pirates consist
mainly of her blood relatives.
She's true to her name – Big Mom!
Have you met Sanji?
Y-Y-Yes... just once.
Although his eyebrows are twirly,
he is very kind and gentlemanly!
Flower! Flower!
Even though he's got heart eyes,
he knows so much about making
sweets and taught me a lot!
Flower! Flower!
We like the same stuff and he's so manly!
I heard his legs are black,
but he's tough and dependable!
He is, isn't he?!
That's not what "Black-Leg" means.
You really got him! He's a great guy!
D-Don't tell me you're in love with...
Are you in love with Sanji-kun?!
L-L-Love?! Well, I mean...
Mama's decision can't be overturned.
And if I marry someone, I prefer, um...
I like Sanji very much too!
We're the same!
No, I can't say such a thing!
SHOCK!!
This is totally unexpected!
I can't believe such a lovely girl is the bride!
No wonder Sanji-san's got heart eyes!
We should tie her up!
She'll tell them that we're here.
If they find us while we're on
one of the outermost islands,
we'll never be able to get to Sanji!
How could you say that, Pedro?
How else can we silence her?
Don't forget that she's Big Mom's daughter.
Yeah, but she's scared of her mother too!
That's why she'll tell her!
How would you know?!
You stay out of this!
Excuse me.
I think I can still let go of my feelings...
... towards Sanji-san!
People in Totto Land...
give their blessings to my marriage.
So do the members of the Vinsmoke Family.
Mama looks forward to the wedding cake.
None of us can disobey Mama's order,
so I knew I couldn't marry for love,
but I've been dreaming
ever since I was a child.
Wondering what my husband would be like.
And then, Sanji-san came along.
I was surprised,
because he was such a wonderful man.
But, he actually said to me in the end,
"I want to marry you, but I can't do it."
"I want to go back to my friends."
What?! Sanji rejected a girl?!
But... it's good to know...
I knew he wanted to continue the adventure!
It wasn't just him who wanted to be back,
because you all actually came here
to take him back at the risk of your lives.
Even if this is Mama's decision,
it'd be hard for me to stay with someone
who didn't want to get married.
And most of all, I know you all
care about Sanji-san very much,
and I can't take him away from you.
He said he wanted to go
back to his friends too.
Then all I can do for him
is help him with that.
Take this route.
This is the only way you can get there
without Mama finding out.
Only we siblings know about it!
Is that where Sanji is?
If you go along this route,
you can get to Whole Cake Island.
But Mama won't let go of Sanji-san.
So let's meet up at the southwest coast of
Whole Cake Island tomorrow.
I'll promise to bring Sanji-san there.
I'll cooperate with you!
Is it okay?
Won't you get punished by Big Mom?
I'm her biological daughter.
Don't worry.
You're in enemy territory.
Worry about yourself.
Pudding...
But is it really okay?
Sanji-san and you all care about each other.
Pudding-san, you're so...
It's a bit of a shame,
but my next husband to-be...
... could be someone even nicer!
H-How wonderful this girl is!
Is she really the Emperor's daughter?!
Thank you, Pudding!
You're welcome!
Pudding-sama, we're here to pick you up.
One moment!
I'm working now, so wait a second.
You need to stop working until the wedding,
Pudding-sama.
But I have customers...
You have to prepare for the wedding too.
Oh, it's you! The groceries
that you ordered are ready.
They're there, so just take them.
Oh, there they are!
Can you carry them?
Thanks. We'll be fine!
Choco-burger?!
Don't look at other stuff!
Let's go! Pekoms is waiting for us!
I want the choco-burger, Nami!
– Choco-pasta.
– Choco-fried chicken.
We have enough food! Come on!
Oh?
Pekoms?
Did you find him?
No!
This is strange.
Doing number two, maybe?
What about the bathroom?
Hey!
There is a message in the bathroom!
"Turn back"?
– Did Pekoms write this?
– Who else would do that?
Did somebody invade?
Has Pekoms been abducted?
Maybe they've found out about us.
In any event, this is serious.
Turn back
"Turn back" means if we don't turn back,
something's gonna happen.
Yeah.
Okay, everyone, keep that in mind!
Let's keep going!
What?
This is getting exciting!
Broc Coli Island, New World
Damn!
– All done?
– Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
How dare you kill my wife?
How dare you kill my children?
How dare you destroy my country?
You're Germa, aren't you?!
You guys are not human!
Wall.
I can't believe it took four hours.
I have to attend my brother's wedding.
I have no interest in your family.
Nor your war for that matter.
It's finished.
How could a war between such
weak countries last two years?
– The commission?
– I got it.
– Thank you!
Our country has been saved.
Did we ask demons for help?
No, we didn't! They're angels!
Drop your weapons!
The war is over! It's over!
Thank you, Germa!
Germa 66! Hurray!
Germa! Germa! Germa! Germa!
The wedding is in three days.
Two days is enough
to get to Whole Cake Island.
What about Sanji?
He's already here.
Oh, great. I can't wait to see him.
Yeah, right!
See you in two days.
Clank.
Editing:
Feeso,
Galaxy 9000
Timing:
Halee,
Sewil (Opening)
Quality Assurance:
Galaxy 9000,
Grug,
Mr. Luffy,
Pepperjack
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Translation:
Crunchyroll
Yibis (Opening)