Straw Hat, Ivankov and Inazuma all have Devil Fruit powers!
Don't forget to bring your prison bullets!
We've arrived at Level Six!
Charge!
What's this stone structure?
N-No way!
Are they still here?! Find them!
You seriously think anyone would open a hole like that and not run? Idiot.
H-Head Jailer Shiryuu!
See that, you worms? When I'm not around, you can't do anything.
You've been doing a pretty damn lousy job here.
This is a horrible incident.
A shame to Impel Down.
Those three guys you're looking for freed Crocodile and Jinbei...
before going up to Level Five through that hole.
Relay this message to Magellan at once: I'll lend him a hand.
Well...
W-What?!
Crocodile and Jinbei?!
Yes! They're not in their cells!
S-So that means, even though I had them sealed up inside Level Six, they've managed to escape?!
There are five of them now, and they're all on Level Five?!
That's how it is!
Do you think I'm responsible for this?
Warden Magellan is handing over Portgas D. Ace right now, so you'll probably have to take full responsibility.
Full Responsibility?!
Right! I shall fight them as well!
Send all troops to Level Four!
Sadi-chan! Saldeath!
Take all your men with you and head for Level Four!
This will be an attempt to become Warden with your lives on the line!
Ah, I got it wrong! This will be a battle with your lives on the line!
Are vyou ready?
Even if vwe DO make it to the entrance on the first floor,
the problem is what comes after vwe've made it outside.
Vwe're surrounded by the impassable Calm Belt.
If vwe're to cross it and reach Navy HQ, vwe have no choice but hijack one of the Navy's warships.
Numbers are absolutely essential!
Vwe have to get more allies.
The truth is, right now only a handful of vyou will make it to the first floor without getting caught!
If vwe are caught, gruesome torture awaits vus.
So listen up, in order to increase vour survival rate just a little bit,
vwe'll have to free as many prisoners as vwe can between Level Five and Level One!
The more trouble the prisoners cause, the more enemy troops will be distracted by them!
Vwe will steal as many keys and free as many prisoners as we can while making our way up there!
Vwe are going to cause a riot here in Impel Down the likes of which has never been seen!
So let's go, Straw-Hat-boy!
Huh?
He's gone ahead already.
He freed himself?!
Vwe'll follow him immediately, Candies!
Wait! Will someone please stop me?!
So fast! So fast! I'm spinning even faster than ever!
The Tension Hormones were too effective!
Yeah. But that's actually pretty convenient, isn't it?
No, it isn't!
It's almost ten in the morning right now!
The execution will take place at three this afternoon!
They're certain to carry out the execution at that exact moment!
If Whitebeard intends to stop them, he should attack several hours before the execution!
Ace-san is already being taken across the sea.
The battle could break out any minute now!
They won't kill him before three o'clock, right?!
Then we still have a chance!
These doors are completely pointless.
I'll dry it up with my right hand.
Explanation of Crocodile's Suna Suna Fruit powers.
Suna: Sand
He is a sand man who can turn into and manipulate sand.
The palm of his right hand can absorb the moisture from anything.
When touched by his hand, people and plants will dehydrate, while earth and stone will crumble to sand.
Here they are!
T-This is Level Four!
The prisoners that escaped from Level Six, the Warlord Jinbei...
Inferno Hell, huh?
The intruder, Monkey D. Luffy...
Hot!
The former Warlord, Crocodile...
They're all here!
Start counterattack!
Fire!
Morons! Use the prison bullets!
Crescent Sand Dune!
Shoot him! Use the prison-bullets!
Gomu Gomu no...
Rain!
Fishman Karate!
What?
Arabesque Tile Fist!
T-There's no way we can win!
He's a rookie with a 300 million beli bounty, and he's got two Warlords with him!
D-Don't falter!
We'll just have to hold them back with our sheer numbers until the reinforcements arrive!
Move it. I'm in a hurry.
Let's go.
Damn them... Shoot!
Beast Hell
Hurry!
What is all that noise?
Camisole...
Long-johns...
All troops, proceed to Level Four.
I think I just heard something from the speakers...
Has something happened in the prison?
Hey, Buggy! Look!
The guards and the Blugori are leaving!
All troops, urgently proceed to Level Four.
Seems like there's some trouble on another floor, partner.
This is a great opportunity for us!
Yes, that's right...
When I think back on it...
We were chased by the Army-Wolves in Level Five...
And just moments ago, we were pressed against the floor trying to deceive those Accursed Beasts...
It might have seemed like comic relief, but we've FINALLY made it back here to Level Two...!
We're a breath closer to that long-awaited outside world...
Ya ready, guys?
Of course we are!
Fake keys that Three-guy made out of wax...
This is totally awesome!
All troops, proceed to Level Four.
Sector A! What's happening?!
Sector B, wait!
Assistant Warden! This is the monitoring room!
What is it?
This is strange...
Oh, no no... This cool hat, you see,
it is a specially-made headdress that I was going to wear to commemorate my promotion to Warden...
I'm not talking about the thing on your head!
I can see someone sneaking around on Level Two!
It looks like a couple of prisoners!
What?!
Oh, the keys! We're getting out of here!
Thanks a lot, you there!
C-Crocodile?!
I'm thinking of escaping this place, but I'll need some soldiers.
How 'bout it?
Wanna join me...
Mister One?
I suppose I'll tag along, if it's with you.
I was starting to get bored.
Thanks a ton.
It's Captain Buggy you should be thanking.
Level Two guards, are you there?!
If you are, then respond!
Yes!
What are you guys doing?
Uh, we're heading to Level Four, like we were ordered...
No! Stay and keep watch on that floor!
This floor?
Things have turned to our favor, partner!
If these guys start rioting again, we can use that chance to smuggle ourselves onto a warship!
Indeed, and then our escape will be complete!
I suppose Straw-Hat and Mister Two are already dead...
Even if they survived, they'll be stuck in prison for the rest of their lives!
Our own lives are the most important thing!
So long, suckers!
That's Buggy the Clown!
Up there! Look above you!
Above us...?
Well then, men!
This is the best chance we'll ever get!
If ya wanna taste the fresh air again, raise hell like your lives depend on it!
That's the kick-off!
Our savior!
That's Captain Buggy!
T-This is Level Two...
The prisoners have escaped from their cages and are running wild again!
Please send the Blugori back here!
We can't restrain them!
This is Level Four!
What is it now?!
The Okama-queen Ivankov, Inazuma,
and the guy you ran into earlier, Mister Two...!
Quit messing around!
They've arrived, followed by a huge crowd of people!
A... A crowd?!
All troops, urgently proceed to Level Four.
And the people they've brought with them are... You won't believe this!
They're prisoners who have vanished over the years,
who we thought had been taken by the Demon's Tug!
What did you say?!
What's going on here?!
Vwe've finally made it!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
You got a tension boost, huh?
I'm unstoppable now!
Why are you here, Mister One?!
Who's this guy?
He's the guy who was beaten by
Waistband-chan back in Alabasta!
Oh? Someone I don't know, then.
Assistant Warden! Hurry and send reinforcements to Level Four!
Level Two, as well!
What do I do...?
Emporio Face-Growth Hormone!
It's too hot!
Hell Wink!
It's no use!
We can't stop them!
All these prisoners, who were really ferocious before they disappeared,
are all wearing some kinda weird, fanatical getups!
They're unstoppable in more ways than one!
Let's go to Navy HQ!
It seems like an unprecedented riot is taking place in Impel Down.
Their leader is Monkey D. Luffy.
Take a good look at the sky. It's the last time you'll see it.
Once you've been secured on to the execution platform,
you'll never...
see the sky again.
This is Onigumo.
Prepare to open the gates to Marineford.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
How did it go?
He's nowhere to be found!
There's just over 5 hours left till Ace's execution.
We have no idea when Whitebeard might show up,
and now, even though we've entered the most critical time,
we can't find the Warlord Blackbeard anywhere on the island, no matter how hard we look!
And one more thing...
A warship that didn't get clearance to leave...
just arrived at Impel Down!
What?!
You don't suppose...
Please, wait here!
We didn't call for any outside reinforcements,
and we're in a state of emergency and cannot take on this responsibility!
We were just checking with HQ...
Who cares about that? We're on the same side, ain't we?
S-Still! Pirates aren't allowed inside the prison, regardless of the circumstances!
No need to hold back.
I'm with the Government!
What a depressing place this is!
Reporting in!
The crew of the ship that Blackbeard arrived on...
has been eliminated!
What?!
Hey!
Sir!
Wait, you lot!
Liberation!
We've got an intruder!
He's one of the Seven Warlords, Marshall D. Teach!
Hey! Hang in there!
These guys are the guards that were just wiped out!
Darkness...!
Blackbeard and his crew have broken in with hostile intent, no doubt about it!
I was... pulled into the darkness...!
We don't know what they're here for!
It's over! My life is over!
No, that's not true.
This is the beginning.
This is the beginning of my dark, depressing life where I'm unable to become Warden.
Assistant Warden!
Pull yourself together!
Straw Hat Luffy is on Level Four,
Buggy the Clown is on Level Two,
and the Warlord, Blackbeard, is at the main entrance!
What can I do about this?!
How about going back to the monitoring room and eating some crackers?
Pull yourself together! We must protect Impel Down!
Sure, you're not the one taking responsibility here, so of course you can say that...
Don't tell me you're trying to take my job as Assistant Warden?!
Hannyabal!
Can you hear me?
W-Warden Magellan, is that you?
Where... Where are you now?
I'm in Level Two.
I've taken care of the imbeciles who were causing an uproar here.
What?
Help...!
I've sealed all the exits to this floor.
They'll be completely immobilized before long.
We're trapped here!
Captain Buggy! There's a clog of poison blocking the way!
Damn you, Magellan! You sneaky bastard!
We'll be in big trouble at this rate!
I have no idea why Blackbeard has invaded this place,
but I have a plan to deal with him.
It's a risky move, but as things stand now, we have no choice.
A risky move, is it?
I hoped it wouldn't come to this, but I've decided that we must release Shiryuu!
Seriously ?!
In any case, we can't rely on
reinforcements from Navy HQ.
We must pull through on our own, one way or another.
Send all available troops to deal with the situation on Level Four.
I will be on Level Four shortly.
Hold tight until I get there!
Warden!
Yay! Warden!
Let's just hurry up and get moving.
Impel Down Head Jailer
Shiryuu of the Rain
Shiryuu. Does it feel good being out of that cell?
Yeah, I've learned my lesson.
I was about to die from eternal boredom...
You're not just gonna use me then lock me up again, are you Magellan?
You've been sentenced to death.
This is an opportunity to postpone your sentence.
There is no second chance.
Yeah, I see.
I'll keep that in mind.
Your sword, Head Jailer Shiryuu.
I'll leave Blackbeard to you.
Very well.
My sword, eh?
Long time, no see...
So sorry...
For cutting you guys down.
All the guards have been defeated!
They've stolen the keys!
Now, keep building vour numbers, and let vus throw the prison into chaos!
This way, the enemy can't hold vus back, and vwe'll increase vour chance of survival!
If you wanna escape, get out of those cells!
This is your chance to escape!
Let's go together!
You're letting us out of here?
Go, Blugori!
Go wild!
Damn, it's the Blugori!
Head Guard Saldeath, we're counting on you!
Blugori! Get that Okama with the humongous face!
It's not a huge face! It's vmy Face-Growth Hormones!
Get him, Blugori!
Hell...
Wink!
He took out the Blugori army with one hit!
I-Impossible!
I don't get it! What is that?!
Straw-Hat-boy!
Vyou don't have time to be standing around!
Leave vyour back to vus, and just keep running forward and climbing upward!
Get going!
Right, gotcha.
Thanks!
It's the Demon Guards!
There's three of them!
Alright, it's reinforcements!
Sadi-chan and her team are here!
These kids won't...
let you take a single step past this spot!
Luffy-kun, let us go! I will help you!
Though I am not so good at fighting on land...
Really? You're pretty tough...
Get them, Demon Guards!
Take this!
Without its eyesight, even a Demon Guard
is useless as a tree stump.
Get them!
We'll crush them!
Everyone attack at once!
Pathetic weaklings...
No use! They're too strong!
Neither guns nor cannons affect them!
Help!
It's hopeless! Don't fight 'em! Pull back!
We're all gonna die!
These guys are worse than the Blugori! Run!
Oh, I just love the sound of your screams!
Those Demon Guards are quite frightening, indeed!
Help us!
Gear Third!
Fishman Karate!
Get them, Demon Guards!
Gomu Gomu no...
Gigant...
Five Thousand Tiles...
Sables!
Fist!
Pistol!
Raise the drawbridge!
Don't let them through!
Hurry!
Underwater Prison Impel Down
Crimson Hell
There's only five of 'em! Stop Blackbeard's crew!
Fire! Fire!
He might be a member of the Warlords, but he's intentionally betraying us!
Blackbeard is no longer our ally!
So what if he betrayed us? He was a pirate to begin with.
H-Head Jailer Shiryuu!
When did you get out of the cell?
Five enemies, eh?
Who's that?
This guy looks dangerous...
Is that Magellan?
You're Marshall D. Teach... "Blackbeard", are you not?
Yeah, that's right! And who're you?
It's no use!
They beat the Demon Guards! We can't stop them!
Charge forward!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
Damn! Their numbers keep growing!
Damn-!
That's the leader of the Demon Guards, Sadi!
Who cares?! Get her!
Silence! You will refer to me as Sadi-chan!
Violence of Arousal...
Red Demon Whip!
How dare you...
do such a thing to my adorable...
minions?!
Damn her!
Wait.
Didn't Vi tell vyou to keep moving forward?!
Emporio Female Hormone!
Make way, eccentric girl!
Silence! You're a female Ivankov, huh?
You ambiguous anarchist!
Right now...
Vi feel like a woman.
Hurry! The staircase to Level Three is close!
I will open the door!
Right, let's go!
What? The door is opening itself!
Who cares? We're in luck!
Now let's go to Level Three!
This is the fortress of Hell!
You shall not pass!
Who is this guy... Barging in here like he's so big?
Hannyabal! He's the Assistant Warden of this prison!
Fire!
Behold!
I've got a thousand men guarding the stairs to Level Three,
all wielding bazookas loaded with special prison ammunition!
There's no escape for you!
To defend the bright future of the defenseless civilians...
Straw Hat, infamous, world-renowned pirate...
I will carry out your sentence on the Warden's behalf!
His attitude is different from what we're used to...
Move it!
No way!
He's serious!
Then we can count on him! He's really strong!
Hannya! Hannya!
W-What?
You know it!
The Hannya Carnival!
Inferno Hell Carriage!
If you're not gonna move, then I'll send you flying!
I will save Ace!
Don't make me laugh!
If you could send me flying so easily, I wouldn't be worthy of being Assistant Warden!
Gear Second!
Gomu Gomu no...
Jet...
Gatling!
We've been waiting for you...
Warden Magellan! Please hurry!
Where are the ones leading the riot?
They're right in front of the stairs to Level Three.
The stairs leading from floor to floor are pretty far apart. Let's hurry!
We're just barely managing to hold them back with the help of Assistant Warden Hannyabal!
Assistant Warden!
Let go of me!
I will not...
LET YOU PASS !
Follow the Assistant Warden's lead! Keep fighting!
FINE BY US!
That was nothing! I can still fight!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
I-I will not let you pass!
Gomu Gomu no...
Jet Stamp!
Wait!
Don't get in my way!
Damn! I have to hurry, or Ace will...!
What do you mean, you're gonna save your brother?!
Don't try to glorify the trash of society!
You pirates and rebels gained your reputations outside by committing crimes!
Assistant Warden Hannyabal!
Just stay down! You'll die!
Civilians can't sleep at night...
fearing that their loved ones will lose their lives, and it's all because you scum dare to sail the seas!
And that is why we imprison the most dangerous criminals around the world...
To make sure that the defenseless civilians can rest easy!
This is the fortress of Hell!
If it were to fall, the whole world would descend into the depths of fear!
I said I wouldn't let you pass, so
you're not taking a single step past me!
Assistant Warden...!
Ace is important to me! So move it!
I can't reason with such a fool...
A-Assistant Warden! Help us!
H-Hey! What happened to you?!
Just give it up!
Don't go around spouting that crap about "Justice" or "Evil"!
You can look all over the world,
but you'll never find an answer!
Ridiculous!
He's that guy I met in Jaya!
Well, this sure is quite an impressive group.
We've walked in on a pretty major incident, huh?
Teach! What are you doing here?!
Or I suppose I should call you Blackbeard now?
Jinbei...
Hey, hey, no need to be so violent. Mind loosening that fist of yours?
Oh yeah, I heard you and Ace were good friends, huh?
But I'm not the one you should be blaming here.
Blackbeard?!
I'm chasing after a certain man.
He calls himself Blackbeard.
People's dreams...
will never end!!
I heard that a pirate called Blackbeard...
managed to join the Warlords by capturing Fire Fist Ace.
Blackbeard...
So you're...
Blackbeard?!
Huh? Oh, yeah, I never introduced myself, did I?
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I sure was surprised when I heard that you were Commander Ace's little brother!
Shouldn't you be there?
They're gonna start soon, ya know?
Your brother's execution, that is!