From what I heard, you're the one who took down that former Shichibukai Crocodile over there, huh?
Straw Hat Luffy!
Back then, when I was still trying to become a Shichibukai,
I thought the best idea was to kill you and use that to prove my strength to the World Government.
Whitebeard's reign is over!
I'll become the next Pirate King!
For starters, I'm gonna kill
Straw Hat Luffy, who is in Water Seven,
as a gift to the Government!
Another reason I can't let you go free!
He's my brother!
But it seems fate was in your favor!
Ace, who had been chasing me ever since I broke the laws of Whitebeard's ship,
just happened to be your brother!
Once he realized that we were planning to kill his little brother,
he just had to fight us himself!
You understand?
If he'd let us go, not only would he have disgraced Whitebeard,
but his brother would have been killed, too!
There is no such thing as coincidence in one's fate.
Meaning...
You got real lucky!
Now that the captain has become a Shichibukai, he has no need to take your life.
Your brother put up an admirable fight!
You should be thankful for Ace's interference.
If he hadn't interfered, the one dying today,
would be you, Straw Hat.
In that case...
WHY DON'T YOU TRY KILLING ME NOW?!
Captain!
I'm not letting Ace die!
Gomu Gomu no Jet...
Black Vortex!
Straw-chan!
Blood? Isn't he a rubber man?
Devil Fruit powers are useless against me!
And so what?!
Wait, Luffy-kun! Stop!
Let me go!
This is not the time! Just endure it!
Let go of me!
You can't, Luffy-kun!
What's more important here?!
Think! Luffy-kun!
Ever since he was on old Whitebeard's ship, no one's ever known his true nature.
I don't know what tricks he used, but he certainly possesses the power to defeat even Ace-san!
We can't afford to waste time and energy here!
If you get carried away and fight him now,
we won't have time to save Ace-san afterward!
You're even stronger than I had imagined.
Your haki has increased, too.
You said you're Blackbeard, right?
I'd heard that some no-name pirate from Whitebeard's crew had taken my place in the Shichibukai.
But isn't this odd?
Why would you, who's been called to Navy HQ, be down here right now?
You're pretty much throwing away the
Shichibukai rank that you wanted so badly.
It's all part of my plan.
It's not like I'm obligated to tell you anything...
...Mister Crocodile.
That's true, and to be honest, I don't really care.
Pretty touchy, aren't you?
H-Hey wait! What's going on?!
Magellan is here!
This is not good!
Straw-Hat-boy!
Hurry up and go!
If vyou're hit by any more of Magellan's poison, Vi won't be able to bring vyou back again!
It's Prison Warden Magellan!
Oh, crap... Hurry up and run!
Warden... Magellan!
Thank God... The Warden is here!
Magellan... So he finally shows himself?
Climb the stairs! The bazooka squad's gone!
The path is clear!
Straw Hat! Hurry and climb up to Level Three!
You took out the guards blocking the stairs... That makes things easier for us.
Well, you guys helped us too.
All this panic is real convenient for us.
Alright! It's the stairwell to Level Three!
Let's get moving!
It's another Demon Guard!
It's the Minotaurus!
What?! The Minotaurus?!
Didn't we beat that thing back in Level Three?!
Of course it recovered.
They're awakened Zoan-type Fruit users.
They're much tougher and recover much faster than normal people.
Those things are Devil Fruit users as well?!
If we stay here for too long, the other three will get up again too.
But this is not the time to be scared of those things.
The boss of Hell is just around the corner.
Warden Magellan!
We've received word that Blackbeard is on this floor, at the stairwell to Level Three!
Shiryuu should have already dealt with Blackbeard!
Was he defeated?
This is the monitoring room!
What's happening?!
I-It's terrible!
The main Surveillance Snail was taken out!
The monitoring system for the entire prison has been destroyed!
What's more, all connections to Navy HQ and the Government have been severed!
We've completely lost contact with-
What's this?!
Hey! What's wrong?! What happened?!
Who did this?!
Don't go tattling on me...
Or Magellan will know I'm here.
We've lost contact!
Send someone to confirm the situation!
Yes, Sir!
This is not good.
If Blackbeard is on this floor,
it means he has unsealed the door that I sealed on Level Two!
Everything seems to be going wrong here!
This entire mess has broken out because we allowed one little mouse to break in!
Buggy!
Mister Three!
Yeah! We got flashily lucky!
Men! We're finally on Level One!
Everyone! We're about to reach the outside, where the sun shines!
Our great savior, Captain Buggy!
I'm definitely going to save Ace!
Sure, I won't say it's useless.
After all, there's no such thing as "impossible" in this world.
Sky Island did exist, didn't it?
The era where pirates dream is over?!
Huh?!
People's dreams...
NEVER END!
Ain't that right?!
One Piece is the same.
It definitely exists!
Look forward to it, you guys!
In just a few hours,
we will give you all a show that'll shake the world to its core!
Don't bother with him, Luffy-kun!
Advance!
To Level Three!
Warden!
Help me, Warden!
Sadi-chan! What happened to you?!
Okamakov...
Beat me!
I'm so ashamed!
There's no reason for me to live if I can't torture people!
Let her down.
I'll go on ahead.
Uh, yes! Right away!
So you're Magellan?
And I take it you are Blackbeard?
I am indeed.
Hydra!
I don't have time to ask why you're here.
It hurts! What is this?!
Poison? Damn that bastard...!
Hannyabal.
You did well to hold them back for so long.
Leave the rest to me.
Assistant Warden!
What a disgraceful appearance!
Take care of him for me.
Yes, Sir!
Assistant Warden! Hang in there! Assistant Warden!
Don't die.
I won't accept anyone but you as my successor.
Straw Hat...
How did you survive my poison?
I'm sure he's the one in charge of this whole incident.
I will absolutely finish him off this time!
STRAW HAT!!!
Who's that?! Is that Magellan's voice?!
He's at the bottom of the stairs!
If he catches up to us, we're finished!
The poison guy!
I will never let you get away!
Straw-chan! Don't look back, just keep running!
I won't let you get away.
Get moving!
Hurry! Magellan is close!
Hurry to Level Two!
That was the last group.
Of all those behind them, not a single man was left standing!
Inazuma.
Understood.
Great Scissors!
Inazuma-san!
Why'd you slice up the stairs?!
Iva-sama is still down there!
Never mind that, just hurry and get off this floor!
Please... Survive!
What...
Is the meaning of this?!
"What is the meaning?" vyou ask?
If vyou don't understand what the meaning of that move was...
Then vyou're...
A TOTAL IDIOT, AREN'T VYOU?!
Death Wink!
I won't let Straw Hat and the others escape while you're stalling for time!
Stalling for time?
Vyou don't actually think you can beat me, do vyou?
Vi will show you the true power of the
Newkama Kenpo of the Kamabakka high temple!
Alright, get out here! The outside world awaits you!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Alright!
We're free!
Now make sure you work hard, alright?
Here.
Thanks.
Take this.
Advance! Keep moving!
Once trapped on Level Two by Magellan's poison but fortunately managing to escape,
Captain Buggy and his merry prisoners are now heading to the front entrance.
They are currently on Level One.
Having made it through Level Four,
Inferno Hell and Level Three, Famine Hell,
Straw Hat Luffy, the Newkama troops he commands, and the released prisoners...
are now running through Level Two, the Accursed Beasts Floor.
And the ruler of Hell, Warden Magellan, who is trying to catch them,
is currently fighting Okama Queen Ivankov, on Level Three.
He broke...
My spine...
D-Damn you, Ivankov!
I won't forgive you!
Get going!
How long...
Are you gonna sleep for?!
And the four Demon Guards, having just recovered from their earlier beating,
are in the lift, heading for Level One.
The traitorous Head Jailer, Shiryuu, has blocked all communication with the outside world.
No one has received word on the current state of the prison.
As this unprecedented incident continues to escalate beneath the sea...
Warships and prison ships are stationed all around the prison!
If we can hijack one of them, we should be able to reach Marineford before Ace-san is executed!
Right!
Wait for me, Ace!
Four and a half hours remain before Ace's rapidly approaching execution.
Long-johns!
Chemise!
That's weird...
The poison guy was right behind us a second ago...
Iva-san and Inazuma stopped him at the bottom of the stairwell!
Then they're fighting against the poison guy right now?
Let's go back!
Stop kidding around!
If they are fighting, then that makes it all the more important for us to move forward!
Let's believe in the power of the Miracle Worker!
Spin, spin!
What's wrong with this floor?
It's completely deserted.
Strange...
There's no sign of prisoners in any of the cells.
And all the cells are already open, too!
Who let them out?
Vmy face...
VMY FACE IS MELTING!
Vmy face... Vmy face...!
It's... It's... It's...
NOT MELTING!
Vi was just wearing lots of makeup!
What a frivolous waste of time!
Is that so?
Vi found it funny, though.
Then how about vwe end this?
This battle between vyou and vme?!
Newkama Kenpo...
Aesthetic Art 44 Hidden Technique...
Dream Smash Removal Fist!
Iva-san!
Iva-san...!
It didn't work?!
Keep Out!
Another attempt to stall for time?
They're here!
We finally made it here, and now all four Demon Guards are here too!
Run!
This is as far as we go! Let's turn back! We can't win!
Let's just give up on escaping!
WHAAAAAT?!
Are you alright?
Hey! Watch it, you crock o-
-DILE?! {Yeah, I couldn't really think of any way to make this sound good.kae: I went with 'crock of shit' getting truncated. it might be over-localized, but buggy is weird.}
B-B-B-B-Boss?!
So it's you, Mister Three.
What's a worthless piece of trash like you doing here?
That's quite a big shot they've released...
C-Captain Buggy!
They've knocked out the Demon Guards!
S-Straw Hat?!
I-Is that the Shichibukai, Jinbei?!
What a relief! So you guys are alright?
(What a relief! So you guys are alright?)
My heart!
It hurts!
Captain Buggy!
Prisoners and perverts just keep coming up from Level Two!
Perverts too?!
What the hell?!
Who're you calling perverts?!
You two... How dare you abandon us back there?
So you're here too, Mister Two?!
What are you doing to Captain Buggy?!
This is bad!
The prisoners from Level Four have finally made it up here!
Did they manage to escape from Warden Magellan?
How can this be?
The two insurgent groups have joined forces!
Where is the Warden?!
Hydra!
MAGELLAN TOO?!
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE ON THIS FLOOR?!
Huh?! Does that mean that Iva-chan and Crab-chan were...
Dammit!
You can't, Straw-chan!
We've got no choice but to run from Magellan!
Let go of me, Bon-chan!
I'm gonna kick his ass!
Are you sure?
I understand, but do you really want us to?
Yes. Follow my orders, and do it quickly!
Yes, Sir!
Oh no, so that's their plan?!
You almost died because of him, remember?!
But I'm still alive, aren't I?
Miracles are called that because they won't happen twice, you know!
You two, hurry to the next floor!
Luffy-kun!
We must hurry to the main entrance!
The situation has gotten worse...
We've been too focused on Magellan!
Hydra!
Everyone, get out of the way!
Candle Wall!
Three!
He stopped Magellan's Hydra!
That optimism of yours makes me want to puke!
The second I let my guard down, I start thinking of you as a friend!
Sheesh...
I hate being indebted to others!
I've underestimated you, Brother Three!
I see. Wax, huh?
That's right.
I ate the Doru Doru fruit. I'm a candle-man.
Your poison will never be able to pass through my hard-as-steel wax wall!
You never know how suitable some powers can be.
Now, hurry up and go!
I give up quickly, you know!
Three!
How irritating.
This is no time to be hesitating! I can't hold him back for long!
Right. Then we'll just get going.
Let's go, men!
Were you always this good?!
Yeah, as long as I'm not on a hot floor...
Now all of you, hurry and get out!
I want to escape too, you know!
Luffy-kun. We must hurry as well!
Oh, yeah, you said we're gonna steal a warship, right?
I did.
Then you and the others should just go on ahead.
I'll try stopping the poison guy in the meantime.
I mean, it'll be hard to steal one while he's chasing us.
Yes, that's true...
I've got an idea.
Does it stand a chance?
Yeah, leave it to me!
I understand. Just don't do anything too reckless!
Right, Three! Let's fight together!
No, that's wrong! I have absolutely no intention of fighting!
My only intent was to guard us the best I could and run away!
Brother Three! We'll stay behind and help, too!
I'm telling you, I'm not that motivated!
THIS IS JUST TOO COOL!
It's perfect!
Pay attention to what's in front of you!
What are you talking about, at a time like this?!
The tears just won't stop...!
Thanks for making me look so awesome...!
Like I care! Hurry up and fight him!
H-Here he comes!
Hydra!
Three!
Leave it to me!
Candle Wall!
No matter how many times you try, it won't work!
Gomu Gomu no...
Champion Rifle!
Alright! I can touch him now!
We've got the cannons ready over here!
The candle wall is shielding us!
Awesome! We hit him!
We can do this!
Alright!
We're almost there! Push for the surface!
Just a little further!
We can finally get out!
Since we've made it this far, there's nobody left who can call themselves our enemies!
Don't let your guard down, amateur.
What?!
Outside these walls, there are at least ten warships.
There are about eight hundred marines on each ship.
I don't know what kind of plan they've got to intercept us,
but stealing one of the ships means we'll be making the other ships our enemies.
This is no time to take it easy.
I-I see...
That's not the only problem here.
There's no guards left!
Now we just have to get through this door!
Right! Prepare your weapons, all of you!
Let's open the door!
Let's do this! Ready, push!
Finally, we'll see the light of the outside world!
Idiot! We're not out of this just yet!
The navy troops are waiting right outside this door...
If we win, we'll reach Heaven! If we lose, we'll go to Hell!
It's light!
We're getting out of here!
All of you, put some spirit into it!
I don't know how many troops are waiting for us, but we will beat 'em and return to sea!
Now, let's go, men!
Follow my lead!
What... is going on here?!
There aren't any warships around!
There's not a single warship for us to steal!
There isn't a single marine here, either!
No way... That means...
There's no way out, is there?!
What are we gonna do?
Is there nothing to do...
but wait helplessly for Magellan to arrive?
Damn it! You gotta be kidding me!
I see. So the enemy wasn't as stupid as I thought.
The great Sea Kings are lurking on the ocean floor.
This Calm Belt here is truly
Impel Down's greatest defense.
We finally made it all the way here, from the depths of Hell!
Damn! At this rate, we'll only fall right back into Hell!
We have no time to stand around crying!
Magellan ordered them to set sail just a few minutes ago.
Take a good look!
You can still barely see their shadows through the mist!
Y-You're right!
But how is being able to see them in the distance gonna help us?!
Don't worry!
I'm here! You can leave this to me!
Seriously?!
He's freakishly strong!
All those who have the resolve to fight, get on!
Right, let's move out!
Very well! Let us hurry!
He's surging forward while carrying that heavy door!
Just what I'd expect from the captain of the Fishman Pirates!
I'm really getting excited here!
I never thought I'd see a Shichibukai in action!
Not only that, but our savior, Captain Buggy, is with them!
There's still hope for us!
You dumbasses!
It's obviously much safer with these Shichibukai than staying there and dreading Magellan!
Fools!
They're shooting at us!
So they spotted us.
He dodged it! He's fast!
Don't think he's just any fishman! He's the Sea Knight, Jinbei!
All ships, fire!
If we just sink Jinbei, they're all done for!
Warships coming in hard and fast!
I'll launch you onto the deck of one of the ships! Hold on tight!
What?! What did you say?!
You damn fish!
You listening, bastard?!
WHAT IS GOING ON?!
I see! He abandoned us and ran off on his own!
TRAITOR! TRAITOR! TRAITOR! TRAITOR!
Why did you even come along?
They'll hit us if this keeps up!
Just calm down, you.
Fishman Jujutsu...
Water Heart...
IT'S COMING THIS WAY!
Sea Current Lifter!
WE'RE FLYING!
What's that water pillar?
It's almost like a living creature!
What could that be?!
I don't know.
But someone's riding it... It's Crocodile!
Here they are!
They've come to steal the ship!
Don't let them take it!
If we can push the Devil Fruit users into the ocean, we win!
Huh?