HE ABSORBED ALL THAT ENERGY?!
You're unbelievable!
You ain't human!
There's no way you could've survived Magellan's poisons!
He beat the poisoning in only 20 hours!
It's an unbelievable miracle!
A miracle...
This is more than a miracle!
Hooray!
Thank God...
Bon-chan!
You're alright after all.
Stupid! Quit joking around!
I'm the one who ought to be saying...
Bon-chan! Hey!
You okay? Hang in there!
What's wrong? Hey!
He's just overexerted himself.
His injuries have nothing to do with it.
Oh, Iva-chan...
Iva-chan!
We survived! Thanks a lot for everything you've done for us.
It's this Mister Two Bon-boy vyou should be thanking.
Vi just used vmy abilities and lent vyou some strength.
But he...
He kept on shouting for hours on end...
Until his throat was dry and he was coughing up blood...
He stayed here all along, sharing vyour pain...
Constantly shouting for vyou to hang in there and live on!
Vi'm pretty sure he made at least some difference in vyour struggle to survive.
I see...
What's with that guy?
He's naked...
Straw-chan... I'm here to save you...!
In the name of our friendship...!
Bon-chan, thanks a lot.
I'm in your debt!
Here's your hat and some clothes.
You've survived, but that's all.
You won't make a full recovery
until you've rested a few days.
I don't have time for that!
I've wasted too much time already!
Sorry, but can you guys take care of Bon-chan?
I'll come back for him later.
Hey, hey!
See? You're completely worn out.
The paper is still pointing down.
Ace is down there...
Come to think of it, where are we?
What's that?
Isn't that a Vivre Card?
This is the space between Levels Five and Six.
Now that vyou've recovered,
Vi suppose vyou don't care about anything other than saving vyour brother, right?
Well, it's none of vmy business what vyou do with vyour life...
Iva-chan, aren't you gonna escape?
I mean, Bon-chan came down here hoping to save your ass, y'know?
His ass?!
Mind telling me where Ace is while you're escaping?
What are vyou saying?
Bon-boy came here to save vme?
So that's how it is, huh?
Well isn't that cute...
It's the thought that counts, Vi guess...
But it's not the time for vme to break out just yet!
Vi understand the balance of power in the world.
The Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates are both trying to shift the world in their favor...
But "that man" has yet to make his move.
The man who oversees all the revolutionaries in the world...
Vmy companion...
The revolutionary, Dragon!
Oh, you mean my dad?
That's right.
As soon as vyour dad rallies his troops and makes his move...
Vi shall once again return to the surface and throw vmyself into the flow of the world.
Even if Vi were to try and escape right now,
Vi would merely end up being hunted down.
DID HE SAY "DAD"?!
Dragon is...
vyour dad?!
V-V-Vyou've got to be kidding vme!
Vyou're Dragon's son?!
He has a son?!
Ah...
I wasn't supposed to tell anyone...
Well, whatever. Gramps told me...
Your father's name is...
Monkey D. Dragon.
He's a revolutionary.{Garp is clearly only capable of discussing matters of lineage with his finger up his nose.}
I don't really know him myself...
To be honest, I don't even know what he looks like.
If he doesn't know, that just makes it all the more convincing!
He doesn't look like a liar, and he's made a huge impact on the pirate world!
And he just demonstrated a will to live that defies common sense!
He's not normal!
What he said makes perfect sense!
Where are vyou from?
East Blue.
Dragon...
When vyou're standing out here in the wind,
vyou always face the same direction, vyou know.
Really?
You notice the strangest things, don't you?
I've never really thought about it.
Then maybe it's an animal-like homing instinct?
Isn't vyour hometown somewhere off in that direction?
Do vyou have some family vyou long for back in the eastern seas?
Well?
Stop enquiring about my personal history, Iva.
Pardon vme.
If that's true...
If Straw-Hat-boy here really IS Dragon's son...
Inazuma! Go find out when Ace-boy is being taken to his execution.
Right away.
It'll be a race against time.
If the Vivre Card is pointing down,
then he hasn't been taken away yet.
Vi will be heading to Level Six alongside Straw-Hat-boy here.
You're gonna show me the way?
But... Level Six?
I thought it was Level Five...
Like he said, this is Level 5.5.
Well, whatever. I'm counting on you. Let's go!
Vi was careless!
Vi never even considered this!
That would mean Straw-Hat-boy's brother, Ace, is also Dragon's son!
Could the Navy be doing this intentionally?
No, Vi can see no advantage for the Government in angering both Whitebeard and Dragon!
What is the Government thinking?!
In any case, now is the time to break out of here!
Well then, Bon-chan. I'll come pick you up later, okay?
Straw-Hat-boy!
In the future, vyou must not let slip such information about vyour origins!
Yeah, you're probably right...
Vi am vyour father's companion.
One of the leaders of the revolutionary army.
That's the reason Vi was locked away here.
Vi might be acting of vmy own accord, but Vi have a duty to support vyou!
Vi will not let a friend's son die while Vi'm around to see it!
Give the message to all inhabitants of Newkama Land!
Vwe will hereby attempt to save Ace-boy and break out of Impel Down!
What?! All of a sudden?!
You might say that, but...
Important decisions are always made suddenly!
Those who want to come along, prepare vyourselves for the worst and gather here, ready to fight!
Right! Wait for me, Ace!
I'll be right there!
His pulse...
is still there!
It is?!
Emporio Tension Hormone!
It's adrenaline.
Vyou'll be able to ignore vyour fatigue for one day.
Vyou'll suffer some major aftereffects in exchange for it, but Vi assume vyou don't mind?
Mister Two, Mister Three and Buggy the Clown...
You're sure these three entered Level Five, right?
Yes. Their disguise was flawless.
Still, the only thing we found on Level Five was a blood-stained headdress.
We assume that, after Straw Hat was let out of his cage, the four of them were eaten by wolves.
I see.
I didn't think I'd have to wear this specially-made headdress before I became Warden...
I haven't even gotten rid of Magellan yet!
You're giving away your motives!
If they manage to break out again, you and the Warden might both lose your jobs.
They'll take MY job too?!
Inside the elevator to level 6
You're late.
You're so harsh, Domino.
Please finish up sooner next time.
Don't be so unreasonable...
We are to hand over the prisoner at the main entrance at exactly nine o'clock this morning.
That is our mission.
If we cannot complete it, it will tarnish the reputation of Impel Down.
Impel Down Main Entrance
You got it?
From the moment we take
Portgas D. Ace into custody...
Until the moment we've reached Marineford and handed the prisoner over...
You are not permitted to drop your guard, even for a second!
Yes, Sir!
Prepare for the worst.
It's the duty of our five Navy Vice-Admirals and warships to escort the prisoner without any breach of security!
I will not accept any mistakes!
Yes, Sir!
Oh wow, I'm overflowing with energy!
Let us hurry.
Even the slightest delay could change the outcome of our actions.
No one is watching us here, so as long as vwe don't waste time sneaking around, vwe'll get there very fast!
Keep moving as fast as vyou can!
What's that?
Who're those guys running by?
He's...
Is that the same Ivankov who's supposed to be dead?!
No way!
MOVE IT!
DON'T GET IN OUR WAY!
Death Wink!
Inazuma! The keys!
Yes!
There are surveillance cameras past this point.
If they're gonna come for us, then let 'em come!
Suspicious figures spotted!
Someone is running down the hallway between Levels Five and Six!
That man...!
He's the Okama Queen who vanished a few years back, Ivankov!
What's going on?!
Where has he been all these years?!
The guy next to him is the one who broke in yesterday, Straw Hat Luffy!
I thought the Warden's poison killed him!
And there's another prisoner we thought had vanished!
The revolutionary from South Blue, Inazuma!
What's going on?!
They're heading straight for Level Six!
They're after Fire Fist Ace after all?!
Domino-san and Warden Magellan are going to Level Six right now!
At this rate, they'll run right into each other!
They're still alive?
Assistant Warden!
Activate the traps in the corridor!
Have the guards on Level Six prepare for battle!
Make sure they'll hold out until Sadi-chan and the Demon Guards get there!
Also, contact Warden Magellan and alert all Floors!
Don't just stand there! Hurry up!
Yes, Sir!
The Assistant Warden is taking this seriously all of a sudden?!
Could he be an impostor?!
We must capture them at all costs!
They're not cutting my head off!
Make it! Make it!
I'm coming now, Ace!
Well, then.
Portgas D. Ace...
You will now be taken to the city where your execution is to take place, Marineford!
Ace!!
Hurry up!
Out of the way!
Gomu Gomu no...
Ricochet!
The traps had no effect.
All guards were eliminated.
Straw-Hat Luffy...
Okama Queen Ivankov...
Revolutionary Inazuma...
These three criminals are now entering Level Six!
Where are you, Ace?!
I'm here to save you!!
Ace!!
Is this it?!
Ace!
He's not here!
Are vyou sure this is the right cage?
There's no doubt about it!
I wouldn't...
do such a thing as lie...!
It seems we were one step behind.
A straw hat... This man...
It has to be!
She said...
That my brother's coming here.
He's really here!
To break into the impenetrable Impel Down...
and come all the way down to Level Six, he is really...
Hey, are you Straw-Hat Luffy?
Yeah.
They've just taken him. Chase after them!
Ace-san was being escorted to the lift!
GO! You can still make it if you hurry!
Old dude... Who're you?
He is another of the big shots!
Right, I got it!
Thanks! Whoever you are!
I can't believe it...
One or two lives shouldn't be enough to get a man down here! {Just risking one or two of your lives can't possibly be enough to get you down here... //Actually, I'm not entirely sure about this myself, but I believe this is closer.}
Did he really pass through all Five Hells?!
They must have used this to reach the upper floors.
Let's go!
They've left the gate open for the lift!
Alright!
The mechanisms are locked; it's useless!
We can't use it?!
But if we climb this we can probably make it up-
Do it!
Yes, sir!
T-That was close!
It's to be expected.
It's not like they'd just let us climb up.
The lift is useless!
They're watching vour every move.
Let's use the stairs vwe came down!
Hey... They blocked the stairs.
They're trying to close us in.
If vwe can't break this, there's no way out!
It's a massive gas cloud!
Don't tell me it's poisonous?!
Hey, you guys.
I dunno who you are, but don't make us suffer because of your stupidity.
Silence, you "Level Sixers"!
I don't care if it's poison or whatever!
Wait!
It must be sleeping gas!
There's a limit to recklessness, Straw-Hat-boy!
Stop screwing around, seriously...
Don't come this way!
They're going to put everyone on this floor to sleep...
and then finish us off.
Assistant Warden
Level Six is now sealed!
The sleeping gas is powerful.
There's no escape.
Just to be safe, keep all armed guards on standby.
Did you report to Warden Magellan yet?
Just now, sir!
Good.
And with this, it seems I've managed to secure my job!
Now all I have to do is push the responsibility for this mess onto Magellan, and...
I can finally become Warden!
But the microphone's still on...
What did you say?!
How unfortunate for you.
I've been informed Straw-Hat arrived on Level Six not long after we left.
L-Luffy!
There are no other ways out!
The emergency sleeping gas was released a few moments ago.
Straw Hat's capture is only a matter of time now.
It seems the Freezing Hell wasn't enough for him.
Fortunately, your cell is now available,
and we can inflict our ultimate torture on him down in Level Six.
Luffy...
Don't stop!
Keep walking!
You!
Stop this futile resistance!
Luffy!!
Your brother is also a pirate by nature.
There's no path to salvation for him.
I wanted it to be a lie!
Why did you come, Luffy?!
At any rate, no matter how great a Will,
that amount of poison will always be fatal.
How did you survive it...
Straw Hat?!
Hey, do something!
The floor will be filled with gas!
Save me...!
What's with that guy?!
He's cutting the floor as if it was a piece of cloth!
What? Now he's folding it like paper.
He used the folded floor to seal off the gas...
That guy's good...
Inazuma ate the Choki Choki Fruit and has become a scissor-man.
Choki: Sound of snipping
He can manipulate anything he cuts as if it were paper.
What, he can?
Don't sleep!
I'm also trying vmy best to endure the gas, but...
But...
But I'm not tired!
You're not tired?!
He's awake.
Hey, I wanna keep moving.
Crab-chan! We can't catch up to Ace now that you've closed off the stairs!
Sealing the stairs was the only way to stop the gas.
It'll be impossible to rescue him if you're unconscious.
I'm gonna save him even if I'm unconscious!
Do you realize Ace is going to be executed?!
Don't be too rash though.
The enemy's plan was simple, but we fell for it.
Now we're all stuck here on Level Six.
In this situation, there's no way to escape.
It's a shame, now all vwe can do is this!
Cut off their connection.
If vyou think logically, vwe just can't make it in time.
Ace-boy will have already been escorted to the meeting place.
We, on the other hand, have to deal with all the enemies standing in our way.
The military convoy is quite fast.
Observe the Vivre Card.
It's not pointing directly up, is it?
He's probably being handed over to the Navy as we speak.
Right now vwe need to change our attitude.
Vi will do everything in vmy power to help vyou escape this prison safely.
Ace-boy will most certainly be handed over to Navy Headquarters.
Vyou'll have to give up on him.
In fact, all we can do after that is trust in Whitebeard.
He's not the kind of man who would discard his own men!
He'll act in one way or another...
I'm going too.
Huh?
I'm going to Navy Headquarters!
Are vyou stupid?!
This is a battle between the world's greatest powers!
What can vyou do if you go there?
Do vyou realize Whitebeard's true strength?!
Do vyou realize the Navy's true strength in it's admirals, vice-admirals, and Warlords?!
Did vyou forget that vyou fought Magellan one on one and almost died?!
How many lives do you think you have to spare?!
What is it...
If I give up now,
I'll regret it forever!
This feeling...
I've felt it countless times before...
It's the exact same feeling I get when looking at Dragon!
Before all that, we can't even escape from this floor!
If you wanna escape from here, set me free.
I can open a hole in the ceiling.
So how about it?
You...!
You're a prisoner here?!
Crocodile!
Former Royal Shichibukai
Former Baroque Works President (Mr. 0)
Pirate
Sir Crocodile
Long time no see!
I'd been thinking that even if I were on the outside, there'd be nothing going on to interest me.
But now I hear the Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy are going to war?
I never thought I'd get the chance to take that old man's head.
I'm interested in this war.
With my powers, we can all escape from here.
It's not a bad deal, is it?
We've both got something to gain from it.
Get real!
You're the one who messed up Vivi's country...
That's all in the past.
I no longer have any interest in that country.
Let's release him, Straw-Hat-boy.
He would certainly make a powerful ally.
Iva-chan! That guy's...
Vyou're not stopping here.
If vyou're going to Navy HQ, vyou'll need him even more.
Ivankov...!
Long time no see, Croco-boy.
What? You know him?
Vwe've met...
Back when he was still a rookie.
It'll be alright.
Even if he were to try to betray vus, Vi can hold him back.
Vi can't completely trust him, but...
Vi've got a firm grasp on this guy's weakness.
As long as vyou're a good boy and help us out, Vi won't say a thing.
Why, you...!
What the hell? In that case, release me too!
Me too! I've got a grudge against that Whitebeard!
Release me too!
Silence!
Death Wink!
I beg of you!
Please, take me with you!
I'll definitely be able to help you!
I've known Ace-san ever since he joined the Whitebeard Pirates!
He's told me everything about you, his little brother!
I'm here because I was opposed to this war!
I wish to save Ace-san!
Please! Let me choose the place of my death!
He's another of the big shots.
The Warlord Jinbei, Knight of the Sea...
and Portgas D. Ace, commander of Whitebeard's second division.
I never thought a connection like that could exist.
Sure.
Hey, is that really okay?!
We know nothing of this guy's personality or how dangerous he might be!
It's fine. Let him out.
I am most grateful.
Hey! I'm also most grateful!
I beg of you!
Silence!
Death Wink!
I'd never have thought we'd be bringing two Warlords along...
Two? Who's the other one?
I'm grateful to you.
Now, I might be able to be of some use to him.
Even if you were able to prevent the war between Whitebeard and the Navy...
it wouldn't matter in the long run.
One way or another, I will definitely take that old man's head.
I won't let you lay a hand on old Whitebeard, Crocodile!
In that case, maybe I should just kill you now?
Croco-boy! Vyour past, remember?
Well then. There's no time to waste.
Vwe're gonna force our way out of this prison!