Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Formatting
Sewil
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
An Island in Chaos
Sorry guys.
Punching this guy means a navy admiral
is gonna come here with a warship...
I missed my chance to cut him down
because you beat him up first.
Hachi! Hang on!
You're all in big trouble now...!
We can't help it! That's just how Luffy is!
Alright then...
Guess that makes it clear
what we gotta do now.
I think the key to Camie's collar
is probably somewhere backstage!
I need to tend to Hachi's
injury! You get the key!
Guys...!
Charloss...!
Brother Charloss! Not even
Father has ever struck you!
Curse you!
How dare you a commoner
lay a hand on my son!
Th-They've made the Celestial Dragons mad!
Run! Get outside!
I'll teach you what happens
when you assault us
the descendants of this world's Creators!
Hell if we care you bastard!
How dare you strike Saint Roswald!
Joue!
Concasser!
Go Franky! Free Camie-chan!
Alright! Super leave it to me!
Guards! Get them! Seize the pirates!
They just keep coming!
Only a fool would protect a lousy fish!
You intend to defy us to
the very end do you?!
Camie isn't for sale!
Call for a navy admiral and a warship!
Let them see who's boss!
A pirate struck a Celestial Dragon!
Navy Headquarters is going
to send a warship now!
Duck!
36 Pound Cannon!
Are you trying to kill us?!
Camie!
Hatchin!
Are you okay?! They didn't do
anything bad to you did they?!
I'm fine! But you've been hurt!
Don't worry! Who do you take me for?!
I'm Hachi the takoyaki seller!
Just hang on a little
longer! Wait right there!
Yeah! Hatchin! Everyone!
An uproar is already underway. There's
a flood of people at the entrance.
Our only choice is to jump into the
fray! Just crash into it if you would!
Understood!
Huh?! I-I need to prepare myself first!
Here we go!
My "can't go to auction houses" disease...!
More flying fish!
Thank you!
Take care!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Alright! Good luck!
Off I go!
Clutch!
Now then! Pardon my late entrance!
Damn! Guard the mermaid at all costs!
500 million! She sold for 500 million!
Since I'm here maybe I'll
just fret for a little longer!
Get going already!
I actually would've preferred
to do it at my own pace!
I'll punish these cretins by
stuffing and preserving the women
and making the men slaves and starving them!
Father!
Oww oww...!
Wait that didn't hurt that much...
Sorry mister!
S-Saint Roswald too?!
You just repeated your crime pirate!
Usopp! Robin! Brook!
Looks like everyone's here!
Luffy! Where's Camie?!
Over there! We'll run away as soon
as the bomb around her neck is off!
We have to hurry before the
warship and admiral get here!
Eh?!
The navy's already here Straw Hat-ya.
Who're you?
What's with that bear?
They've had the place surrounded
before the auctions even began.
Navy Headquarters has a post
on this archipelago you see.
Please leave the area immediately!
It's all right! We're here!
How's it look inside?!
We've finished evacuating the patrons!
The three Celestial Dragons are still inside!
Bring them out at once!
You damn pirates! Don't think
you'll get out of here unhurt!
I dunno who they wanted to catch
but I doubt they expected anyone
would beat up the Celestial Dragons.
That was an interesting show
you gave Straw Hat-ya crew.
You must be Trafalgar Law.
Luffy. He's a pirate.
Huh?! The bear too?
The 500 million Berries!
P-P-Please wait Saint Shalria!
That item hasn't been paid for yet!
Please wait Saint Shalria! Saint Shalria!
Quiet commoner!
Crap! Camie-chan's in trouble!
Quit your squirming!
Damn...!
S-Saint Shalria!
See Mr. Giant?
The place is in a real uproar.
I'd say the auction's over.
I've stolen some money now
so guess I'll head back
to the gambling houses...
You're one disagreeable old man.
You were only here to get some money?
I was hoping for a chance to steal
from whoever bought me too...
But I guess it wasn't meant to be.
Oh right. I'm all out.
First thing is more alcohol.
Think about it.
I don't know about you but I wouldn't
want an old man like me for a slave.
Oh? Looks like we've
garnered some attention...
Who's that old man and that giant?!
Those are today's merchandise! How
did they get out of their cell?!
They don't have collars!
How did they unlock them?!
What do we do?
What do you mean? Catching people is
outside of our field of expertise!
We can't hold back an unshackled giant!
R-Rayleigh!
You mean Rayleigh the coating craftsman?!
Which one is he?!
Oh! Is that you Hachi?! It is!
It's good to see you again!
What are you doing here?!
How did you get that injury?!
No that's okay you needn't say a thing!
In short... I see. I understand
the situation now.
You sure got yourself into
a heap of trouble Hachi.
And you folks saved him?
Well then...
Is he...
It couldn't be!
Huh?! How?! What did you just do?!
Who is this old guy?!
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
I've been wanting to meet you...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
Sabaody Archipelago Lawless Zone
This is bad! This town-- this
whole archipelago-- is in danger!
Straw Hat Luffy supposedly kicked
a Celestial Dragon's ass!
At the auction house on Grove #1!
What?!
Apparently Kid and Law are there too!
That Straw Hat bastard!
What was he thinking?!
Doesn't he know that an admiral
from Navy Headquarters
will bring a warship here if
anyone hurts a Celestial Dragon?!
Has our ship been coated?!
It was completed yesterday!
We set sail for Fish-Man Island immediately!
We can't just sit around
while an admiral shows up!
There's no point in staying here!
Yes sir!
Guess that dumbass's captain
is an even bigger dumbass!
If I ever run into 'em in the
New World... I'll destroy 'em!
Causing trouble with Navy Headquarters
with the New World right in sight...
What a truly troublesome lot they are...
Focus on getting ready to set sail.
Yes sir! Right away Captain Drake!
Now then. Who's going to show up?
Given the situation I somehow doubt
this is an all-out arrest plot.
It's Straw Hat Luffy they're after right?
I think I'd like to see what
an admiral is actually like.
You can't be serious Apoo-san!
Let's just get out of here!
Captain Hawkins! It's dangerous
here! Let's set sail immediately!
Calm down.
I am not destined to die today.
"Holy Land of Marie Jois"
That brat again?! It's one
thing after the other!
What's with that entire family's bloodline?!
Reports indicate the presence
of the Straw Hat crew
Eustass Captain Kid and his crew
and Trafalgar Law and his crew.
Thirteen people with bounties
have been confirmed!
Of them five are rookies
worth over 100 million each!
Naturally the key offender
appears to be Monkey D. Luffy
who assaulted the Celestial Dragons!
We've lost contact with the
guards at the Human Shop--
oh I mean Employment Office.
I believe they may have all been subdued...
In any case this act of taking
three Celestial Dragons hostage
is a vile and unprecedented transgression!
Have they made any demands?
No none at the moment...
Whatever the case may be Sengoku-san
we'll need to take action
given that World Nobles are the victims here.
Kizaru...
Allow me to go. Rest easy; I won't be long.
"Justice"
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 1
Human Auction Shop
Backstage
This is no laughing matter!
This is your shop you know!
Mister Doflamingo...!
Where are you right now?!
The shop has lost all credibility and
then there's Roswald's family too!
They're definitely going to lash out at us!
Do something to fix things!
Seriously... Human trafficking
is so old-fashioned you idiot.
It's all about smiles now! Smiles!
Disco I'm giving the shop to you.
So don't be callin' me anymore!
What?! You're abandoning us during
the worst crisis we've ever had?!
Quiet you annoying bastard!
While you sit there blaming
me for your own misfortune
a "New Era" draws ever closer Disco-kun.
The navy has given orders forcing
me-- no us-- into active duty!
Knowing this what do you see
on the horizon Disco-kun?
The Whitebeard Pirates versus
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Grove 1
In Front of the Auction House
Please evacuate as far away as you can!
No watching please! These
are dangerous people!
The slave I bought is still inside!
Have the mortars arrived yet?
Yes most of them! We're
hurrying to set them up!
Has HQ said anything?
That Admiral Kizaru is coming but
the vanguard will consist of...
Of them?! They're coming here?!
Yes sir! That's what they said...
Hold on old man! Don't
be crazy! It'll explode!
We've seen a slave's collar explode before!
That's a bad idea! A very bad idea!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
I dunno what kind of power he used...
What's Franky doing?!
I'm telling you it's too dangerous!
It won't come off without the key!
It's ringing! What're we gonna do?!
Camie!
What's all this now?!
Don't scare me like that!
Your collar and handcuffs are already off!
It came off...
C-Camie!
Camie! Thank goodness!
What the hell?! I finally manage
to find 'em but then...!
Oh! You found them? Well done!
But we no longer need them.
Here you carry this girl.
U-Umm... Th-Thanks!
What in the hell's going on
here?! Who are you anyway?!
Huh? What did he do?
That geezer did something mysterious again!
Just who is that old guy?!
Hey almost-slaves!
All the buyers took off! You
should scram while you can too!
Here!
If that geezer took out these
guards all at once too
then he must know how to use
magic or some type of sorcery!
He's got powers or something!
He said something about
your straw hat though...
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
I've been wanting to meet you...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
How do you know him Luffy?!
I don't know him! Really!
I think he used what's called "Haki."
I don't know much about it either though...
Sorry about that fellows. I didn't
realize other pirates were watching.
You must be quite strong to have
withstood that with no problem at all.
I never expected to meet
such a big-shot here...
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh...
No doubt about it. What's a legendary
man doing in a place like this?
On these islands I'm Ray-san
the coating craftsman.
Don't go calling me that other name.
I'm an old soldier now. I just
want to live in peace and quiet.
I take it you'll survive Hachi?
After I told you all those times
not to walk around these islands...
I'm sorry...
Thanks for saving my friend fellows.
So what's this about wanting
to meet me old guy?
Yes let's save that for later.
We first need to get out of here.
They have the place completely
surrounded Boss.
Alright you criminals! Release
the Roswald family at once!
An admiral will be arriving shortly!
I recommend immediate surrender!
Don't blame us for whatever
happens you rookies!
We're not only caught up in this we're
being treated as accomplices now.
I got a good glimpse of the insanity
that makes Straw Hat Luffy so notorious.
I have no complaints but I'd rather not
run into an admiral now if I can avoid it!
Oh I'd prefer not to use that power of
mine anymore so I leave this to you!
It'll be hard for me to stay settled
down if the navy discovers who I am.
I have no intention of helping
out a senior citizen!
The longer we stay here the
more troops there'll be!
I think I'll go on ahead!
While I'm at it I'll help you guys out too!
I'll clean things up outside so don't worry!
I told you I'll do it!
Shut up!
I'm gonna do it!
Get outta here!
Shut up you guys!
I'm going to do it.
What're you talking about?!
I told you leave it to me!
No! I'm gonna do it!
Don't tell me what to do!
You guys just don't get it!
You're the one who doesn't get it!
Alright!
You guys can go back inside!
Hey! Are you even listening?!
I told you two to stay back!
Tell me what to do again and I'll start
by getting rid of you Eustass-ya!
Get ready!
Geez they're so simpleminded!
Hey! There's gonna an all-out brawl!
Let's use that chance to escape! We
can't just sit around here anyway!
Hatchin...
Thanks... I'm sorry for
causing you trouble...!
Never mind me! I'm just
glad you're all right!
Let's follow them. We're going
to break through in one go.
All right then.
Let us meet up on Grove #13 should
we find ourselves separated.
Grove #13? Got it!
You don't "got it" at all!
What will you do Mr. Giant?!
We were all on the verge of becoming slaves.
I'm going to flee somewhere
with these people!
I see! Be careful not to
draw attention to yourself!
Old man! Straw Hat's friends!
I will repay this favor if we
ever meet again! Thank you!
Thanks so much!
Thank you!
Sure no problem!
You're taking credit?!
Mortars! Fire!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Repel!
Room.
Wh-What's this circle?!
Shambles.
Watch out! All three of 'em have powers!