Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Infoboxes
Timing
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
I have reached my limit! I have a muscle cramp!
Duval's Tragedy
Though I do not have any muscles to have a cramp in!
Brook, you're pretty enthusiastic, huh?
You took out quite a few of the Flying Fish.
I am glad to have been of help!
But please... let me rest for a while...
Zoro-san...
It looks like you're still hurt...
I won't let these fish beat me! Don't worry about it!
You let down your guard, Roronoa!
Six-Sword Style...
Octopus-Arm Danger!
You saved me, huh?
That's right! You guys were spacing out and all...
Hacchin! You were really cool!
Just what I'd expect from you, Hachi!
Really?
Die, fishman!
Right! Excuse me!
I thought I was gonna die! Thanks!
I told you to watch yourself, didn't I?
Don't take them on one by one... Get in formation!
Formation (Hentai)
Pervert?
Pervert
(Hentai)
You called?
Attack in flying formation!
Formation (Hentai)
Flying (Hikou)
Delinquent pervert?
Pervert (Hentai)
Delinquent (Hikou)
You mean me?
They're here!
Here I am! Here!
Welcome!
A woman? It's a shame, but we were ordered to kill everyone!
Can you kill me?
What the-?!
Too bad.
Mirage Tempo!
Beware of thunderclouds of despair!
Dos Mano
Clutch!
Split-Hoof
Diamond!
Don't break formation!
I knew it, they're calling for me.
Now!
Huh? They didn't mean me?
What?! Bullets don't affect him?!
Strong Hammer!
Amazing! They're all really strong, Pappag!
To think they'd go this far...
We were just gonna grab Hachi and escape...
Take this!
Damn! Franky! We need to get the ship ashore!
They're at an advantage out here in the ocean!
That's probably why they live out here, you know.
They're not gonna give us a chance to steer the ship!
Luffy!
Run! A huge guy is coming!
Is it the Iron Mask?!
The masked guy and a cow!
A cow?
That's Motobaro's voice!
It's the Head!
Getting yourselves knocked down in droves...
What's that?! Something showed up!
Duval's
Beloved Bison
Motobaro
You're not just bugs, y'know! Flying Fish Riders!
H-He crushed his own house...
I don't need this base any more, as long as I can kill the Straw Hats!
We're so sorry, Head! We'll draw them out to sea and finish them off right...
Move it!
I have no need for a fishman, mermaid, or glove! If you wanna run, then just get lost!
I'm a starfish!
I didn't enter the slave-trading market 'cause I wanted to!
You guys understand that, right?!
Of course, Head!
What a great day this is!
The man whom I wanted to kill so badly that I even saw him in my dreams, is right here.
I'm so grateful!
I guess there is a god, huh?
One day, I was suddenly thrown into the depths of hell because of that man!
Hey, isn't he looking at us while he's talking?
Today, I'll kill ya right here, even if I die myself...
Pirate... Black Leg Sanji!
I really wanted to meet'cha!
Oh, crap! The Head's really pissed off!
Me? That guy wants to kill me?
Sanji, who's that guy?
It seems like he's got some sort of grudge against you...
Could it be something that happened at the restaurant? Try to remember!
If it's something from back then, I did plenty of things that people might be mad at me for...
Let him shoot you! You've deserved it!
Quit playin' dumb, Black Leg!
We're talkin' about somethin' recent here!
Crap! Those are harpoons!
But if it's something recent, then I'm even more confused!
W-What? There's something strange about these harpoons...
These're my scorpion venom harpoons!
If they hit'cha, ya'll be headed for the afterlife in three minutes!
Know the depths of my fury!
Nami-san, watch out!
Damn bastard, I can't remember at all! Who are you?!
I'm gonna kill ya and yer crew!
I saw what was underneath that mask.
Really? Who is he?
Don't be surprised. You've seen his face too!
Me too?
That bastard...!
He knocked off Duval-sama's iron mask!
Very well... Take a close look at my scarred face!
What the-?!?!?!
No way!
He's...!
My...
Oh, my...
I wanna cry!
I've been waitin' for this day...
I decided to murder ya, and so I set out to sea!
But lookin' for ya would be a problem, y'know...
After all, yer wanted poster and yer true face didn't match!
Even if the marines or bounty hunters ran into ya, they just might' not notice ya!
Nah, there's no way that'd happen!
Those guys'd definitely find ya!
Head...!
They'd find ya, and then they'd say...
"Found you!"
"Black Leg Sanji!"
And then I'd tell 'em...
"I dunno anyone like that!"
"I ain't even a pirate!"
Hey, Sanji, where are you going?!
Do ya realise...
How frightenin' it was, suddenly bein' targeted by bounty hunters?!
Why?
Why'd I suddenly have to be chased by the Navy HQ?!
Why'd all those big name bounty hunters suddenly start huntin' me?!
Why?!
Sanji?
What'd I do?!
Give me my life back!
Black Leg Sanji!
Like I care!
Head!
Whaddaya mean, "Like I care"?!
If ya ain't gonna take responsibility for dis, then who will?!
Shut up!
I'm more pissed about that wanted-poster than anyone!
So, things like this really can happen, huh?
What a surprise...
This world is really big.
Was Sanji born under some kind of miracle-star or something?
He might meet quite an interesting end someday...
I can't help but feel sorry for that Duval guy...
Those two look exactly like each other!
Like two peas in a pod.
Brook! I'm so gonna kick the crap out of you afterwards!
Well then, Sanji...
We'll just be going on ahead.
Are you saying this is my fault?!
If you don't want to look like that wanted picture, you could just change your hairstyle or your beard!
There are plenty of things you could just change!
So I could have done that?
Are you all morons?!
We're not morons!
You know, Black Leg, we...
We...
Were running a small, unknown mafia in some distant corner of this sea...
We spent every single day by threatening the villagers for money...
That was the kind of happy life we had.
Black Leg...
Do you understand?
I, who had never caused any kind of uproar...
Suddenly found myself with a bounty of 77 million...
And was chased around by those powerful marines...
I got this nasty scar on my back,
and was forced to wear this iron mask to hide my face from the world!
It's yer fault dat my life was ruined!
I'm prepared to chase ya to da ends of Hell!
If dat's a problem for ya...
Then how about you just kill me right now?!
I'm bein' killed!
Those stupid accusations of yours...
Why'd you even have to put Nami-san and Robin-chan in danger?!
It's dat ship and dat crew dat made ya a famous pirate!
Of course I'd want revenge on'em!
Ya guys should all die!
Poison harpoons?!
Get in formation!
Huh?
Oh, crap!
Sanji-kun!
They're trying to pull him down into the ocean!
Sanji! Hurry up and get out of there!
Damn, this net is made of steel!
Now suffer and drown!
Sanji!
Dammit... I'll save you right now!
Don't go there yourself, idiot! I'll go get him!
Wait!
You humans are too slow, you can't catch him!
Leave this to me!
Fool!
You fishmen don't stand a chance at catching up!
The Flying Fish are the fastest animals in the sea!
And the Riders riding them have air canisters, so they can stay under water for as long as they like!
That guy doesn't stand a chance!
The next time that guy, Black Leg surfaces...
He'll already have drowned and died!
What was that!?
Feel the Head's anger, Black Leg!
Can't breathe...
It's okay!
Camie!
Hey, cowboy!
It seems that you forgot someone here!
Huh?
The Flying Fish are most certainly faster than fishmen.
They're in the top-class among sea-creatures. They really are something!
However...
The creatures at the very top of that top-class are the merfolk!
In this great sea...
There are no creatures that can outrun a mermaid under water!
It's alright...
I'll save you right now, Sanji-chin!
Is she really that incredible?
Actually, if she hadn't been spacing out all the time, nobody would ever catch her!
I see...
Camie!
Take care of Sanji!
What's that?!
A huge anchor?
It's way too huge!
Aim for the Straw Hat crew's ship.
Hit it head-on and sink it!
Some of'em are Devil Fruit users!
If we get'em into the water, they're ours!
This is bad! Just one hit from that and we'll sink!
Dodge it! Use the Burst or the Paddle! Can we make it?
No, it's too late!
Hurry and come with me, Usopp!
Huh?
Y-Yeah!
You get on the bow!
Huh?
Uh, right!
We're gonna use our secret weapon!
Secret weapon?
Drop it!
The Sunny's in trouble!
That thing is dangerous!
Believe in this ship!
The mane started spinning!
Sink!
It's falling right at us!
Emergency Evasion...
Secret Weapon!
Chicken Voyage!
They dodged it!
No way!
I've never heard of any ship that can go backwards!
Usopp!
Get inside the prow!
The prow?
Woah! You can enter it!
Don't think dodging it was all we could do!
This ship has got way more power than that!
Awesome!
What is it now?!
Charging complete!
Hey!
What should I do now?
Get as many as you can inside the circle!
Circle?
Like this?
They're in!
Lock on with the button on the handle, then pull the lever!
This and...
This?
What's that?
Gaon: Lion's roar
Gaon Cannon!
Fire!
Amazing!
You're too impressed!
Did you see that?!
The Sunny's full power?
That move took out almost all the Flying Fish!
That's just how good Usopp is!
For a first try it was magnificent!
Wow!!! What an amazing destructive power!
Sunny!
Lion-chan is incredible! It seemed as if my eyes were going to pop out!
Though I have no eyes to pop out...
It uses three barrels of cola to prevent the ship from being blown away...
And at the same time, it releases two barrels worth of Coup de Burst from the cannon.
It uses a ton of cola, so don't you overuse it!
She's tied us up with the net!
Damn!
That speedy mermaid!
We're almost there, Sanji-chin...
Hang in there!
Camie!
Thank goodness!
Is Sanji all right?
Everyone, it's terrible!
Sanji-chin is losing a lot of blood!
Huh?
Did he get done in?!
Just when I thought I'd saved him, a lot of blood suddenly started flowing out of his nose!
Nosebleed?
It's fine...
If he dies like that, then let him die.
That's true...
At least he seems happy.
Hang in there, Sanji-chin!
Is this...
Heaven?
Damn...
He survived, huh?!
Well, it looks like your subordinates are useless now, doesn't it?
Why, you...!
Then, I guess you should learn how terrifying Motobaro is!
I've lost count of how many fools have been impaled by his giant horns to this day!
They say his horns have even managed to destroy village dams...
Put him in a cage, and he'll break straight out!
The only reason I've been able to escape from the Navy all this time...
Is because of this guy's horns!
They call them the "Heart-smashing horns"!
All right.
I'll stop you!
Go, Motobaro!
Watch out, Luffy!
The horns were completely useless!
There's no point in us fighting!
Hey, what's wrong, Motobaro?
The cow's acting strangely, isn't it?
What?
He lost consciousness?
What just happened?
Luffy!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Motobaro!
Damn, how can this be?!
It doesn't seem like he attacked it...
It seems like Luffy won the cow over by talking to it...
What?
You mean, he psyched it out?
But that huge thing just fainted!
Is that even possible?
Why, you... Damn Straw Hat kid...!
Hey, wait a minute, Luffy!
Sanji!
I'm glad you're alright!
I'll end this stupid incident filled with pointless accusations myself!
Finish it?
Black Leg!
As long as you keep on living as a pirate I'll never find peace!
I'm the one who's sick of the accusations!
Shut up!
I don't want to see that stupid poster-face any more than you do.
It shouldn't even exist in real life!
Well, then...
You should just die!
Oeil
Eye
Nez
Nose
Joue
Cheek
Bouche
Mouth
Dents
Teeth
Menton
Jaw
Please, stop it...
Parage Shot!
Trimming Shot
Taste the classiness of my finishing attack, and end your misery.
You shitty bastard.