Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Infoboxes
Timing
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Iron Mask Duval
The Flying Fish just... left?
Even though they were focused on the attack back there...
It seems like they received some kind of message.
Maybe they were ordered to retreat? Although I wouldn't know why...
I wanna ride those! Those Flying Fish can stay in the air for five minutes, huh?
Awesome!
Anyway, we're now headed for their base, right?
In that case, we'd better be prepared to fight them again.
But who'd have guessed that they'd come at us from the sky?
How about getting the cannons out on the deck?
I'll shoot them all down!
Nice thinking!
I wonder if Hacchin is alright...
You know, Macro is really after you!
You've gotta be careful too!
East of the
Sabaody Archipelago
The Flying Fish Riders'
Headquarters
Duval-sama! The three of them have returned!
Duval-sama, why'd you order us to pull back?
I'd like to know that too.
You could have just left the capture of the mermaid and the pirates to us!
You idiots!
You guys...
Kidnapping Gang
"Flying Fish Riders"
Head
"Iron Mask Duval"
Do you have any idea how long I've been anticipating...
The arrival of...
Those pirates?!
Whenever I think of dat man...
This huge, great scar on my back starts throbbin' like hell!
O-Oh, crap! The Head's mad!
Ev'ry single day... I've cursed dat man's name ev'ry single day!
Head, please calm down!
I'm gonna kill dat guy right here, today!
Got it?!
Dat's my life-long, immortal wish!
Do ya understand?!
Y-Yes! That guy can't be allowed to live!
And dat's why ya gotta make sure to do this properly! Dat's how we'll get'im!
You punks just follow my orders exac'ly!
Yes, Head!
Hey, Macro-crew!
Huh? You called?
What is it, Duva?
"Duva"?" Whaddaya mean, Gyaro?! And what's with the "Huh", Tansui?!
Ya guys should learn some better manners!
Heh, "Duva", that's funny!
Macro Pirates
Gyaro
(Pop-Eyed Goldfish Fishman)
Macro Pirates Boss
Macro
(Makuropharynx
Fishman)
Macro Pirates
Tansui
(Arowana Fishman)
Geez! Oh, you called, Master Duval?!
Boss... This guy's totally freaked out...
Oh, shut up!
Ahhh, I apologize profusely, Master...
These guys are complete idiots, they don't even know what they're sayin'!
Oh, it's fine, you guys.
To me, you're like my angels of good fortune.
I can't even say how thankful I am to you.
Go on.
I told you to shut up, Tansui!
Thanks to you guys... at last...
I can meet them...
The Straw Hat... Pirates!
Straw Hats? Who're they?
The Straw Hats? So it wasn't just my imagination?
Listen up...
Dat guy...
Dat guy I bin waitin' all my life ter kill is on dat boat, a'ight?!
I ain't never gonna forgive dat punk!!!
Head! Calm down, please!
He really does hate that guy, huh?
I never thought I'd hear the name "The Straw Hat Pirates" here...
Hey, you, the big guy!
It's Duval-sama! Show some manners, you damn octopus!
Takoyaki Shop Owner
Hacchan
(Octopus Fishman)
Former Officer of the Arlong Pirates
Are you saying that Camie has been captured by the Straw Hat Pirates?!
This is bad... Of all the people to run into...
Are they coming here as well?
Yeah, they're heading here right now.
But ain't it your mermaid friend who's turned to the pirates for help?
I don't know the details, but it doesn't seem like she's been caught.
Well, no matter who she brings with her,
as long as we're here, we'll just catch'em all and sell them to the Human Shop!
As if they could do that!
Those guys are terrifyingly strong!
This is a problem... I wonder if Nami's there too...
I wonder if she's still mad at me...
Well, of course she would be...
I did those horrible things to her when I was with Arlong, and all...
If I don't hurry up and escape before those guys get here, they'll definitely beat me up, too...
I'm in trouble!
Duval-sama! The Straw Hats are here!
They're finally here?
Say, Macro...
Huh? What is it?
I'll give you lots of takoyaki, so could you please let me go?
Yeah, right! Dumbass! What kinda glutton do you take me for?!
Is that man on the ship?
Yes! He's definitely there!
It's about time for you to pay the piper, an' all! Prepare yourself!
Looks like that's the Flying Fish Riders' base.
And this Hacchin-guy is being kept over there?
I'll go in there and save him in a flash, Camie-chwan~!
Thanks a lot, Sanji-chin!
Oh! But everyone! Please be careful!
The Macro Crew alone have captured me about 30 times!
You get captured too much!
You get eaten too much too.
This isn't really an island, though. It seems like someone built a village on top of the water.
But why would they want to set up their base here?
Who knows...
Anyway, it sure is quiet here.
Luffy! Should we really...
Forward!
Shouldn't we at least think of a plan?!
Hey! Hacchin! Are you alright?!
Get out here, Macro! Give Hachi back!
Oh, crap! It really is the Straw Hats' ship!
Damn it!
I really can't get out... Well, in that case...!
Octo-Hachi Black!
It seems like someone is inside that cage.
Could that be Hacchin...?
This is great, Camie! There aren't even any enemies around!
They must all be off having a snack!
Are you guys serious?!
Anyone could tell that this is a trap!
Everyone is obviously hiding in there, waiting to ambush us.
What insight!
I-I never would have considered that!
That's why you keep getting caught!
I'm here! Camie, I'm okay, so you don't have to worry!
You're all black! What happened?!
Well, this is kinda my own fault...
Anyway, this is a trap, so hurry up and turn back!
You know that I'm strong, right? So it's fine, just go!
That voice is really familiar, and then there's that unusual silhouette...
Hey, Nami, what do you think?
There's something very suspicious about him...
What?
We'll know if we ask him, right?
Hey! Is Arlong doing alright?!
Huh? Arlong?
No, him, Choo, Kuroobi and everyone else got caught by the Navy.
I was the only one who escaped, and I'm now living out my old dream of running a takoyaki-stand.
Arlong...?
So it was you, huh? You damn squid!
Damn it!
So you're that damn squid who was with Arlong?! You're that takoyaki-seller, Hacchin?!
What?
Well, it was a while ago now...
Nami's hometown was once under the control of a nasty crew of fishmen called the Arlong Pirates...
Nami was in quite a terrible situation herself...
And that octopus was one of the top-members.
So he's an old enemy, huh?
Of course, I took Luffy and the others along, and kicked the crap out of the whole crew!
Usopp, you're awesome!
Y... yeah, I guess...
I thought all the fishmen were arrested by the Navy... But it seems like that guy managed to get away...
I see. You have gone through a lot...
Hey, squid! Now that we know it's you, there's no way we'll save you!
B-But...
I-Is your takoyaki really as good as I heard it was?!
Oh, come on! Getting caught between your appetite and your reason?
How stupid.
You mean, you know Hacchin?
Is Hacchin an old friend of yours?
He's not our friend!
Turn the ship around!
Nami-chin...
Sorry, Camie...
We never would have thought your friend was that guy...
No way...
You won't help me save him after all?
Hacchin!
Camie! That's okay! Just turn back! This is a trap!
No... I'll save you...
Hacchin, you're always saving us after all!
Pappag!
That's right! I never thought you guys would be such a load of unfeeling halfwits!
Idiots! Idiots!
Shut up!
Wait for us, Hachi!
We definitely won't abandon you, Hacchin!
Here we go!
Camie-chan!
We've got you now, Camie!
Oh, come on, that's just pathetic!
Now we're gonna be rich!
With Hachi, who always saves you, in that state and all!
You won't get away, Camie!
That's why I told you to run! Camie! Pappag!
Why, you... Camie hasn't done anything!
Wait, Sanji-kun!
Fine, let's save Hachi as well.
Hachi isn't that bad! Actually, he's harmless.
And we did make a promise to Camie.
N-Nami-swan... That firm, determined appearance is just wonderful!
Hey, Nami...
Is that really fine?
Yes.
Luffy!
If you say so, then I guess there's no choice.
Let's save the octopus as well.
Your eyes turned into takoyaki!
Are the preparations ready...
Flying Fish Riders?
Of course, we're always prepared!
Rubber...
Pistol!
Wait a minute!
He's a Devil Fruit User?!
Straw Hat?
Damn him!
Luffy-chin!
You...
Alright! I got them back!
Straw Hat! Thank you so much! I'm indebted to you!
Zoro! Cut the octopus' ropes and the cage!
Sure!
Straw Hat! Be careful!
You've already sprung the trap!
The Flying Fish Riders have you surrounded!
Charge!
Yes sir!
Luffy-chin...
Whether it's from the sea, or the sky, we're ready for'em!
We're gonna beat'em all!
You guys!
Prepare for battle!
Yeah!
Damn it... Now, while we have the chance, let's take Camie back!
Camie! Pappag! It's dangerous, so stand back!
Get them! Go, Luffy-chin!
Now, come, Flying Fish!
Get them, get them, go, go!
Here they come!
Alright!
Well, well...  Who's got the freshest fish here?
Alright! Him!
I got him!
What?
My turn!
Uh, wait...
This is awesome!
Whoo! I'm flying!
Luffy's riding one of those things?!
Ignore him.
Take this!
Bombs!
Damn!
Too dangerous! That was close!
Geez... If they had hit a lady with that, I wouldn't have let them live.
Pull in the sail! It'll get in the way!
Everybody, dive!
Understood!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
We're in the middle of a fight, so what the heck do you think you're doing?!
I'b sowwy...
Oh, and why'd you two try to save him? You're Devil Fruit users too, right?!
I seem to have troubled you, too...
It's even worse when we have to save all three of you hammers!
Idiot, don't waste my time!
The Macro crew!
Now, let's get Camie back while we have the chance!
Yeah!
Hey, Straw! Could you give us a hand here?
You freed me from the ropes and the cage! Thanks, Roronoa! You're a nice guy, huh?
It was the captain's orders, idiot.
Hachi!
Hacchin!
You guys! You took advantage of the fact that I couldn't move and beat me as much as you wanted!
I haven't punched you yet, Hachi! I'll finish you off with my Fishman Karate!
Man, you've got terrible luck!
Stop flappin' your mouth like that, damn it!
We've got much worse in store for you!
Now, come! I've developed a new style of Goldfish Fencing just for you!
The waters will be stained with blood!
Hacchin!
Takoyaki Punch!
We'll let you go for now!
Hacchin!
Camie! Pappag!
I'm so glad, Hacchin!
I'm so sorry, Camie, Pappag! I was going to save you!
Don't worry about it, Hachi!
Ah! Watch out!
Don't forget that this is our territory! After all, the ones who caught you in the first place...
Were us, the Flying Fish Riders!
Roronoa!
Zoro-chin!
You need to watch yourselves...
Get back. You can just leave this to us.
Thanks for everything, Roronoa!
I'm really sorry for what happened back then!
I hurt you pretty badly with my Six-Sword Style...
You didn't even land a single blow, as far as I remember!
Oh, that's right.
We did it, Chopper! Now, take this!
Fire!
Bullseye! Did you see that, you damn fish?!
Usopp, you're amazing!
Anyone up for the Zero Fight?
The Zero Fight?
Interesting! But isn't that move life-threatening for us too?
I'm sure that you will be more than up to paying the medical fees?
I'll give you a million!
I'll do it, Head! I'll go! Move, move, move!
A really huge guy is coming! And he's swinging a massive club...
He isn't steering at all... Don't tell me that he is just going for a collision...
If that giant hits us at that speed, the ship won't hold...
Luffy! You take care of the fish.
Sure.
Interesting... With this size and speed, the impact will be like a small meteor!
He's not changing his course at all, just like Sanji said!
However, he's not the only one... who can deal some damage while in the air!
Rubber Balloon!
This'll be our dinner tonight!
That's so cool, you two!
Looking at it up close, it really is big.
Damn... This crew doesn't seem like it'll go down easily.
Now that I look at it, there are a lot of them flying around up there...
How many will we have to beat before it ends?
I wanna ride one, dammit! Don't think I've given up just because of what happened earlier!
Give it up! I won't save you again!
How can this be?
What's up, Brook?
To think that my first real action as a member of the Straw Hat Crew was to drown...
It would be a disgrace if I did not help you!
It is about time we reduced the number of those Flying Fish...
Please observe!
What an incredible jump!
What's with that skeleton mask guy?
We'll skewer you!
Lullaby Song
Flan!
Wow! They all fell asleep...
You too?!
Music is... Power!
Excuse me!
We fell asleep!
Damn him, what was that?!
He used some sort of dirty trick!
It is no trick!
It is music!
Wait!
He's pretty good, that Brook!
Looks fun... Here I come!
Wait, Luffy! Not again!
Alright, I caught you! I won't forgive you if you dive again!
Hey, you're asleep?!
Hey, hey! Wake up!
That guy! He went into the Head's room!
You saw it...?
You...!
It seems like you know me...