The Great Pirate Era...
has proven to be a more tumultuous storm than the World Government expected.
The figures in the eye of this relentless tempest are...
Monkey D. Luffy...
and the Straw Hat Pirates!
To confront the furious Great Pirate Era...
fifty world leaders have come
together for the Reverie...
a quadrennial conference that will commence shortly.
Now is a time of great change.
The Empty Throne
Kaido-sama !
What is it?!
Don't bother me when I'm drinking!
No! I didn't mean to!
The thing is...
Whole Cake Island
What do you want?!
It's about Straw Hat.
He's on his way to you.
What are you getting at?
Listen, keep your hands off him!
I'm coming to Wano to claim Straw Hat's head myself.
Is this some kind of joke?! I refuse!
I have no business with you.
If I don't personally squash Straw Hat,
I'll become a laughingstock.{Zenef: I like the original line "I'll lose face" but it's much shorter than the spoken line.}
Besides, he has something that I want back!
I don't care!
You still owe me big time, don't you?
Owe you?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
That was a long time ago!
Even so, it was a lifelong debt.
I'm the one who'll get even
with that Straw Hat rookie!
So I'm the one who'll kill him!
Show your face, and I'll kill you too, Linlin!
I'd like to see you try.
I'm not asking your permission;
this is merely a courtesy call.
Got that? Straw Hat's head is mine!
So let's play nice... for old times' sake!
New Marineford
Big Mom is on the move!
It seems she's contacted Kaido!
They're using an unsecured channel!
Don't they care if we overhear?!
Are they trying to provoke us?
So let's play nice...
{What could oppose both
Emperor Big Mom and Emperor Kaido?}What force could possibly oppose
Emperor Big Mom and Emperor Kaido?
Admirals? The Seven Warlords?
Should I head out, Sakazuki?
Wait, Borsalino.
We have zero intel on Wano's military capacity.
Their samurai, you mean?
Seriously?! Garp-chan ?!
The Red Port
Don't Kaido and Big Mom each have
a bone to pick with your grandson?!
With Straw Hat Luffy?!
What a riot!
You realize this isn't a joke, right?
You're saying you'd just let two emperors team up?
Vice Admiral Gion "Momousagi"
Navy Headquarters
{Well, it's not like we can do anything anyway;
it's the Reverie!}It's not as if we can do anything right now.
Not during the Reverie anyway.
Most of our manpower has been
assigned to protect royalty!
But if nothing is done...
Pardon me, ma'am,
but this is Big Mom we're talkin' about.
She must've known the Navy ain't gonna spare a soul,
Vice Admiral Tokikake "Chaton"
Navy Headquarters
what with the Reverie!
You're right, but...
What did Mister Sakazuki say?
He said, "Wano is a not a member country,
so it's outside our jurisdiction."
Figured as much!
Best not to get involved for now!
But Garp-kun,
if Big Mom and Kaido are up to something again,
Rear Admiral Hina
Navy Headquarters
we shouldn't take it lightly.
After all,
they're the reason you're
known as the "Hero of the Navy."
Rocks, huh?
{Hina, you're quite young.
Where did you hear about this?}Hina, I'd've guessed you'd be
too young to hear about that.
Before Roger, that era belonged to them !
But that was 40 years ago.
The past is in the past.
Though they lost their captain,
their influence only grows.
Hina's worried.
No point worrying!
{True, they would be a threat if they returned,
but things never turn out how you'd expect anyway...}True, they'd be a threat if they returned,
but the future always finds ways to surprise us!
But seriously, that bounty on your grandson's
a real nuisance, ain't it?
It recently jumped to 1.5 billion belly, didn't it?
Why are you smiling? Hina's confused.
And he's still just getting started...
Pangaea Castle
You may enter, King Sterry of Goa.
So this is the center of the world!
– Now, swear your oath.
– What?
C-Can I sit there?!
Don't joke about such things!
Tch!
No one is allowed to sit upon that throne.
It is the Empty Throne.
It symbolizes equality between the nations' leaders.
The oath affirms that no ruler
will seek dominion over the rest.
The 20 weapons that stand sentinel over the throne...
were placed there 800 years ago to represent
the oaths of the First Twenty, the world's creators.
It is located at the very center of the world.
Its vacancy is evidence of peace.
{The greatest authority in the world remains with the Five Elders, the highest-ranking Celestial Dragons.}As the Five Elders, the Celestial Dragons' leadership, remain the greatest authority in the world,
their division of power symbolizes how there is no one ruler over all.
Now, swear your oath, King Sterry.
If I sit there, I'll be king of the world!
King Sterry?
I wanna sit there!
A Courtyard
Pangaea Castle
Come on!
What are you...?!
Please stop!
I caught one-ee !
Saint Charlos
World Noble (Celestial Dragon)
I caught a giant mermaid-ee !
Shirahoshi!
Father...
Do you expect us to overlook
such disrespect, Father?!
Come on! Calm down!
What are you doing?! Please stop!
That's right! Chain her up!
Shirahoshi!
Hold it! What are you doing,
Princess of Arabasta?!
Shirahoshi-chan !
Stop, Rebecca! He's a Celestial Dragon!
So what?! Let go of me!
They lack common sense!
If you anger them, they'll destroy Dressrosa!
That bastard!
Don't do it, Leo!
Shirahoshi!
Whoa, come on!
No one interfere!{Hard to say, but the manga seems to have him thinking it. His mouth doesn't look like it's speaking.}{Do you think he's actually saying this, or do we leave this in the Thoughts style?}
Come on!
Capture it, Slave #3!
I'll make it my pet-ee !
{I can't just stand here!
How dare he do that to our boss' friend!}No standin' around!
He's gonna pay for doin' this to our boss' friend!
Leo!
Damn! There's no other way!
I'm coming for you, Mermaid Princess!
– Don't do it, Kanese soldier!
– Somebody, stop him!
Let me go!
Leo!
Who are you bastards?!
Rob Lucci
Cipher Pol Aegis 0
You should be thanking me.
Cipher Pol 0.
Yes indeedy.
Stopping you just spared several countries.
Kaku
Don't ruffle the feathers of Celestial Dragons.
Even young 'uns know that.
Stussy
Cipher Pol is a secret organization
under the direct control of the World Government.
Aegis 0 is the top unit in the agency,
boasting the most powerful agents.
Sai!
The Celestial Dragons are the gods
who created this world.
And though you are royalty,
you merely rule the lower realm.
It's only natural for gods to get whatever they want.
He's right-ee, you nincompoops!
Where's the logic in that?!
Why would a god need logic?
Vivi-chan-sama...
Otohime,
your dream was to live side-by-side with humans...
in a world of sunlight!
Give me back Shirahoshi! She's my friend!
Wait, Princess of Arabasta!
King Neptune!
Thank you! I'll never forget your kindness!
But I'm afraid I must let go of our dreams-jamon !
What?!
I'll crush them, and we'll return to our seafloor home-jamon !
No! Don't hit him!
If this is what happens on the surface,
I can never bring my people here!
No! This isn't how it is!
King Neptune! This is not humanity!
I'm sorry, Otohime!
Let's face them together!
Then maybe we can make a difference
for the future of the children on this island,
even just a small one!
{Even if we were to love them,
humans won't change!}Even if we gave them our love,
we can't change human nature!
I have to save Shirahoshi; forgive me!
How dare you defy me?
Kill him, Cipher Pol 0!
Wilco.
Out of my way!
Stop it, Great Knight Neptune!
Don't be hasty!
Father, no!
Let go of your hatred!
Ugh...
Who hit the Celestial Dragon?!
I-I have nothing to do with these hippos!
{I'm sorry...
As a fellow Celestial Dragon, I feel ashamed!}I'm so sorry!
As a fellow Celestial Dragon, I feel nothing but shame!
Please forgive us!
Is he a Celestial Dragon?!
Let go of the princess, you idiot!
My apologies, everyone!
This fool induced panic
where we should be peaceably socializing.
I assume you don't remember me, Neptune.
But I am indebted to the Ryugu Kingdom
and have patiently awaited this day.
The day you would arrive here!
That means... you're...
I'm the foolish Celestial Dragon...
who drifted down to
the Ryugu Kingdom a decade ago.
Hurry up and save me, you imbeciles!
– Kill him!
– Make him suffer!
Show him no mercy!
Don't do it!
You stupid fish!
Queen Otohime!!
The queen's been shot!
Queen Otohime!
Everybody, drop your guns!
Children are watching!
Otohime-sama!
It's just a scratch.
Why are you protecting him?
You know what he's done to us all!
I understand your anguish;
the pain runs deep for me too.
Our hearts ache, but...
we mustn't teach our resentment
of humans to our children!
They should get the chance to meet humans and decide for themselves.
Saint Donquixote Mjosgard
World Noble (Celestial Dragon)
The words of the late Queen Otohime...
gave me my humanity!
I would do anything to help your people!
King Neptune, it is an honor to see you again!
Cipher Pol! Leave this place!
The Holy Land
Mary Geoise
Pangaea Castle
The Room of Authority
The Five Elders
Supreme Council of the World Government
What would compel you to come all this way?
The Reverie is at hand.
Your position normally precludes any political entanglement.
We only made time because it's you.
Yes... and I appreciate that.
Let's hear it, then.
Guards, would you excuse us?
Yes, sir!
I need to talk to you about a certain pirate...
A Courtyard
Pangaea Castle
The crowd's really thinned out.
It's to be expected
after a mess like that.{After such a scene,
what do you expect?!}
No one wants to get involved in a scandal.
Wow!
How's that, Shirahoshi-san ?
The bruise is completely gone!
Thank you very much, Mansherry-chan-sama !
What a wonderful ability!
{I think you two are the biggest princess
and the smallest princess in the world!}I think we have both the world's
biggest and smallest princesses right here.
{I'm sorry that I was
afraid of you at first...}I admit you frightened me at first.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not bothered in the least,
Mansherry-chan-sama !
{I suppose all countries have both
good people and bad people.}It seems all countries
are comprised of both good and bad people.
The fishmen are no exception-jamon !
Thanks to you,
I kept my promise to Otohime.
No need to thank me, Neptune!
I want to return the favor
for saving me 10 years ago.
{During the seven days of the conference,
I'll look after Princess Shirahoshi.}For the duration of this conference's seven days,
I'll keep a close watch over Princess Shirahoshi.
If my status can help, I'll gladly make use of it!
I've been told that I should keep
my hands off of the Celestial Dragons,
{but could I kick their butts
if it's on your orders?}but if you gave the order,
could I kick their butts?
Y-Yes! If it's necessary to protect
the princess and her companions,
I'll take full responsibility!
I can't believe an oddball like him exists.
Vivi-sama !
I'm sorry, Vivi-sama.
I heard there was trouble.
I should've been at your side.
Rest easy, Pell. I'm all right.
Anyway, how's Papa?
{Cobra-sama is talking to Admiral Fujitora of the Navy,
the one who sent that letter.}Cobra-sama is talking
to the one who sent that letter:
{Cobra-sama is talking to Admiral Fujitora of the Navy,
the one who sent that letter.}Admiral Fujitora of the Navy.
They're conversing with King Riku of Dressrosa.
I see.
Pangaea Castle
Pangaea Castle has...
three gates outside of its main gate,
and all of them are guarded.
{One of those gates is
the Celestial Dragon Gate...}Most notable is the Celestial Dragon Gate,
which leads to the Land of the Gods
where the Celestial Dragons reside.
Stop! Who goes there?!
Queen Dowager Conney
Kingdom of Sorbet
Why, if it isn't Queen Dowager Conney of Sorbet!
The Land of the Gods is beyond this point.
You can't pass; it's dangerous to be here.
Please return to the castle.
It hurts-ee ! It's unforgivable-ee !
Damn that Mjosgard!
Saint Charlos! Please be calm!
You'll aggravate your wounds!
He can't get away with this-ee !
Open the gate!
What?! What's going on?!
Saint Charlos is injured!
He requires urgent care!
Right away!
Hurry up! He requires medical assistance!
Oh, Charlos! Are you okay?!
Saint Rosward
World Noble (Celestial Dragon)
I heard what happened.
I was on my way to pick you up-ee !
Saint Rosward!
F-Father !
Oh, look at you!
My dearest son!
Huh?
Where did the queen dowager go?
Damn that Mjosgard! I'll make him pay for this!
He's always been a strange man:
a Celestial Dragon who doesn't own a single slave!
Just like Homing who descended
to the lower realm 30 years ago!
The Donquixote family is full of lunatics-ee !
Father, that's...
Warlord Bartholomew Kuma
(Former Revolutionary Officer and Former King of Sorbet)
the invincible slave, Kuma!
That's right!
I finally got to rent him out-ee !
Bartholomew Kuma, known as “the Tyrant,”
was once a universally feared pirate.
Few have had as checkered a life as his.
Kuma, one of the Seven Warlords,
took on a special mission from the World Government
to eliminate the Straw Hats.
{Thus he suddenly emerged
in front of Luffy and the others...}He reached Thriller Bark just as Luffy
and the others pulled through their arduous battle.
Thirty-Six-Pound Phoenix!
So that's your ability?
I have the power to repel things.
I ate the Paw Paw Fruit
and became a paw pad man.
Are you truly willing to die for that man?
Right now, it's the only way
to save my crewmates!
My dream means nothing
if I can't protect my own captain.
Luffy will be king of the pirates!
He has good friends.
I should have expected no less
from your son, Dragon.
{Even though Kuma is a warlord,
he disobeyed the government's orders...}Despite Kuma's status as a warlord,
he disobeyed the government's orders,
and for some unknown reason,
he spared the Straw Hats' lives.
This is so exciting-ee !
Father finally got to rent the invincible slave Kuma!
It's advantageous to have
a warlord as a slave-ee !
You can hit him!
You could even stab him!
Yet he doesn't ever scream.
He's a top-class slave-ee !
Nice, Father ! I want one too-ee !
Ow, ow, ow! I'm gonna die-ee.
Please stay still, Charlos-sama !
Ow, ow, ow! He did a number on me-ee !
Oh, poor Charlos!
Let's get the world's greatest doctor
to look at you-ee !
I didn't expect I'd see him so soon!
Captain Jewelry Bonney
A Pirate of the Worst Generation
Bonney Pirates
Captain Jewelry Bonney
A Pirate of the Worst Generation
Bonney Pirates
My infiltration was a success.
I'll never forgive them!
Not ever!
Damn!
Don't get in a tizzy, Sabo!
Beneath the Land of the Gods, Home of the Celestial Dragons
You boys can all be so scary!
I can't help but get mad!
Our comrade is going through hell!
Our gentle Kuma!
It's unthinkable!
Calm down.
We get it. We all feel the same way.
We won't leave Kuma-san to this fate!
After all, he's one of the reasons we came here.
Having said that, even if we set him free,
he'll never return to his old self.
Let's not forget, Kuma-chan is a prime example
of the World Government's oppression!
Since Kuma-san is the former king
of a member nation,
they wanted to make
an example out of him as a warning.
A warning that no matter your strength or resolve,
this is how you end up if you disobey the gods!
The Celestial Dragons have CP-0
and Navy Headquarters in their corner.
If we fail and get caught–
No. Failure is not an option.
We either succeed...
or we die!
The Holy Land
Mary Geoise
It's finally time for the Reverie!
Pangaea Castle
The world is divided into four oceans...
EAST BLUE
NORTH BLUE
SOUTH BLUE
WEST BLUE
NEW WORLD
MARY GEOISE
by the continental wall, the Red Line...
and the deadly seas of the Grand Line and the New World,
which is where Luffy and his crew are adventuring.
The World Government is a truly massive organization.
Most countries in the world are members:
170 nations total!
Of those, 50 monarchs are chosen as representatives to assemble in the Holy Land every four years.
W-Where's my seat?!
– Finally.
– Yeah.
How's your country been?
You said it was ravaged by pirates four years ago?
Thanks to Fleet Admiral Sakazuki,
they were sent to Impel Down.
Speaking of pirates, there is one name I'm hearing often lately. I think it's...
Straw Hat Luffy, right?
He attempted to assassinate Big Mom,
and rumor has it that he's going after Kaido next.
Kaido?! {Does that mean Wano
will be in turmoil next?}Does that mean
Wano is next in line for disaster?
Wano is not affiliated with the World Government,
which effectively makes it a lawless land.
We don't even know if it operates as a country.
Is there nothing we can do?!
Sending the Navy would cost money.
Trouble seems to follow this
Straw Hat Luffy, wherever he goes.
You got that right!
What's so funny, Prodence?
Luffy-kun...
The position of chairman always rotates.
Who is it this time?
I am!
Everyone, it will be my honor.
Ballywood, huh?
Sounds good.
This should run smoothly, then.
Even if we have a full seven days,
we have so much to address.
This is the great conference
that determines the order of the world.
It is known as...
Well then... my fellow monarchs...
let us carefully discuss
the future of this beautiful world!
the Reverie!
And so the conference begins.
Apparently, King Cobra of Arabasta
is requesting an audience with us.
The Nefertari family...
was the only family of the First Twenty,
who stayed in the lower realm 800 years ago.
In a sense, they're traitors.
Has he noticed something?
Let's hope he doesn't make things complicated.
You could say the same
about the situation with Big Mom and Kaido.
It's been two years since the Summit War.
And yet, this maelstrom will not cease.
This world's equilibrium
cannot be maintained indefinitely.
The time has come for a great cleansing.
The Chamber of Flowers
Pangaea Castle
Imu-sama.
The Five Elders have arrived.
Have you discovered another light
to be erased from history?
Is it decided, then?
If so, you need only give us the name!
Editing:
Feeso
Timing:
Galaxy 9000
KaitouYahiko
Quality Assurance:
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Sewil
Zenef
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Translation:
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Special Thanks:
Randy Troy