New World
Minks' Guardians
Master Nekomamushi is quite a skilled navigator!
I'd expected no less from a man
who sailed with the pirate king!
Now, how much longer do we
have to wait by these ruins?
Until Master Nekomamushi returns with Marco!
I wonder if he'll come...
If Marco accompanies us to Wano,
he'll make for a strong ally.
After all, he's the First Division commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!
He's known as Marco the Phoenix!
I couldn't believe
he's Master's friend!
All right!
I'm gonna get a look at that man for myself.
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
Master told you to wait here
because you-gara have a scary face!
Hmph! Is he the kind of guy
who'd get scared by my face?!
That's not the point.
He said there is a peaceful village on the other side of the cave behind the waterfall...
A group of warriors like us
would terrify the locals.
True.
But Master Nekomamushi's
face is scarier than mine!
Yeah, when he gets mad.
– But he's cute when he smiles.
– For sure!
Onward to Wano
There!
Hey, wait!
Okay.
His treatment is complete.
He can go now-yoi.
He said you're better.
Can you stand, Tama?
Take your time.
My Flames of Restoration can only help others so much.
Marco
Former First Division Commander (Ship's Doctor)
Whitebeard Pirates
With this treatment, he should heal faster.
He'll be jumping around by tomorrow.
Wow! Marco is magic!
Isn't it great, Tama!
Wow! That was amazing!
You're okay now, Tama!
I said, “By tomorrow”!
Don't jump around now!
Thanks, Marco!
You're the best!
– Marco...
– Marco-san...
I've got a stiff neck...
Nekomamushi
Mink Tribe Guardians
Marco, at the mountain...
Marco, our crops...
Marco, my back hurts again!
– Marco-chan, my knees...
– Marco, can you help me study?
Marco, my brother is such a meanie!
All right-yoi.
I'll hear you out one by one-yoi.
This is the village Pops built-yoi...
Old man Whitebeard?
What do you mean?
Due to the extreme poverty in this area,
people here can't afford to pay the heavenly tribute
and join the World Government...
That's how it goes with
non-member nations.
Pirates and human traffickers can roam freely on these lawless islands.
They end up in ruins,
and more kids become unhappy orphans...
Pops was one of those kids-yoi.
He set out to sea at an early age.
Even after he became a pirate,
he still cared about this island...
He kept his identity a secret while funneling his dirty money and resources here...
for the rest of his life.
He didn't have a family back then,
and all his friends were gone,
but this was his home.
In this corrupt world,
there's no such thing as clean money!
Thank you-yoi...
After the Summit War,
we wanted to at least protect the things that were important to Pops.
So when Blackbeard came to invade our territory, the Payback War started.
But we were no match for Teach
after he got Pops' fruit.
He took everything from us...
I wanted to beat the hell
out of that ingrate...
Pops was...
Pops was actually quite cheap.
He always wanted other people's drinks...
but he never treated us!
Since he was funneling
his share of the loot to this village...
We all knew, though!
I see...
So this village is like a memento
that he left behind.
Yeah...
And...
Red Hair buried him nearby...
By the way,
did you hear about that warlord, Weevil? He's claiming to be Pops' son...
and attacking people connected to Whitebeard.
Oh yeah? Is it true?!
I don't know much about his love life,
but I guess Weevil's just after an inheritance.
I doubt they'll take my word
that there isn't anything left.
I figure that sooner or later he'll come after me and this place-yoi.
I see.
So you can't leave-meow.
Weevil's mother Bakkin used to be a pirate.
I know that 30 or 40 years ago,
she was on the same ship as Pops.
Then, maybe he's also a memento
that should be protected.
His behavior tells me otherwise-yoi!
You're right!
If you're going to see Straw Hat Luffy,
I want you to pass on a message, Nekomamushi.
Yeah, no problem.
– You said he's going to Wano, right?
– Yep.
What's his goal there?
To take down Kaido!
The emperor... Kaido?!
Luffy's looking to pick
a fight with Kaido?!
At Sea - The New World
Luffy! It says the Reverie has begun!
Monarchs from all over the world
are attending the conference at Mary Geoise!
Hmmm...
This time, all eyes are on the Ryugu Kingdom....
since they're participating for the
first time in two centuries!
Neptune-san and the brothers are there...
and it says that they were cheering for Shirahoshi at the Red Port!
So she came up to the surface!
Weakhoshi is getting stronger!
Captain "Straw Hat" Luffy
Straw Hat Pirates
Bounty: 1.5 Billion Belly
It seems like your grandpa was their escort.
Really?
They took a big step towards their dream
to relocate the Fishmen to the surface!
Vivi-chwai!
You became an even more beautiful princess!
Who could it be for?
Me?! Hey, is it for me?!
You're in my way!
Vivi!
It's Vivi!
It's been forever since we last saw her!
She's even more graceful and regal!
Oh, so this is Vivi-san.
If I get to see her someday,
I'd like to see her panties...
Like she'd show you!
Oh, these are photos are from a party in the palace courtyard...
Look at all the royals who attended with their guards.
I-If Dressrosa is participating...
There she is! Viola-chan!
Ugh! It's Wapol!
The old acorn guy is there, too!
What? Wapol?! Did he make a comeback?!
Rebecca! Sai! We know so many of them!
Of course. Royals from all around the world gather
at the Reverie to discuss issues!
Oh, maybe at the Reverie...
At the Reverie, the princesses that I know...
are gathering to discuss me!
Wouldn't that be nice?
Hey, look at this, Chopper!
Right here!
What is it, Chobro?
Doctorine!
Oh, is she still alive?
Hey!
Doctorine...
Hey! What are you doing, Chopper?!
– Don't cut it out!
– Wait? What!
– Give me back my princesses!
– What are you doing?!
Hey! I haven't read the other side yet!
It's full of holes!
Oh? Is this an article about Kaido?
Big Mom... What?! I can't read it!
Sanji-kun! Chopper!
Give those back to me!
No!
I'm glad everyone is doing well!
Once we sail around the world,
let's visit them again!
Yes! All in good order!
Anyway, Luffy-san, the transponder snail
still won't connect?
Oh, I forgot.
Hey! This is Luffy! Come in!
There's no response.
Whatever. Let's push on!
Wait, Luffy!
What's wrong?
The wind...
This cold wind... and I've never seen waves like this...
This can only mean trouble.
So this is the sea of Wano!
The wind is getting stronger as we draw closer,
and the waves are getting bigger!
It doesn't look like a normal wind-driven current.
The way it swells...
Plus it has that unusual current...
Look at the rough weather over there!
We wanna avoid a storm...
Shall we wait a little longer?
Hey! What are you talking about, Brook?!
Let's go to Wano now!
Luffy-san, why do you always drag
your crew into such obvious danger?
Actually, Brook...
Kin'emon actually warned me about this...
I shall properly explain through this snail thing.
The entire sea surrounding Wano
is always subject to terrible weather.
The water is rough
and the current is strong,
so it is difficult to even enter the country!
What?! The weather is always this bad?!
Then should we just go?!
That's what I'm saying. Let's go!
Not only does it have strong samurai
but it's also so perilous to enter...
It truly is an isolated country!
Let me think a little...
There must be a way to get through safely...
– What's that thing?!
– It's an octopus!
A giant one!
Why's an octopus here?!
– We're at sea! Octopuses live here!
– I know that, but...
When did it come on board?!
Hey! We're getting closer to Wano!
What?!
Who cares?! Go, Sunny!
To Wano!
Hey! Something's getting closer!
What?! What is it?!
It looks like a giant fish!
– Is it a shark?!
– A shark?!
Oh no! It's coming!
K-Koi...
Oh my, oh my!
It's a massive koi!
It's a school of koi?!
Why are there koi in the sea?!
They're freshwater fish!
How can they survive here?!
That doesn't matter now!
They're more monster than fish anyway!
Hey, Sanji? Are they tasty?!
Forget about these monsters!
Well, soaking them in hot and cold water...
makes a delicious arai-style sashimi.
Or simmer it in miso for koikoku.
They're also good as tempura or as amani.
All right!
We'll have a feast ready
for our reunion with Zoro and the others!
– Don't, Luffy!
– Koi have a lot of tiny bones!
Who cares?!
That's not important now!
Don't fight back!
Of course, it's fighting back!
Why are you always like this?!
Sanji-kun! You're also responsible for this!
Bring Luffy back!
Don't worry, Nami-san.
He'll be fine.
What?!
Instead, we should protect the ship!
The wind is strong!
Carrot, furl the sail!
– Okay!
– I'll help!
Look how clear the water is!
It's like the water of a mountain river!
I'd prefer it wasn't so clear!
The giant fish in the water scare me!
Wait, is this a river?!
Where are these koi heading?!
Hang on tight!
We're going with the flow!
Is Luffy still around here?!
What?!
Whoa-whoa, what is that?!
The river's flowing to the bottom of the waterfall!
How's that possible?!
I got it!
If this waterfall is the
reason that it's fresh water,
a massive spring should be up there!
Could Wano be up there?!
Up there...
What?! Whaaat?! How is that possible?!
Oh! Look at that!
– The koi are climbing up the waterfall!
– Why?!
Holy carp! Those koi are cool!
A sailing ship can't do that!
We'll sink under the waterfall!
Of course, we would!
Luffy!
Wow, those koi are so tough!
– This is no time for that!
– Luffy! She says this ship's gonna sink!
Okay, count on me!
What?!
Hang on tight!
I'm counting on you, koi!
You've got to be kidding!
Go!
All right!
Up we go!
What's wrong with the sea around Wano?!
It's so chaotic!
Hey! There's the shore!
It's a whirlpool!
Luffy! Let go of those koi!
No! They're my dinner!
Enough already!
Brook! Take the helm!
Okay!
It's no good! The current is too fast!
Damn! We're almost there!
We're not gonna make it this time!
Doctorine!
Hey? Where are my koi?
– That's not important now!
– What?
Oh no! We're getting sucked in!
Editing:
Feeso
Timing:
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control:
Feeso,
Galaxy 9000,
Grug,
Pepperjack
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Translation:
Crunchyroll,
Gaijin