Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Translation & initial timing
Yibis Fansubs
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Feeso
you'll have to be tough.
Soundtracking
Halee
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Video editing
Sewil
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
The King of Fishman Island
Invited to Ryuuguu Palace!
Quiet... Be quiet!
Now's our chance!  Hurry and get aboard the ship!
Everyone grab an oar, and prepare to get going!
The Fishman District
"Noah"
Hurry!  Hurry!
They could come chasing after us at any moment!
We can't stay on Fishman Island any longer.
We have to get past the Red Line, quickly!
Damn it!  I really wanted to see the Mermaid Café!
You'll have to give up on that, idiots!  Now stop talking and row!
Honestly... I can't believe this!
The Kraken was sleeping on the ocean floor,
so we managed to avoid it...
and we made it down 10 kilometers.
Pirate from South Blue
Crab-Hand Gyro
Bounty: 73,000,000 belly.
Then all those sea monsters surrounded us...
and we couldn't even fight back!
Join the fishmen or die?!
At that time, we didn't have any choice
but to join them!
We're moving farther and farther away
from the Mermaid Café.
Quit your crying!  Keep moving, men!
We'll be lucky if we escape with our lives!
Huh?  They ran away?
That's right, Boss.
So they ran away again -dosun?
They never learn, do they -dosun?
Member of the New Fishman Pirates
Dosun (Hammerhead Shark Fishman)
Zeo (Wobbegong Fishman)
Humans run away all the time.
Maybe I should just tear them apart?
Member of the New Fishman Pirates
Daruma (Cookiecutter Shark Fishman)
It's fine.
We can use them to set another example.
Captain of the New Fishman Pirates
Hody Jones
Great White Shark Fishman
Member of the New Fishman Pirates
Ikaros Much (Giant Squid Fishman)
In that case, should I take a shot at them -hi?
Not necessary, Ikaros.
Muhi, understood.
I'll go myself.
Huh?!
Prepare a bubble.
You can't take that many power drug pills all at once!
Alright, we're here!
This is my house!
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master!
Oh my!  It's Monsieur Pappagg!
Amazing!  Is it really him?
Yeah, I bet you're surprised now!
Out at sea, I'm nothing more than a stylish starfish.
But here on Fishman Island,
I am the president of the Criminal clothing brand.
A super-popular celebrity designer!
My brand is known all over the world,
and it's sold in stores in every country! { def: we had "all over the world" last line.  maybe reverse: "My brand is known in every counrty, and it's sold in stores worldwide!" }
Even the famous Doskoi Panda-
Oh, look over there!  What's that?
The Criminal Store is on the first floor.
Really?  Let's go have a look!
Caimie... Caimie...
Sure!
Hey!
Won't you listen... to my story...
Wait, dear customer, you're being unreasonable!
This is a very high-class brand we're selling here.
What's going on?
It sounds like the shopkeeper has a problem.
Perhaps someone's complaining?
Like I said, your prices are too high!  Though the clothes are cute.
That voice...
Alright, drop the price to 10,000 belly.
I can't do that, dear customer!
That's less than half the original price!
I knew it was her.  That complainer.
Hey, Nami!
Luffy!
Nami-chin!
Caimie!
Oh, Monsieur Pappagg, perfect timing.
We have a somewhat difficult customer here...
Oh!
Wait, you mean this is your store?
What's with the high prices?  Are you trying to rip me off?!
Monsieur!
Well, the brand's expensive.
I'm a popular designer, after all...
Give me a discount!
No, wait!
Don't be so hostile!
I owe you guys a lot for what you did two years ago!
You can have it for free!  Take whatever you like!
For free?  Really?!
Monsieur!  They emptied the whole store!
You really did go all out!
How nice for you.
Hmm?  What could that be?
There's a lot of noise coming from outside.
Monsieur!  Big news!
What is it?
H-He is here!
Why is he here?
That's...
Look up at the sky!
He's come down from the royal palace!
Jamon!  Jamon!
What's that?  A whale?
Why would he come to these lowly waters?
This is the first time I've seen him in person!
What's going on?  He doesn't even have an escort!
Unbelievable!  He decided to just suddenly come down here on his own?!
Maybe there's some kind of national crisis?!
Ruler of the Ryuuguu Kingdom
Sea God Neptune
Coelacanth Merman
Neptune.
Hoe
(His Beloved Whale)
That's one huge merman!
I much prefer the mermaids.
Hey, you guys!
What a shaggy old guy!
I'm telling you, you're being rude!
Kneel before him already!
That whale is so cute!
Does he have business with those humans?
Hey, Megalo.  You're sure it's these people -jamon?
Huh?  Didn't we meet that shark on the way here?
Hey, human with the straw hat, and his friends.
I have come...
to take you...
to see the Ryuuguu Palace -jamon!
Whaaat?!
R-R-R-R-R-Ryuuguu Palace?!
Ryuuguu Palace?
Near the Fishman District "Noah"
The depths
Hurry! Row Faster!
Or else they'll spot us!
We're caught in a deep sea current!  This is tough!
This is why we should've
had a paddle installed on the ship!
Do you realize how brutal the New World is?!
Captain, look!
There's something ahead of us!
Hody Jones!
N-No way!  He found us!
Huh?  He's...
What's that?  He's wearing handcuffs!
He disappeared!
Where did that damn bastard go?!
He pierced through the hull!
Take him down!  There's only one enemy!
I've fought against fishmen before.
How many trials do you think I've overcome to get this far?!
You're just a fish!
Don't underestimate humans, you fool!
Captain!
Damn it!
Man, this is a nasty thing we've gotten hold of -hi.
The power drugs... Energy Steroids.
A fishman's inherent physical strength is ten times that of a regular human.
However, your power is doubled again if you take a single Energy Steroid pill.
Twenty times the strength of a human.
Taking two of them multiplies it again!
The price for this dreamlike power is that it shortens your lifespan.
However, we will accept an early death in exchange for furthering our cause!
W-What is that bastard doing?!
What is he planning to do with the mast?!
Now I understand why he's wearing handcuffs!
He's showing us that he
doesn't even need his hands to sink us!
The life of Fisher Tiger was taken by humans!
The will of Arlong, too!
Our generation will end
Fishman Island's dark history of oppression!
We, the New Fishman Pirates, will end it!
Float into the New World.
Oh, goodness... You didn't kill them all, did you?
No, I need them alive.
Live with those wounds and show the world above...
what happened to you here beneath the sea!
Tell them who you met!
Tell the humans on dry land about our terror!
We will take the center of the world, Fishman Island,
from that pathetic Sea God, Neptune,
and drag you humans into the dark depths of the sea!
We'll teach you all that fishmen are the superior species!
A few hours ago...
Ryuuguu Kingdom, the Mermaids' Cove. {Yeah, the caption and narration say the exact same thing. Pretty unnecessary, huh?}
This thing is so tightly sealed.
I wonder what's inside it?
This would be some sort of chest if it was treasure.
Since it's just a barrel,
maybe it's filled with some high-class liquor?
It's... so hard... to open!
Oh, that's quite enough.
Opening it up this much is more than sufficient!
What?!  There was someone inside of it?!
No way!
Thanks a ton!
I'm really grateful, my dear mermaids!
Don't try to run away, now!
Quick!  Into the water!
It's too late for that!
I'm... sinking...
It's a swamp!
How'd it get in this rocky area?! {Gil: Only just on the screen long enough for me to read. A good way of shortening the line isn't coming to mind right now...}
You can't break free from this bog!
It's bottomless!
I'm a Devil Fruit User.
A swamp-man, who ate the Swamp Fruit!
The more you struggle...
No!
...the faster you sink!
Help!
Please, don't scream.  I'm not gonna kill you.
Somebody-
Didn't I just tell you not to do that, you idiot?!
Ishilly!
I just need you to go to sleep for a little while!
My body is bottomless...
How much do they pay for mermaids again?
I seem to recall the starting price at auction being 70,000,000 for one of them.
So with three, that's...
I owe the Straw Hats one for this!
Thanks to them, I was able to enter Fishman Island without registering...
And I can hunt high-class mermaids freely!
This place is a treasure island!
Ryuuguu Kingdom Port Town
"Coral Hill"
The Straw Hat Pirates? {Gil: Originally "The crew of the pirate Straw Hat?" but that sounds way awkward to me.}
Were they the ones who kidnapped the girls from the Mermaids' Cove?
No, I didn't say that.
They seemed like nice people...
And besides, they're Caimie's friends.
They may have threatened her.
No way.
If we look at the facts,
the only ones who were there at the time...
were us guards, the girls,
the gang from the Fishman District who were beaten...
and the Straw Hats.
And we have nobody who can attest to what they were up to after they disappeared.
Humans always have a reason to kidnap mermaids.
In human society, young mermaids are sold at high prices.
Even so, you can't just accuse them based on guesswork.
Do you have any idea how many humans have put up a nice front, then kidnapped mermaids in the past?!
Prince Fukaboshi.
And Madame Shyarly,
about what you were saying earlier...
Did you really see a future like that?
That the pirate Straw Hat Luffy
is going to destroy Fishman Island?
Madame Shyarly, have some water.
Yes, I saw it.
That is what I saw, no doubt about it.
Even we at Ryuuguu Palace have heard how accurate your predictions are.
This is quite a dilemma.
We were going to thank them for saving our sister's pet.
But now, even if this prediction is unconfirmed, we can't just let them roam free.
We need to capture them.
Ryuuguu Kingdom
Elite District: "Gyoverly Hills"
They're gone...
Who were they, anyway?
To think that King Neptune would personally invite them to the Ryuuguu Palace.
Don't fall off!
Neptune!
What's wrong with you, old geezer?
Those yells are ridiculous.
Quit being so rude!
Straw, you're scary!  You're honestly scaring me!
That shark there, Megalo...
He's my daughter's pet,
and she cares a lot about him -jamon.
When Megalo didn't come back, she wouldn't stop crying.
So he'd been attacked by the Kraken...
Megalo (The Mermaid Princess' Beloved Shark)
That was really dangerous,
and I'm thankful that you saved him -jamon.
Well, it was just a coincidence,
but yeah, good thing we managed to save him.
So he's the Mermaid Princess' pet?
Oh?  Pappagg-san, did you not once say that
you and the Mermaid Princess were best friends?
Oh, so that was a lie?
I-Is it really alright?
For us to come along to the Ryuuguu Palace.
He did say "Your friends are quite welcome too -jamon", so what's the problem?
To tell you the truth, I sent my sons out to fetch you,
but they still haven't returned -jamon.
So I decided to go myself.
After all, I too am looking forward to the feast, and wish to start eating soon -jamon!
Ah, I forgot to mention, but one of your friends
has already been taken there.
Huh?
He's a swordsman.  He began drinking already.
These feasts are more fun if everyone's there.
What a selfish man.
I believe his name was...
Zoro, huh?
That's Zoro, alright.
Zori!
It's Zoro!
The guards are looking for your companions and will invite them all to the castle, so don't worry -jamon.
Nami, do you know where they went?
With this many people around, I might be able to find information sooner than I'd thought.
Huh?
I'm most curious about where I can find the relatives
of my shipwright master.
This is Tom-san's homeland.
I have some things I want to investigate as well.
You too?
Since ancient times, Fishman Island has been an island rich with folklore.
I'm sure another one lies here...
A valuable fragment of history.
So we split up again.
You haven't had any trouble, right?
Well, you could say we have,
and you could say we haven't...
By the way, old man. {Kijou: the word Nami uses for Neptune is, rather than 'old man', endearing. It's what you'd use for your grandad or someone similar to that position. It's a very friendly (but very casual) term. So 'gramps' or something similar would probably suit better, since at least to me 'old man' sounds a bit rude.} { def: gramps works for me, so long as this isn't the same word that Luffy uses when we say "old man" }
That's the Sea God, Neptune-sama you're talking to!
We're ten thousand meters under the sea, so
why is it so bright in the area around Fishman Island?
It's not that the area surrounding Fishman Island is bright.
This is the only place on the ocean floor where the sun shines, so fishmen started living here long ago.
That's how Fishman Island was founded.
The roots of the Treasure Tree, Eve,
reach down to these depths.
They transfer sunlight directly from the surface
to the bottom of the sea.
Transfer sunlight?
So you are saying this tree has glowing roots
that reach ten thousand meters below the sea?
Indeed.  The scientists keep making new theories for how this can be,
but it is a mysterious tree that receives light at the surface and emits it from its roots -jamon. {Oh look, Neptune has taken a page out of the Monkey D. Luffy-book of explaining supernatural phenomena.}
And its respiration supplies air to the sea floor as well.
So it's like the big boss of the
Yarukiman Mangroves on Sabaody?
Hey, shaggy old guy, I'm hungry!
Hey you!
We are almost there.
That is the entrance -jamon.
Ding-dong.
Yes?
It's me -jamon.
That phrase... Y-Your Majesty!
I will lower the path for you immediately!
Keep your bubbles on tight -jamon.
Now, let us go.
Neptune!
I'm really looking forward to getting to the Ryuuguu Palace!
Here we are -jamon.
Royal Palace of the Ryuuguu Kingdom
Ryuuguu Palace
Amazing!  This is so cool!
It makes Pappagg-san's mansion look as small as a flea.
Don't compare them!
What a beautiful castle!
King Neptune has returned!
I was wondering where he'd gone.
Open the gate!
Opening the gate!
Welcome back, Your Majesty!
This castle looks like a lot of fun!
It is my palace -jamon!  Make yourselves at home!
For crying out loud!  You did it again!
You just went into the kingdom on your own without considering your position again!
You can't just go down to the surface without even bringing an escort!
What are we to do?
I will be more careful in the future -jamon.
He got scolded.
If something happened to you, it'd be too late for apologies!
Do you even realize the situation our country is in?!
Never mind all that, look!
I have brought the people who saved Megalo
when he was being bullied by the Kraken -jamon!
Now, welcome our guests!
Uh, what is Princess Shirahoshi doing?
Well, Your Majesty, it seems to have happened again...
What?!  This is all because you didn't
watch over the princess to keep her calm!
You imbeciles!
And while that was going on...
you just disappeared without a trace!  Can't you see that you made everyone worry, Your Majesty?!
In the first place...
I promise I will be more careful in the future -jamon.
He got scolded again.
I sincerely apologize for bringing this up when you've just brought guests here...
Ryuuguu Kingdom  Minister of the Right
(Seahorse Merman)
but we have important business to discuss.
Yes, Prince Fukaboshi...
Ryuuguu Kingdom  Minister of the Left
(Catfish Merman)
contacted us just a moment ago.
What are we to do?
Fukaboshi, you say?  What happened?!
You see...
I wonder how long they intend to ignore us?
Huh?  Where'd Luffy go?
He was just here!
He can't stay still even for a minute, can he?
What's he thinking, wandering around on God's land?!
Yep, it's this way...
The smell of tasty food!
Maybe this is where they're holding the feast?
They said Zoro was already here, didn't they?
Still, that is one huge, thick and solid-looking door!
The wall looks really sturdy too.
They're like the walls in Impel Down!
What kind of delicious food do they have inside?!
It's pitch black in here...
So this isn't where the feast is being held?
But they do have some food that smells really nice here!
So is this the food storage room, then?
Well, whatever!  I'll have some!
My hunger is at its limit!
What's this?
There are corals wherever I go on this island, huh?
What's this?  It's so soft...
Huh?  Was that someone's voice?
This coral feels like pudding!
Is somebody there?!
What is it?!
What are you doing on someone else's body?!
Who might you be?!
Princess of the Ryuuguu Kingdom
Princess Shirahoshi (Giant Whiting Mermaid)
What?!  It was a huge person... No, a mermaid?!
Y-You've come to take my life too, haven't you?
B-But I'm not afraid of you!
After all, I'm the daughter of Neptune...
So I'm not...
I'm not...
Somebody!
Father!  Big brother!
H-Hey, hey... I didn't do anything!
Seriously, what is wrong with you?!