Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Shaking of the Kingdom!
Luffy vs. Jinbe!
That was ten years ago.
Fukaboshi, Ryuuboshi and Manboshi...
Those three, together with the King and Princess,
have been reaching out to the citizens using monitors.
Thanks to their efforts,
we've regathered many of the signatures.
This is the battle against discrimination
that has been fought on this island for sixteen years.
And it's the reason why the Fishman Pirates
did what they did.
Arlong, the one who caused
so much suffering in your homeland,
was like a little brother to me.
We were planning to go after him
if he ever tried anything...
but Arlong bribed the Navy in the area and made sure that reports of his actions never reached Navy HQ.
Cut open your stomach!
Sanji...
You can apologize with your death!
It still wouldn't be enough for me to forgive you,
but at least it might give Nami-san some peace!
Stop, Sanji-kun.
But, Nami-san... Think of what they did to you!
That has nothing to do with him.
After hearing his story,
it's clear that he meant no harm.
I will accept any punishment, if it makes you feel better-
Don't!
Don't.  Arlong is the one I hate.
In any case, I'm glad you're not the mastermind behind the Arlong Pirates.
I mean, you're Luffy's friend, aren't you?
It's true.  I suffered a lot because of the Arlong Pirates,
but in that spiral of pain, I met many good friends too.
All of that made me who I am now.
I won't hate you just because you're a fishman.
So don't go apologizing for my life.
I don't regret it.  I'm having a lot of fun now!
So, whoever the culprit is...
please don't be angry for me.
Don't tell the people on our island anything!
Not about the tragedy that befell us,
nor about our anger toward the humans.
Don't let it get to you, Jinbe.
You grew up in the Fishman District together.
You're like brothers.
No matter what happens,
you wouldn't be able to kill him.
I don't deserve such kind words.
I am in your debt.
Nyuu- Nami!
Boss Jinbe-sama...
I totally understand
how tough it must be for you, Bro!
You're a real man, Jinbe!
Tiger... Otohime... I love you all!
Shut the hell up, Franky!
He was suffering so much...
Whaaat?!
Hey, wake up!
I sure slept well...
So, Jinbe...
What happened to the robber that Wimp's mom caught?
Did you sleep through the whole thing?!
That was the opening of the story!
Really?
Yeah!
You there... Your name is Shirahoshi, isn't it?
N-Nami-chin!  She's royalty!
You can't just address her as "You"!
Yes...
Please forgive me.
Remembering my mother made me cry.
She sounded like a wonderful mother.
Yes!
Your name is Nami-chin-sama, right?
Your Highness!  Nami-chin is just her nickname.
The -chin isn't actually part of her name.
This is the first time I've met you,
but it feels like I've known you since childhood.
I feel so relieved!
Really?  Maybe it's because our circumstances are kind of similar?
Well then, sorry for taking so much of your time.
First, we have to find out what's happening
at Ryuuguu Palace.
Hody and his crew attacked.
His Majesty and the guards have been captured.
Four of your companions are missing, and we don't know what they're doing.
That's all the information we have at the moment.
Nyuu- Jinbe-san.
If things are going according to Hody's plan, even worse things are happening around the country now.
You know what Hody is planning?!
I always suspected that he was planning something in the Fishman District after leaving the army...
but he never gave me an opportunity to find out what it was.
Yeah, I know his plan.
Hody hates humans even more than Arlong-san does.
It's like he's grown up by feeding on the anger and hatred of the fishmen.
But, he's clearly different from Arlong-san.
Arlong-san looked down on humans,
but he'd never hurt his fellow fishmen.
But with Hody...
Even if you're just a fishman who wants to live in peace with humans...
he will mercilessly attack you!
The World Council Meeting only takes place every four years and will happen this year, right?
We've gathered a lot of signatures.
This was going to be the year when
King Neptune finally let the world know...
that Fishman Island wants to emigrate to the surface!
Don't tell me...
Hody wants to prevent that from happening?!
No, even more than that...
What is that?!
A gigantic Snail Phone?!
That's...
A Projector Snail!
What's it doing here?
Look!  The monitor is turning on!
It's projecting something onto the bubble layer.
That's...
It's him!
Nami-san, you know that guy?
Nyuu- Hody...
Huh?  That's him?
Hacchin!
To all citizens of Fishman Island...
Can you hear me?
I am the captain of the New Fishman Pirates,
from the Fishman District...
Hody Jones!
Okay, next!
Next!
You won't step on it, eh?!
Please forgive us, Queen Otohime.
They'll kill me if I don't do this terrible thing.
I have no choice.
I'm so sorry, Queen Otohime.
Okay, you pass.  Next!
This is no fun.
I didn't think that everyone would step on her.
No one respected Queen Otohime after all!
Daruma-san, Captain Hody is starting his broadcast.
Huh?
So he's in charge of all this?
He's the one who's making us step on the fumi-e?
Hey, isn't he the one that shot Otohime-sama's killer
right after her assassination?
That's right!  That's Hody Jones!  There's no doubt!
Wasn't he a soldier in the Neptune Army?
I have an announcement for everyone on Fishman Island.
This country will soon be destroyed.
And then it will be reformed under a new king...
who will be me!
What the hell is he saying?
What's he trying to pull?!
There's no way that'll happen!
Where is he broadcasting from?
Where is the King?
And didn't I hear something about
the Straw Hat Pirates occupying the palace?
What's happened to our country?!
And the new Fishman Island that I rule over
will have absolute laws.
At this moment,
people are coming here from the Fishman District.
They will be the new citizens of this land.
They hate the humans, just like we do.
They are comrades who wish to change this island,
just like we do.
What?  They're coming here?
Those lawless ruffians are going to live here?
I'm sure that most of you saw
the death of your beloved Queen Otohime.
Queen Otohime had worked tirelessly in order to create a connection between us and the humans.
Who killed her?!  It was the humans themselves.
Even if you trust them and meet them halfway, humans will just stab you in the back!
Why can't you understand that?!
That bastard...
You've been led astray by the Neptune Family.
They are pushing you down a path that leads to death.
Their naive ideals are just
pretty words that can never come true!
Wishful thinking that will lead you to destruction!
No!
Look at this.
Father!
Your Majesty!
Even the once-great Knight Neptune has fallen to old age.
There is no future for this island
if an old man is left on the throne.
I guess that it's really our fault that the King was captured...
What?
Or Zoro's fault, really.
What did you do before you came here?!
Ah!  B-B-B-But Boss Jinbe!
There was a misunderstanding, and the Neptune Army
attacked Nami-chin and her friends.
It's time to end...
the old Ryuuguu monarchy.
Three hours from now, in Gyoncord Plaza,
we will cut off the head of this worthless king.
You've probably figured it out already, but I'm in Ryuuguu Palace.
We found something interesting here.
It's the piece of paper that Queen Otohime
risked her life to get from the Celestial Dragons...
ten years ago.
If it was destroyed,
they'd have no reason to ever give us another one.
Also... we have this huge box.
It contains the signatures
of over half of the subjects of this country.
Surely my eyes are deceiving me.
How could there be so many fools who think we should kiss and make up with the humans?!
Everyone who has written their name here
is opposed to my new kingdom.
In other words, this is a list of traitors.
You can quit using the fumi-e.
Anyone can lie and step on her face to pass that test.
But these signatures
show who supports me and who opposes me.
They are undeniable!
Let's start disposing of these people, one by one.
And finally...
The Straw Hat Pirates!
I have something good to show you.
I know you're somewhere on this island watching this.
These humans earned the wrath of all fishmen by destroying the ambitions of Arlong's crew!
Zoro!  Usopp!  Brook!
What the hell're those guys doing?
How could they have been captured?!
Do it.
Yes, Sir!
What?  What?  What's happening?
We're so high up!
I hear something...
A rumbling sound...
It's water!
Around the same time that we execute the King,
this room will finish filling with water.
Such inferior creatures.
Humans die from something as trivial as this.
Straw Hat Luffy, with a bounty of 400 million beli!
The heads of you and your companions
will serve as warnings to the humans on the surface.
Well, it's time to start cleaning up
the old Ryuuguu Monarchy.
We're going to leave behind the weakness of our past,
setting course for a strong future!
In three hours,
this country will be reborn as a proud Fishman Island!
How could this happen?
We won't let him do this!
Damn it!  The water keeps pouring in!
And I just finished drying out too, Usopp-san.
I don't want to be submerged in seawater again.
Neither do I!
Do something.  Anything!  Zoro-kun!
Sure thing.  Now then...
Get me out of these chains.
Got it!
Here it comes.
Chains, fall off... Chains, fall off...
Chains, fall off... Fall off chains!
Fall off!
It's no good... I don't have enough faith.
But did you see it?
The look on their faces when I started moving...
Ding!  Ding!  Ding!
We have a winner!
It's... moving!
That's right.  I'm "Nothing but Bones" Brook!
Who's fault do you think it is that we ended up like this?!
Save me!  They'll kill me!
Ah, but I'm already dead.
Well, Nami and her group managed to get out, right?
We'll be fine if she manages to
get Luffy and the others.
And what'll you do if he doesn't come?!
Robin'll be all...
"I wonder if Nami was killed and eaten
by the deep-sea fish."
That's Robin, alright!
This is a bit different from
the other poneglyphs I've seen so far.
It's almost as if it's a letter... or a written apology?
Who are you apologizing to?
Who are you... Joyboy?
Did they just say that my bounty's at 400 million?!
When did it go up?
As if this is time for that!
They've picked a fight with us, no doubt.
After the great war in Marineford,
your fame shot up through the roof.
Once it surpasses 300 million,
it'll take a lot for them to raise it again.
Well, if they want a fight then we'll give them one!
Hey, wait, Luffy-kun!
Father...
Father!
Megalo!
We have to go save him!
Hold on a second, Princess Shirahoshi!
Stop, Megalo!
Wait!
Boss Jinbe-sama... But I...
Both you and Luffy,
you need to stop for a second.
Princess, I also think it's better if you don't go.
Hachi-sama.
In all of Ryuuguu Kingdom,
Hody's biggest fear right now is...
Princess Shirahoshi's power.
Even if he recreates Fishman Island
the way he wants it,
it will all be destroyed if the Sea Kings attack.
He took the King hostage to use him as a shield.
So in other words, their true goal is Shirahoshi-chan?
Nyuu- Hody isn't planning to
capture the Princess and use her power.
He fears the very existence of the power.
So he teamed up with Vander Decken, who wants the Princess's life.
Hody plans to get rid of everything that stands in his way.
Yeah, that's right.
If the Princess goes to the plaza it'll be just what he wants.
I've heard the prophecy about my power before,
but I've never been able to talk with the Sea Kings before.
I don't even know if I really have the power or not.
Either way, Hody will definitely want to finish you off.
But we can't let Hody find out
that you can't control the power.
We want him to be afraid of it.
You done yapping?
Alright then.
Shark!  Take me to Ryuuguu Palace!
Sanji, I'm leaving Wimp in your care.
Yes!  Leave it to me!
Didn't I tell you to wait, Luffy-kun?
Huh?
You mustn't fight with Hody!
Why're you trying to stop me?
Is it because we're human?
Don't include yourselves, that just complicates things!
That's right!  It can't be you!
The fishmen who don't hate humans already may wind up changing their minds!
Leave this to me.
Jinbe!  My friends have been captured!
If I don't do something, they'll be in trouble!
Luffy-chin...
Straw Hat...
You still don't understand, after everything I said?!
I'm going.
You don't understand a damn thing!
Blah blah blah... shut up!
If you want me to stay, then try to stop me!
Luffy...
It was foolish to think you'd listen to me, even after we've fought side by side.
I had almost forgotten...
that you are his brother.
Since you don't intend to stay here,
there's no other way to do this.
Luffy-chin... Boss Jinbe...
Luffy!  Jinbe!  Hang on!
What are you two doing?!
I'm gonna go to Ryuuguu Palace, rescue my friends,
and send that Hody guy flying!
And I'm telling you not to be rash!
Hey, now!  Why are you fighting?
Stop it, you two!
Luffy-sama... Boss Jinbe-sama...
Shark, give me a ride!  To Ryuuguu Palace!
I'm telling you, wait!
Get out of my way!
Fishman Karate
Shark Tile True Fist
What?!
Luffy-chin!
Luffy-sama!
T-That hurt...
What?!  It worked!
I thought physical attacks couldn't hurt a rubber man!
The true power of Fishman Karate
lies in its ability to control all water that it hits.
It creates a shockwave, from the water in the air
to the water inside one's body.
All living creatures are clusters of water.
Even a rubber man can't escape it!
You bastard!
I will not let you go, Luffy!
Is that all you got out of your training?
I'm not done yet!
That's enough.
Robin!
Robin-chwan!
Hey, get out of the way, Robin!
Who are you?!  Move!
Robin-chan is in trouble!
Huh?
Robin-chan...
You mustn't fight.
I don't know the circumstances here, but aren't you on the same side?
Huh?!  How did Robin get to the forest?!
Well then, here I go.
Hey, wait a second!
Explain what the hell is going on!
You can even do that now?
Oh yes, it happened...
back when I was touring the world as the Soul King.
Booooone!
Wait, whaaaaaat?!
What is going on?!
This technique even lets me slip through walls.
What do you think I did?
If you are a man, I am sure you already understand.
I'm so jealous! Zoro, he's making me jealous!
Shut up!
It's time to leave for the execution stand.
Should we leave someone behind
here in Ryuuguu Palace, Boss Hody?
No, there's no need.
Ryuuguu Palace is impenetrable.
Just leave behind a few gatekeepers
to open the gates when we return.
We can't have the King
locked out of his own castle, after all!
Yeah, you've got a point there!
You're no King -jamon!
You can't win the hearts of the people with violence!
You've only got a few hours left to live.
Spout whatever nonsense you'd like until then.
My wound is aching.
The wound from that arrogant swordsman.
The painkillers are wearing off.  Give me the Energy Steroids.
S-Sure...
The pain is gone.
Will he really be alright, taking that many?
G-Good question...
Boss, what about those three Straw Hats?
They're just humans.  Leave them alone, and they'll drown before long.
Even if someone tries to save them,
it's impossible to break into the palace.
More importantly... How are things going
with the new citizens from the Fishman District?
No problems at all.
They've already started to move in.
I see.  They'll have places to live soon enough.
Many people will leave the country or be killed.
They can just use their houses.
This will become a fine country,
where everyone despises the humans!
I have found our light of hope!
Everyone seems to have disappeared for some reason,
and the palace looks empty...
but Pappagg-san has been left behind!
Then, Brook.  Ask Pappagg to
look for the keys to these chains right away.
Oh, and the cage, and the room-
Hang on, idiot.
I just need one sword.  Bring my swords here.
I'll cut through all our obstacles.
Whoa, you're too reliable!
I have arrived, with a "bone"!
Ghost!
Wait!
Ghosts are so scary!
Pappagg-san, it's me!
We're in a hurry!
Umm, get the key... No, a sword!
Umm, listen...
Stay away from me!
Noooooo!
Don't be like that!  Listen to me!
Wait!
Just think about this, Luffy.
What do you think will happen
if you just go wild on Fishman Island?
Whenever fishmen have tried to open their hearts to humans, the humans have only worked against them.
"Humans are brutal creatures."
"Humans discriminate against fishmen and hate them."
The harsh reality of the situation is that history has taught fishmen to see things in a negative light.
Even in the case of Arlong,
more than a few of us think that humans hunted him down just because he was a fishman.
And if you, the very same people who defeated Arlong,
were to attack Hody as well, what would happen?
Even if you saved Fishman Island from this crisis...
they'd see you attack Hody,
who is taking a stand against humanity.
It will just remind them of Fishman Island's history,
and convince them that things will never change.
So you say, but Jinbe...
It's natural for us to want
to save our captured companions,
and if we leave things the way they are,
then Fishman Island will fall under Hody's control.
We've got many friends here on this island.
Hey, Hachi.
You seem determined not to tell us
who gave you those wounds,
but you also said...
that Hody will even attack fishmen
who want to be friends with humans, right?
You...
were attacked because you stood up for us, weren't you?
Hachi...
Hacchin...
Is that true?  Did Hody and his men do this to you?!
Well...
Jinbe.  To Luffy, knowing that this is your country
just gives him another reason to fight.
We can't just leave this island behind.
We have a reason to fight.
After all...
Caimie-chan is here!
Shirahoshi-chan is here too!
Indeed!  This country is the Mermaid Paradise
of my dreams!
Get out of my way, Jinbe.
I said I'm going, so I'm going.
I will not let you!  Leave this to me!
Why, you!  I'll just have to send you flying and then go!
If you won't listen to what I say,
I'll stand up to you as many times as I must!
What was that?!
Stop it, you two!