Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
You say you'll protect them all?
Don't make me laugh!
You sure have a big mouth, Straw Hat.
Damn that Hody.  He's even willing to attack Decken.
Run away, Shirahoshi!
Draw the Noah away from the island as far as possible!
It's too late.
Too late?  What's he talking about?
Wait... Didn't he just take out Decken?!
If Decken dies or loses consciousness inside the Noah...
...then his ability will stop working right above Fishman Island.
The Noah... will fall...
right onto the island!
What're ya doin'?
Dat hurt!
You damn Manjuu-bastard.
Manjuu: A rotund Japanese pastry
How dare you...
knock Nami-san over
with the shockwave from your fall!
Payback time!
This is payback...
for the shockwave that hit Nami-san! {...Say, does anyone else think this is an exceptionally petty grudge he's holding? "YOU FELL NEAR NAMI AND KNOCKED HER OVER, YOU ARE SO GOING TO DIE!!!!!!!"}
Oh, crap!
Beware of the shockwave, Nami-san! { def: they're saying shockwave way too much.  maybe just "Look out" or something similar here? }
Another shockwave?  Give me a break!
Don't let your guard down!  Watch out!
She made something fly out of her staff earlier!
What now?!
Is she a witch?!
How rude!  I'm not a witch!
Call me an enchantress instead!
Granted, it's not really magic.  Just calculated science.
C-Clouds?!
Thundercloud Rod
Hot!
Help us!
Stay away!  I'll turn into a fried squid -hi!
Was it that woman's fault -hi?!
Hey, Ikaros.
The man in the black suit
became concerned when he thought she was hurt.
She is most likely the Straw Hat Pirates' weak point.
What?!
I'll go hold her still.
When I do, finish her off with your spears!
Roger that -muhi!
Just leave me alone now,
unless you want to be roasted!
What?!  My legs won't move!
I'm gonna make you into fried squid -hi!
W-W-Wait a second!
Why won't my feet move?!  Somebody!
Nami-san!  Oh, that's right!
Take this!  My Fried Squid Spear!
May I see your panti-
No way!
Is this a friend of yours?
He's gonna be dried up!
Become a fried squid!
Pardon?
What's happening -hi?
My spears should drain the water from your body,
and dry you up -hi!
Hey, Dried Squid Spears!  Why?!
What's wrong?!
Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!
Umm...
I dried out a long time ago.
There's no way that could possibly be true!
Hey!  Aren't there any worthy opponents around?
Are you alright?
Who are you -hi?!
It's me!
That doesn't help -hi!
What?!  You don't recognize this super robot?!
Hmm?  Now that I look at you,
I see that you're one of the commanders!
You must have backbone, right?!
I may be a squid, but I'm also a fishman!
I do have a backbone!
What?  You're a squid, yet you have a backbone?
Sympathy!
He didn't mean it literally.
Hey, skeleton.  Step to the side real quick.
What?  Why is that?
Your feet!  Your feet!
What about my feet?
You're standing on him!  Standing right on him!
Huh?!  Who's this guy?!
He's the reason why I couldn't move?!
Um... Who might you be?
How do you like it?!
What?
The power of my headbutt to the bottom of your foot!
My attack will slowly begin to take effect.
What?!
He refuses to admit that he got stepped on!
My apologies for stepping on your face!
Don't say that!
My attack's name is...
Chou Ashiura Zutsuki!
Super Sole Headbutt!
He gave it a name!
Where'd you go, you damn coral-head?!
I'll chew you to pieces!
There's no way I can lose underground!  I move wherever I want!
Daruma-san!
Don't fill the ground with too many holes!
We're gonna get stuck!
Alright!
Chopper!  Are you done?
Come out over here!
Fool!  He's let his guard down -dogon!
I'll flatten him!
Be squashed and die -zugan!
Usopp, duck!
Horn Cannon: Eleven
Nice going, Chopper!  Did you connect the tunnels?
Yeah, it's done!
Alright!  Here we go!
Skull Bomb-Grass
How'd you like that taste of my strength?!
We fought against enemies who dug holes back in Alabasta!
Our experience won this fight!
Yeah!
Damn you, coral-monster!
Was that you?!
I'll show you my terrifying power!
When it comes to power, I've got an ace up my sleeve!
I'll chew that nose to pieces!
Why don't you try?!  Back me up, Chopper!
H-Hey, I need backup!
Chopper?
Help me.
Are you alright?
I'll treat your wounds right away.
Darling!  Stay awake!
Daddy!
Hurry and treat their wounds!  Quickly!
Damn Hody.
He even attacked defenseless citizens!
Is the princess... alright?
I don't know.
But I'm sure...
she's still fighting for us!
Madame Shyarly.
What will happen to Fishman Island?
Will it really be destroyed?!
I have to take it away.  Far away!
You sure are desperate.
Away from the island...
Noah!
Shirahoshi!
If the Noah falls, it's all over!
Oh no!  She can't hear us!
You mustn't swim straight up!
To the side!  Move to the side!
So they've caught on?!
Shirahoshi!
Brother!
Ryuuboshi!
Don't interfere with my plan!
Brother!  Hang in there!
If Decken's power doesn't stop working here, then what was the point of killing him?
So that's it!
If we don't move, then the ship will crash down onto Fishman Island and everyone there!
After Weak-hoshi worked so hard to draw it away from the island!
Bro-hoshi!  Let's go to Weak-hoshi!
Right!
Shirahoshi!
Weak-hoshi!
I won't let you go!
Fishman Island will be crushed, along with all of its people!
Straw Hat, all your companions are sure to die as well!
Are you alright?!
Shirahoshi!
Swim to the side!
Weak-hoshi!
Damn mermaid!
How insolent!
Shirahoshi heard us!
She's swimming to the side!
You shouldn't have done that!
I won't let you!
Wait!
Let me go!
I ain't letting go!
Damn it...
Noah!  Come this way!
I'm losing my grip...
Noah!  Follow me!
Let's go!
Right!
Damn Decken!  Just die already!
Damn it.
That bastard, Hody.  I won't let him get away with this!
Noah!  I'm right here!
The ship... It's starting to move to the side!
Great!  Keep going, Weak-hoshi!
Shirahoshi!
Go!
My left hand's target...
Hody, it's you!
Remember that!
Until you die...
I will always be hunting you, body and soul!
Noah!
Shirahoshi!  Just a little further!
If it moves too far, all of this was pointless!
All the way to the ends of hell!
The Noah... is falling!
Just in time!
Fishman Island...
is still in danger!
It can't be!
Victory is mine!
So he finally bought it.
Now Vander Decken's power will stop working,
and the Noah will crash down onto Fishman Island!
Die!  Straw Hat Pirates!
You fools have gotten in the way of my retribution.
Fishman Island's going to...
...be destroyed.
One way or another, we have to stop the ship.
Straw Hat!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't you?
That bastard.
If the Noah crashes into Fishman Island,
then it's all over.
Our kingdom and the centuries-old mission
to protect the Noah.
Listen, my sons.
That Ark, the Noah, isn't just a historical ruin.
A long time ago, hundreds of years past,
we exchanged promises with a very important person.
That ship has been waiting patiently
on the ocean floor to carry out that promise.
The ship has not yet completed its mission.
And now, even the techniques used to build the ship
have been lost in time.
Until the promised day comes,
we mustn't allow the Noah to get a single scratch!
We understand, Father.
We will find out what's causing it to move
and deal with it appropriately.
We have to save our kingdom and the Noah,
no matter the cost!
Was it just a bluff when you said that
you would protect everyone, Straw Hat?!
I'm gonna stop it!
I'll smash that boat into smithereens before it hits the island!
Don't even say that!
Even if you could do it, I already told you that the Noah holds both our past and future.
Then is there another way we can save the island?
We don't have time to think.
What else can we do?
Decken may still be alive.
If we get him to wake up, we might be able to
make him change the ship's course!
You say that, but what if he's dead?
If we don't hurry up and destroy the ship-
I told you to stop saying that!
You two gonna start fighting?
Look at what's happening while you two squabble.
Noah's gonna crash into Fishman Island.
Please wait, Noah!
There are many people on the island who are precious to me!
Decken-sama!
If you're alive, then please, aim the boat at me!
Please spare the lives of everyone on Fishman island!
Shirahoshi!
Sea drum
Manboshi dearest!
Manboshi!
And now it's your turn.
Hody!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama?!
Dammit.
My Color of Arms is good against blunt strikes,
but it's useless against this kind of attack.
My Haki still needs training.
We don't have the time to fight underwater.
If I'm gonna kick his ass, we have to move.
In other words, you want to fight on this falling ship?
But what you really want must be...
the air on board!
If I get on board,
I can take out that bastard Hody in a single hit!
I was worried he might do this!
Bubbles will break
if you tear a big enough hole in them!
Dammit, there isn't any air on the deck anymore!
By now you must know that humans, who are helpless in situations like this, truly are inferior to fishmen!
You're in no position to think about stopping the Noah.
You can't even beat me!
Die, Straw Hat!
What happened?
Luffy-sama.
I'm incredibly sorry, but...
Weak-hoshi?
Fukaboshi told me to do this.
Bro-hoshi.
Hody!
Just what are you trying to do?!
Don't you realize how many lives there are on that island?!
Bro-hoshi.
Fukaboshi dearest.
Even though you only have fake strength,
The fact that I couldn't stand up to you
means that I'm still inexperienced.  I'll admit that.
But there is still hope!
But Hody, why?!
Why are you trying to kill so many of your innocent brethren?
Just what is your goal?!
What drove you to do something so terrible, Hody?!
Die!
Fukaboshi dearest!
Fake strength like that can't beat me!
So you managed to survive?
Hody, what are you trying to do?!
You say you want retribution against the humans,
but you're attacking fishmen.
Don't you know how many of your fishmen brethren you're going to kill on Fishman Island?!
You're even going to kill
your childhood friends from Fishman District.
Do you know what you're doing?!
Do you have so much hatred for humans that you've become blind with rage?
What could have happened to you?
Were you abused by humans?
Did the humans kill
a loved one or a dear friend of yours?
What could have possibly happened to make you do this?
Answer me, Hody!
Just what did the humans do to you?!
Fukaboshi dearest!
Weak-hoshi...
Straw Hat Luffy-san.
This is the Air Tank.
I'm the one you met earlier.
We've been briefed on this terrible situation.
Our sensors have detected the falling Noah.
Preparations are proceeding according to plan.
So this is what Bro-hoshi was talking about earlier.
Is there something you want on the deck?
Then I'll get there first.
Hody!
Follow him!
No.  Wait, Straw Hat.
Why do we have to wait?!
You should have learned by now.
Fighting in the water is
devastatingly favorable for a fishman like Hody.
If we keep going...
So what'll we do?!
I have a plan.
Hey! Where're you going, Bro-hoshi!
Prince Fukaboshi.
What has happened, Prince?
We may need a large amount of air soon.
Prepare it at once.
Aye!
It'll be fine.  Isn't there air on the deck?
I'll just defeat him there!
Leaving aside the problem of Decken,
do you think Hody will just fight you on your terms?
Take this Baby Snail Phone with you,
in case of emergency.
Be careful in your planning.  We're off!
Luffy-sama, whatever shall you do about the Noah?
Hey!  You there?
How're you gonna give us that air?
We'll use all of the air in the Air Tank.
Air Tank?  What's that?
It's an air transporting device,
used to deliver air to Fishman Island.
If we use the air in the Air Tank to create a bubble,
it should be possible to completely enclose the Noah.
But the bubble disables buoyancy,
so the air won't cause the Noah to float.
In other words, it won't stop the Noah's descent.
Also, to get a bubble big enough to enclose the Noah
we'll have to use all the air we have.
So we only get one shot.
We have one split second when the Noah is directly beside us and if we miss...
there'll be no second chance.
I didn't understand all that...
but basically, it's all or nothing?
Yes sir.  I wish we could do more,
but all we can do is entrust everything to you.
We're incredibly sorry for putting you in this position-
Don't tell me how hard it is!
Just hurry up and give the air to me!
As long as I have air, I'll manage!
Roger that.
We'll do everything in our power to help you.
Luffy-san, we leave Fishman Island to you!
Straw Hat.  Shirahoshi.
What do you think you'll accomplish by staying with the Noah's descent?
This is just the sort of idiocy I expect from a human and the Mermaid Princess!
Straw Hat!
You bastard!
He doesn't give up!
Hey, human.  Give up, human.
Just looking at you makes my skin crawl.
Even if I shorten my life...
No matter how many bystanders are hurt...
I will have my revenge on you humans.
That Hody.
You absolutely can't miss.  We only get one chance.
If you miss, Fishman Island's...
Hey, Straw Hat.  Can you hear me?
It's Fukaboshi's voice!
Bro-hoshi, are you okay?
By some miracle.
But more importantly, listen closely.
Hody Jones...
I understand him now.
Color of Arms: Vulcanization