Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
What were they for?
In ancient times, there existed in this world the power to destroy everything.
Three ancient weapons named after the gods...
Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
And she is one of those weapons.
Indeed.
It would be awful
if anyone found out about this, right?
I'm sure that all the major influences around the world would want to claim Shirahoshi's power for their own.
Both the Government and the pirates.
An ancient weapon?
The power to destroy the world, you say?!
I thought I'd just say goodbye to this place now that I have all their treasure,
but I've overheard something
pretty amazing here, haven't I?
I see, so the Mermaid Princess is...
By the way, Luffy.
How much do you know about what's happening in the world?
What's this, all of a sudden?
Judging from that answer,
I guess you don't know anything.
I'm worried about your lack of interest.
Really?
Thank you for waiting.
Will you come outside and talk?
Alright, just wait a second.
I'm bringing the food with me!
What, you guys are here too?
I drank a lot.
I'm recovering from drinking too much booze.
I'm recovering from eating too much food.
Sanji's recovering from seeing too much mermaid.
Mermaid Island... is the greatest...
What?!  Akainu and Aokiji got into a big fight?!
So I was right.
You don't even know about an event that big?
No.  I didn't hear anything during my training.
Rayleigh was pretty strict, huh?
I heard about it!  I did!
Seriously?!
Immediately after the war two years ago,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku decided to retire.
Sengoku wanted his trusted subordinate, Aokiji,
to become his successor...
but there were many high ranked government officials
who wanted Akainu instead...
so they both became candidates for the position.
Aokiji rarely shows interest in anything...
but he was strongly opposed
to Akainu becoming Fleet Admiral.
The two disagreed, and the unprecedented quarrel
between two Admirals escalated...
until they finally settled it in a duel on a certain island.
Dead men tell no tales.
The loser would no longer be around to complain. {He doesn't outright say that the loser will be unable to complain because he's dead, but it's very heavily implied.}
Control of the Navy would
pass into the hands of whoever won the duel.
Their deathmatch lasted for ten days, and became a subject of conversation all over the world.
They were almost equal in terms of power,
but the battle finally reached a conclusion.
The winner was Akainu.
Sakazuki is the new Fleet Admiral of the Navy!
Akainu!
You're mine!
Did Aokiji die?
They were both gravely injured...
but I suppose when he saw
his former comrade collapse before him,
even Akainu felt some remorse.
Aokiji refused to serve under Akainu...
so he left the Navy.
What?!
So, Aokiji isn't a marine any more?
Indeed.  Who knows where he is now,
or what he's planning.
In any case, the Navy has lost a valuable asset.
But the Government has a plan to fill that power vacuum...
and it gives the Navy almost unthinkable power.
Listen up, all of you.  A lot of things have happened in the New World over the past two years,
but there are two changes in particular that you must keep in mind.
First of all, Navy HQ under Sakazuki's command...
has become an even more powerful force for justice.
The other...
is the rise of the Blackbeard Pirates!
Blackbeard?
The people we met in Mock Town, right?
The guys who once ravaged my homeland!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
He had been with the Whitebeard Pirates
for quite a while.
He was familiar with their territory, and after the Old Man died...
he went and took it over almost immediately.
And did it by using the very same Gura Gura power
he'd stolen from him.
Among society, he already ranks up with...
Red Hair...
Kaidou...
and Big Mom...
as one of the Four Emperors.
So he just snuck in and took Whitebeard's place.
What an insufferable guy.
He truly is a damnable man.
Rumor has it that they're out hunting Devil Fruit users.
I don't know how they do it, but they can kill Devil Fruit users and take their powers.
Blackbeard and his crew's goal is to
collect even stronger Devil Fruit powers.
Be careful.
I'm in danger!
I don't think they need the Hito Hito Fruit.
What?!
Luffy-kun, you have...
a lot of history with Blackbeard... with Teach.
You have to be...
Luffy!
Are you even listening?!
You're the captain, aren't you?!
You should at least pay attention
to the important parts!
Oh, don't worry about it, Jinbe.  We all heard it.
Huh?  You mean a captain isn't
someone who ignores everything people say?
Being the captain means you're responsible
for the lives of your crewmates, does it not, Luffy?!
Nah, Jinbe, just take it easy.
I like to leave it to chance, after all.
I'm sure this has been hard on all of you.
Absolutely.
Oh, Caimie!
Come to think of it, I don't see Weak-Hoshi around.
The Princess said she was a little tired
and wanted to rest.  She just went to her room.
Hey, Zoro!
Sanji!
Is it just me...
or is there something like a wild animal in the palace?
Yeah.
It does feel like something's here.
Somebody!
Please don't do this!
Please just tell me who you are!
Somebody!  Anybody!
Don't make such a bitter face, Your Highness!
Don't worry, this isn't gonna hurt.
After I stole the treasure, selling mermaids seemed like more trouble than it's worth...
but you're a special case!
I just need you to go to sleep for a little while!
My brother and the others just let me know
that they've arrived here!
Let's go to the New World together!
Hey.
Come on, let's see a smile.
Licky-licky.  Licky-licky.  Licky-licky.  Leee!
Hey!
Straw Hat?!
Luffy-sama!
That guy was still here?
I was so terrified!
You're so damn lucky, Luffy!
I should have kicked him, dammit!
That was so close!  Once again, we are in your debt.
Don't sweat it.
I can't believe that treasure thief was still in the castle.
Usually, not even a single minnow
could find its way into the castle...
but the gate was left open
during the chaos of the battle.
Look!  The tower to the right was cut clean in half!
I'm sure it was the treasure thief
who took advantage of our absence and...
No, it was this guy who cut the tower.
When they were escaping from the cage, he showed off by cutting the bars and the room clean in half.
Let him take the blame, you dumb starfish!
What's with you?!
Lying is the first step to becoming a thief!
Wait a second, Right Minister-chan!
Chan?
What do you mean, treasure thief?!
It's just what it sounds like.
That man stole all the treasure in the palace.
Huh, that guy?
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Those are your country's treasures, right?!  Aren't you gonna go after him?
Compared to the lives of all our citizens, the treasure is completely insignificant.
Like hell it is!
So, if we take it back...
It would be my honor to bestow the treasure
upon our country's saviors.
Really?
Hey you!  Why'd you send him flying?!
Why didn't you just knock him out
and tie him up here?!
Even when she's angry, Nami-san is still-
Go find him, right now!
Your Majesty!
Something's happened to Hody and his crew!  And their handcuffs have come off!
What?!
Humans!  Our malice will not end...
The time of our revenge will still come.
Bring Straw Hat to me... I will kill him.
Am I drunk?  My joints hurt...
I got old on purpose.
First, we will get revenge on the Straw Hats -fosun...
We will bestow judgment upon the humans.
What is all this?!
Is this really Hody's crew?!
Don't think you can keep me in a cage,
you dumb king!
T-These bars...
Captain Hody!
How can this be?!
As I thought, the Energy Steroids you've been using...
were the pills from the legendary Tamate Box, right?!
Tamate Box?
A national treasure passed down
through the generations on Fishman Island -jamon.
The truth is, ten years ago...
there was an incident when
the contents of the Tamate Box were stolen.
We didn't know who was responsible, and His Majesty decided to keep it secret to avoid panic.
Now that I think about it,
it happened when you left the army, Hody!
That's right.  I stole them.
You fools.
Even the legends are unclear what those pills do.
Some legends claim that they can
give you the power of a thousand men,
others say that they just make you old.
As far as a national treasure go, they're rather peculiar.
I'm guessing that they're just a vile drug, and were heavily guarded to prevent the dangerous effects.
You opened a box that should have never been opened,
gained some power,
and became deluded with grandeur -jamon.
Shut up, Neptune!
You'll never be able to
carry out your revenge like this.
Shut up!
We are the destined avengers!
We will definitely slaughter...
both you and the humans!
Now that it's come to this, I pity you.
I'll have to reconsider your punishment.
Fukaboshi, you're a disgrace to our species!
You killed my mother,
but I bear no grudge against you.
So please...  Be quiet now.
We mustn't let our island's children hear you.
Left Minister!
Sir Pekoms and Baron Tamago are at the Candy Factory!
Big Mom's subordinates... are here now?!
We have no candy to offer her this month.
Hody and his crew destroyed the factory,
and everyone wanted to give the candy that wasn't destroyed to the Straw Hats...
so we took it to the banquet!
I don't know if excuses will be enough.
We're dealing with a monster
who's willing to destroy whole countries over candy!
One of the Four Emperors...
Big Mom!
The feast has been properly enjoyed, and has come to a proper close.
What?!  We can have the treasure?!
Amazing!
Well ain't that fortunate?
Will Luffy-sama and the others be alright,
Nami-chin-sama?
Yeah, don't worry about them.
We're making it big
just as we break into the New World!
Is life really that simple?
Hey, Usopp!  Why don't we go look, too?
We really shouldn't.  Upon checking, I found out...
that my bounty is over two hundred million beli!
Huh?  But I'm still only worth fifty.
Hey, look, Zoro and Sanji!
There he is!  That was easy!
So your punch already knocked him out?
How boring.
This is an impressive pile!
Is the shaggy king really going to
give all of this to us?
Awesome!  I'll be able to buy tons of meat with this!
He really had all of this
stored inside that swampy body of his?
Heave-ho!
Alright, back to Ryuuguu Palace!
How?
We'll need a flying fish.
Which way to town, Zoro?
Over there.
Okay then, we go the other way!
Hey!
Now then, Left Minister...
Is it too much to ask
for some sort of leniency this one time?
The factory was unexpectedly attacked by Hody's crew, so...
Your little rebellion has nothing to do with us -gao!
I was planning to take a little taste for myself,
and now I'm starving!
You give us an offering of candy once a month,
and we give you Mama's name to protect you!
Wasn't that the deal?!
We're business partners, so I didn't want to say this...
but you know how terrifying Mama is, don't you?!
Make her mad, and you'll...
be annihilated!
He's so cute when he makes threats.
Pay your protection -gao!
There's a crowd over there!
This is the Candy Factory that Pappagg talked about!
Really?  I hope there are some flying fish here.
This must be where they made
all that delicious candy we had earlier!
Hey, Candy Factory!
Oh, it's Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy-san!  Is the feast over?
Luffy-kun!  What are you doing here?!
Yeah!  I'm stuffed!
The meat was great too,
but the candy from Fishman Island is just the best!
What?!
Uh... Straw Hat-san...
Don't tell them that!
Ah!  Mr. Droopy Mustache!  You're here too?!
Did he just say candy?!  Who's this guy?!
Right!  That's Straw Hat Luffy!  No doubt about it.
What's such a famous pirate doing here?
Uh, well...
Hey, kid!  What did you say about the candy?!
No, Sir Pekoms, you see...
Who're you?  You're not a fishman.
Did you come to buy candy?
I just ate until my stomach was about to burst!
What?!
What is the meaning of this?!
He's saying he ate all the candy!
Uh, well, you see... There is a reason for...
Huh?  A talking lion!
Well, whatever.
We've got a similar guy in our crew too.
Pekoms.
Recklessly threatening everyone
won't necessarily help us collect the candy.
Let us find a peaceful solution to this -soir.
The tea party isn't for another four days -bon.
If we set off tomorrow morning, we can still make it -jour.
Another weirdo.  Who are you?
Bon day to you.
I am a soft-boiled member of our pirate crew.
I go by the name of Baron Tamago -soir.
Tamago: Egg
Egg?
Please remember my name, at least -s'il vous plait.
Incidentally, my dear fellows...
Did you just say something about eating
all the candy this factory produced -c'est si bon?
What is he, a compass?
That's right.  I'd love to eat more if they had any!
And it is precisely because they don't that we are in this quandary -bon.
That mark up on the factory is the flag of our boss,
the great pirate Charlotte Linlin -soir.
That flag marks this island
as part of the Emperor Big Mom's territory.
Meaning!  Fishman Island is being protected by Big Mom's name -bon!
She must be nice!  I'd love to meet her!
Big Mom, huh?
Make no mistake.  This is just business!
Ten tons of candy per month.
That is the price they must pay to fly that flag -bon.
Ten tons?!
Indeed.  Mama loves sweets
more than anything else -soir.
Fishman Island candy in particular, is her favorite.
So we will wait until tomorrow morning.
No, no, Baron... Like I was just saying,
all the ovens in the factory are broken...
and it'll take several days to repair them,
so at least give us two weeks to-
No can do -soir.
Hey, Egg!  Why can't you just wait?!
How could one of the Four Emperors be such a small balled bastard?
She is no bastard!
Mama is a great female pirate -vous plait.
She does not have any balls at all -jour.
So she's a Madame?
I love candy... and you too, since you can make it.
So, what happens
if she doesn't get the candy on time?
If that happens...
our agreement will be null and void!
And in a few short days, Big Mom will send
valiant warriors to destroy Fishman Island -vous plait!
Destroy Fishman Island?!
What are you, stupid?!
You think I'll let this country fall because of candy?!
We just saved this island!
You seem happy, Mama.
I'm looking forward to the tea party in four days!
I'll be able to eat that delicious candy from Fishman Island again!
I'm so excited, my stomach acid is just gushing out.
So excited!  So excited!  Fishman Island candy!
You're looking forward to it too?
But of course!  That candy is a masterpiece!
Then... you can look forward to it from inside my gut!
Mama!
I'm back!
Right... So how did it go, Bobbin?
We took care of 'em, then burned it down!
Good.  That country's baked sweets were the best!
I'm sure the burning country must have smelled nice?
It's too bad, but it couldn't be helped.
They failed to deliver the promised sweets, after all.
Got any snacks?
Anyone who won't give me candy must be killed.
I hate people who tell me
they'll give it to me and then don't!
I hate them as much as bitter candy!
Speaking of which...
Apparently Fishman Island might not
be able to deliver the candy for this month.
Pekoms just contacted me.
Should we burn down Fishman Island, too?
The candy from Fishman Island isn't coming?!
Get me the Snail Phone right now!
It must be Mama -gao!
I just explained the situation to her.
A... A message from Big Mom herself?!
Hey, Pekoms!
You answer it -gao!  I don't want her to yell at me!
Hello?!
Hey!
Whaaaaat?!
Are you Big Mom?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're not Tamago, nor Pekoms.
Who are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who will become the Pirate King!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Luffy-kun!
Straw Hat-san!
Monkey... D?
Ah, Garp's grandson?
Now I remember!
You're that kid who caused a ruckus during the war two years ago, right?
There's no candy here!
I ate all of it!
There really isn't any at all?!
There was supposed to be ten tons of it!
I ate all ten tons!
Straw Hat-san, you don't have to do this!
What is he trying to do?!
What an idiot you are!  Don't lie to me!
You're covering for the fishmen, aren't you?
But it's true that I ate it!
I didn't know it was promised to someone else.
We've got tons of treasure here.
I'll give all of it to you as compensation for the candy!
Treasure?!
Huh?!  As if I could eat treasure!
I want to eat sweet candy!
Hey, wait a second!  Is that all treasure?!
Yup.
Mama, this is Tamago speaking!  Let's think about this calmly!
A few days days ago, that brat, Captain Kid, sunk two ships that we were supposed to protect -bon!
They lost a lot of money.  To tell the truth, we've been needing a little money to settle that problem -bon!
Just this once, the smart choice would be
to wait another two weeks for the candy,
and accept this treasure
as an apology for their blunder -jour!
As for your sweets, we'll pick up the sweetest and most savory we can find on our way back.
You gotta be kidding me, Tamago!
How dare you say such a disgraceful thing.
What pirate would ever accept a compromise for the things she wants?!
I- I'm soiry!
Although...
this brat who's willing to stand up to me
has piqued my interest.
As you wish, just this once...
I'll change my target from Fishman Island to you!
Monkey D. Luffy...
I'll remember you.
Come, to the New World!
Luffy-kun!
Sure.  Just you wait!
I've got something to settle with you now.
Huh?
You're too dangerous to trust!
I'll kick your ass in the New World...
and make Fishman Island my turf!