Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Ryuuguu Palace!  Ryuuguu Palace!
This is the Border Police!
An enormous shipwreck is requesting emergency entrance!
The Shipwrecked Celestial Dragon!
A Bullet that Seals the Future
What are you doing?!
Naturally, you have to let them in-
If I'm not mistaken...
a Celestial Dragon is onboard!
What?!
King Neptune!
A Celestial Dragon?!
Grant him access!
Send an emergency unit to the coast!
Yes, Ma'am!
I will be there shortly.
Otohime-sama!
What business does a Celestial Dragon have on the ocean floor?
A Celestial Dragon's ship...
It looks like it was attacked by a deep sea creature.
What business do Celestial Dragons,
who discriminate against us, have on the ocean floor?
Hurry it up!
Damn it!  Those spineless cowards all died on me!
Hurry and bring me a mask, you pathetic fish-creatures!
This place reeks of fishmen!
Hurry and bring me a mask!
Save my life, you imbeciles!
Just how self-centered...
Is that really the attitude
someone asking for help should have?
Doctor!
Get me a doctor!
Where's the medical team?
They're here, but...
they're not sure what to do about him.
We should kill him.
The worst type of trash in the world.
There sure is a lot of noise coming from the port.
Hey.
Captain, apparently a Celestial Dragon has come here.
A Celestial Dragon?
Seems he got here on a wrecked ship,
and he's now asking for help.
Sounds interesting.
Let's go take a look.
This wasn't supposed to happen...
What? My fishman slaves
have returned to Fishman Island?
Why did that happen, My Daddy?
From what I hear, My Son,
the latest addition to the Seven Warlords of the Sea
was a fishman named Jinbe.
Jinbe?
The slaves who fled and joined the Sun Pirates,
which he was a part of,
were given a pardon by the Government, forgiven for the sin of running away,
and returned to their country, it seems, My Son.
I'm sure that the slaves that ran away from my house
are among them, My Daddy!
They must be.
When I think about how they must be living
such carefree lives right now, I get really annoyed!
In that case, I'll go get them back, My Daddy!
My fishman slave collection,
that I spent so much money gathering!
Damn it... I didn't know...
that the deep seas were this terrifying.
Hey!  What are you doing?!
Long time no see, Myosgard.
You dare address me without honorifics... Huh?
Oh, you are... my slaves.
Obediently come back to my home!
Who gave you permission to be free,
damn fish-creatures?!
S-Stop it, you guys!
He's a Celestial Dragon!
Lay a hand on him, and your pardons will be void!
Stop it, you fool!  Know your place!
Do you have any idea who I am?!
I am... I am...
Up on the surface, a Navy Admiral will immediately be dispatched if a Celestial Dragon is harmed.
That's the only reason why everyone fears you.
However, this is Fishman Island, on the bottom of the sea.
As long as the citizens here keep quiet, it won't matter what happens to you.
It'll just be assumed you had an accident.
That's true.
I won't say a thing!
Neither will I!  Of course!
He's barely alive anyway!
He'll die if we just ignore him!
Let him taste the pain you had to endure as slaves!
Kill him!
Let him suffer, and kill him!
Don't forgive him!
What?  I am great...
Even if I wanted to forgive...
You're the one person I could never forgive!
Hey, stop!
Do it!
Kill him!
Stop!
Damn fish-creatures!
Queen Otohime!
Her Majesty's been shot!
Queen Otohime...
Everyone... Please throw away your guns.
The children are watching!
Aladdin!
What's this I heard
about a shipwrecked Celestial Dragon?
I only just got here myself.
Boss Jinbe!
Mother raced out of the castle.
What?!
Big Brother, who are these Celestial Dragons?
They're humans, Shirahoshi.
Humans?
Out of all the humans in the world, they're among the scariest ones.
I heard several gunshots.  Let's hurry.
Yes.
Otohime-sama...
It only grazed me.
Why did you protect him?!
Do you know what that man did to us in the past?!
He treated us worse than slaves, even worse than cattle!
I can hear the screams of
your hearts so clearly, it hurts.
Mother...
Mother!
I know it must be difficult for you,
but your anger and hatred toward the humans...
Do not pass it on to the children!
Think of what they must face from now on!
So, I beg of you!
Don't tell the people on our island anything!
Not about the tragedy that befell us,
nor about our anger towards the humans.
Brother Ti...
Look out, Mother!
Don't move!
Oh no!  Your Majesty!
Mother!
What?!
Sea Kings?!
What... was that?!
It couldn't just be a coincidence.
Shirahoshi... You couldn't be...
What's wrong, Captain?
There is a legend passed down in my family...
In the distant past, there lived a Mermaid Princess
who possessed the sacred power to control Sea Kings!
My forefather Vander Decken traveled to the ocean floor in pursuit of that legend!
Honored forefather!  I have finally found it!
Shirahoshi is the legendary Mermaid Princess?!
You did it, Captain!
It would be bad if anyone else heard about this!
This is a secret legend, that only my family knows of...
I presume!
If I could freely control the Sea Kings and have them do my bidding,
everyone would have to do as I told them!
I would be able to take whatever I wanted!
So, what are you going to do?
Are we going to kidnap Princess Shirahoshi?
First, I must become the princess's husband!
Whaaaaaat?!
But Princess Shirahoshi is still a kid!
Indeed, and therein lies the problem!
Aladdin.
I will... treat his wounds.
And yours as well, Otohime-sama, as soon as I can.
Some weeks later, after the Celestial Dragon's treatment was complete and his life had been saved,
and he was about to leave for his homeland...
Queen Otohime made an astonishing move.
Remember this!
All the tactlessness and rudeness that I, a World Noble, had to endure here...
Damn fish-creatures!
I swear I will make you regret them!
We saved his life, so why does he resent us?!
Our country gave him
the ship and crew to take him home.
How can he talk to us like that?
We shouldn't let him leave.
He'll just put the island in even greater danger.
Please, wait!
We still have some unfinished business, it seems.
That being the case,
I will accompany you to the surface.
To the surface?!
That's crazy!  Otohime-sama!
Mother!
Wait -jamon, Otohime!
I will not allow you to do something so self-centered!
If you absolutely must settle things with the Nobles, then I will go!
You are the king and a great knight,
I'm sure you'd never be captured by the humans...
That's why it should be me!
No.  If someone as strong as you went,
it would be meaningless.
If the weak cannot travel there and return safely,
we cannot prove to our citizens that the surface is safe.
That is why I, who am weaker than most,
must go to the surface.
Mother!
Otohime-sama!
Are you going somewhere, Otohime-sama?
Otohime...
Believe...
in the wife you chose, and in the humans.
She's merely the queen of
these fish-creatures!  Such conceit!
Mother!
Jinbe...
Nobody could have possibly stopped her.
We can only believe in her, and wait.
Your Majesty!  Please, be safe!
Otohime-sama!
Mother!
The Ryuuguu Kingdom was enveloped in a cycle of sleepless nights caused by uncertainty.
But there was nothing we could do except pray for the Queen's safety.
Japanese folklore object resembling Pandora's Box
What's that?  The Tamate Box?
That's right, Captain!
Amazingly enough, I hear it's in Ryuuguu Palace!
And anyone that opens the box immediately grows old?
That's right!  That's how it works.
So, for example,
if a little squirt like this kid were to open it...
she'd become a sexy broad
above the age of consent?
She most certainly would.
Yes!  My problem is solved!
Then I could quickly marry Princess Shirahoshi...
I presume!
Go steal that Tamate Box immediately!
No... wait a second...
Breaking into Ryuuguu Palace ain't so easy.
But if you marry Shirahoshi first...
then you could come and go as you please.
You guys sure are smart.
Shirahoshi ain't exactly ugly,
so she should be a good looking broad in ten or twenty years.
But she'll be even bigger.
That's even better.
I don't have anything against big women!
That girl is the legendary Mermaid Princess who can control Sea Kings.
I will become her husband,
and once I've gotten that power, I will finally realize...
the dream that the Vander Decken family has sought after for generations!
Alright, now let's get started on the wedding invitations.
Proposing comes first!
Oh!  I don't have any friends!
Days passed without any news of the Queen.
The uncertainty just grew and grew.
Man, I even miss her speeches.
Please, somehow, come back alive.
Hey, Boss, where's Otohime-sama?
When's she coming back?
Have faith in her and wait.
She set out on this journey for the sake of your future.
Your Highness, please be safe.
Mother...
It's fine -jamon.  Believe in her and wait -jamon.
A week passed, which felt like 100 days.
And then...
Hooray!  Otohime-sama!
Your Highness!
Just knowing that she's alive... We're so...
Welcome home!
Your Highness...
It took several days to persuade them,
but Queen Otohime finally calmed the Celestial Dragons...
and the sheet of paper that she brought back...
could be called the light of hope for Fishman Island.
Attention everyone!
The World Nobles have a lot of political power...
when it comes to the Council of Kings, and even the World Council.
This was written by a World Noble.
Here's what it says:
"For peace and friendship between fishmen and humans,
I hereby endorse
the proposal of the attached petition."
In other words, when we submit
all of our signatures to the World Council Meeting,
by including this single piece of paper we will have actual power.
We will definitely be able to emigrate to the surface.
The Celestial Dragons are backing it?
Politics is complicated.
All we have to do
is to collect a large number of signatures...
so the final decision is yours.
I can only wait while you decide.
How about it?  Live alongside the humans?
Please indicate your desire to emigrate to the surface.
Please!  Your signatures!
Children, aren't you just trying to make me happy,
only to ask to take them back later?
Nope!
Mom said she's gonna submit one, too!
Otohime-sama.  This small box just ain't big enough!
Just how many people do you think are in this country?
That's right!  Start using this box, please!
Put your signatures into this box
to say that you support the Queen's burning dream!
Fishmen and humans.  We're turning
our eyes away from the history of segregation.
But, it was the Queen's decision to take
those first bold steps that gave birth to this hope.
If we can gather just a few more signatures,
we might really change Fishman Island's future.
If he'd been touched
by Queen Otohime's burning conviction,
even Arlong might have been saved.
I wish Brother Ti could have seen this...
It was at that moment...
when I gained the courage to truly change this island.
That moment?
Yes, the day when the Sea Kings peeked in on Fishman Island.
I think everyone was surprised that day.
They came because Shirahoshi called them.
What!?
All fishmen are capable of
communicating their feelings to fish,
so we're certainly able to talk to them, right?
But not just anyone can talk to those great Sea Kings.
Even the only person capable of communicating with whales, your father, Neptune, can't do it.
There is a legend that is passed down
through the royal family.
Every few hundred years, a mermaid will be born with the ability to communicate with Sea Kings.
Those humongous Sea Kings?
You're talking about Shirahoshi?
That's right.  Someday, someone capable of guiding her power to be used for the right purpose will appear,
and this will bring about a great change to the world.  Or so the legends say.
The whole world?
If that's true, I'm sure that great changes will occur on this island too.
So, maybe that power will assist your efforts?
I think so.
If you want to save people, it's a power of love capable of saving thousands of lives.
But if a dark-hearted person were to wield it,
they could sink the whole world under the sea.
One of the most terrifying powers in this world.
She still hasn't realized that she wields this power,
and she can't control it yet.
If Shirahoshi experiences another shock, even greater than the one before,
she may unconsciously
send the Sea Kings on a rampage.
If that happens,
Fishman Island could be turned into rubble!
What should we do?!
Don't worry about it now.
I'll figure something out eventually, so it's fine.
For now, the three of you should concentrate on
growing up and becoming magnificent warriors.
Please, as big brothers and as warriors, you must protect your little sister with your life.
I understand!
Of course!
Thank you.
But then the incident happened, without any warning.
Get back!  They're going up in flames!
How did the signature box suddenly catch fire?
Water!  Get water!
Quickly, put the fire out!
How could this happen?!
After all the effort we went through to collect the signatures!
Otohime-sama's been shot!
Who the hell?!
There's a sniper out there!  Protect the Royal Family!
Mother!
It's too dangerous here!
Please fall back to the Ryuuguu Gondola.
Princes!
Your Highness!  Your Highness!
Otohime-sama!
Hey Princess, this must be difficult for you...
Who are you!?
Oh no!
Don't approach the Princess!
Hold it right there!
Mother!  Mother!
Mother!
Dammit!  Who the hell did this?!
Why aren't the paramedics here yet?!
Mother!  Mother!
Open your eyes!
Unforgivable!
I'll destroy whoever is responsible for this!
Mother!
Stay by my side, my little angels.  Don't make such scary faces.
I was careless.
All those signatures made me so happy.
Truly happy!
Prince Fukaboshi, I'm the one who is upset...
Your Highness!  We're ready to treat you!
So, whoever the culprit is...
please don't be angry for me.
Don't lose yourself in anger and hatred because of me.
Mother!
Shirahoshi.  Control yourself.
If Shirahoshi experiences another shock, greater than the one before...
This...
Shirahoshi, no...
Hey!  Shirahoshi!
Akkamanbo akamanbo!  Akkamanbo akamanbo!
Look!  Shirahoshi!
Akkamanbo akamanbo!
It's fun!  It's fun!
There's nothing to cry about!  Let's sing, Shirahoshi!
The three of us will always be here for you -la ti do!
Manbo dancing sure is fun!
So fun!
Yeah!  Fun -do re mi fa!
What are the princes doing?!
Stop them!
This isn't appropriate!
Mother!  Look!  Look!  It's fine!
We'll always protect her like this -la ti do!
Please stop!
Don't you understand Her Highness's condition?
Mother.  We'll recollect the burnt signatures.
We'll become great soldiers like our father.
Just as we promised,
we'll protect Shirahoshi with our lives!
So please...
P-Please, don't worry!
It's just a hair's breadth away... The light of the real sun.
There he is!  We've found the assassin!
Hurry!  Hurry to the roof!
Is that him?!
Where is the assassin?
Jinbe-san!
We just took him down.
Who was it?
Well...
This is...
a human?!
Don't let anyone know!
What?  Boss Jinbe?
What?!
What would become of all of Her Majesty's efforts?
This would destroy them completely.
Isn't that just too much?!
But this is the harsh reality.
No!  He's a pirate!
Whether or not he's a pirate is irrelevant.
Don't do it, Hody!
Stop!
Listen up, all of you!
A human...
killed our country's queen!
Queen Otohime's killer was human!
How could this happen?!
A human.
Her Majesty kept telling us to live with them...
and moved by her words,
we had decided to walk beside them.
But now a human...
has shattered that dream.
He's taken the life of the person we all dearly loved!
You may be dead, but that doesn't
give us Queen Otohime back, human!
Has this world been forsaken by God and Buddha alike?!
This is too cruel!
Far too cruel!
Is His Majesty still inside Koukaku Tower?
Minister of the Left...
It is as you hear.
He said that he couldn't control himself.
Lock the door!
Don't open it until my bloodthirst passes!
Your Majesty...
It's me.
Minister of the Left...
The culprit was still carrying a gun...
so the soldiers shot him down.
It was a human!
I would have killed him even if he was unarmed!
But I'm sure Otohime would
never have forgiven me for that.
I don't know when this cycle of revenge started...
but if I had killed him,
I'd have just been sucked into that very cycle.
And any children who saw it...
would have the seed of hatred planted in their hearts,
so they'd also be dragged in.
The cycle would grow even larger.
In my head, I understand what Otohime told us.
Or rather,
I could if this was happening to someone else!
But... why can't I kill someone if they kill my wife?!
I just don't get it -jamon.
I lived as a warrior
and avenged countless fallen comrades.
Many humans attacked me, and I crushed them.
After all that, I didn't think I had the right to help with Otohime's campaign,
so I just watched over her instead.
Why do the innocent die... while I still keep on living?!
Even if I tried to continue Otohime's work,
I would just look like a hypocrite -jamon.
But... peoples' hearts constantly change.
We are all full of contradictions.
Both fishmen and humans.
And there will always be things
that only a warrior can protect.
Your Majesty!
Sorry for worrying you.
I couldn't miss my own wife's funeral -jamon.
Father!  Father!
Shirahoshi...
Father.
Children...
Thank goodness.
Forgive me... for not being here when you needed me.
Father, look at this.
What's this?
Wherever I go, letters keep flying after me.
This is the fifth one already, Father.
This is... a love letter?!
Shirahoshi is still only six years old!
Who is this Vander Decken?!
He's from a family of pirates.
Don't let the children attend the funeral!
The assassin might still have
some allies running around.
And as for this pirate named Decken,
capture him immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Everyone...
The monitor...
Prince Fukaboshi?
Fukaboshi...
Just before she died,
our mother told us with a smile on her face...
that the light of the real sun was just a hair's breadth away.
We have decided to dedicate our lives to fulfilling our mother's wish.
Princes...
Your hearts may not heal
in time for the World Council Meeting in two years...
but there's another one in six years.  And yet another in ten years!
I'm sure you have conflicted feelings about humans following this incident.
We discarded all the signatures
that hadn't already burned to ash.
Let's restart from square one!
Someday...
when everyone's hearts have had time to heal...
let us... dream of the sun together!