Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
T-The Noah is...
The Noah isn't crashing into us anymore.
The Princess is luring the boat away for us!
Princess Shirahoshi!
Please make it out alive!
Where do you think you're going, Shirahoshi?
There's no place you can run!
Shirahoshi!
I have to make it out into the sea
and pull the Noah off the bubble!
It'll be awful if the bubble is damaged more than it has been already!
But it's too far to make it to the main gate.
Luffy-sama's friends must have been
the last people to leave Ryuuguu Palace...
so maybe they left the connecting channel open!
Damn it, isn't there anything we can do?!
The Princess is risking her life to save us!
It isn't the Princess' fault
that Decken has been stalking her!
Decken's on board that boat.  And it's not just him...
Hody is also climbing aboard!
Princess Shirahoshi's life is in danger!
That insane backstabbing Decken.
But I've still got a use for him.
Watch out for Hody, Luffy.
In the water, humans are no match for fishmen.
I know!
It won't be any good if I break the outside bubble
and send him into the sea.
I've gotta get it just right.
It can't be too strong nor too weak.
Sanji!
This sure is a huge chain.
So this is between the two bubble layers.
Hody!
He's still below the first bubble.
Pull!  Pull!
We can't stop it, but maybe we can
slow it down a tiny bit for the Princess...
A tiny bit might be enough!
Pull!
Stop the Noah!
Princess!  Please use this chance to find a safe place!
Dammit!  Stop!
The merfolk!
Everyone...
Are you guys for real?!
There's no way it'll move a single inch!
Wasting your energy like that.
Hey!  Stop it!
You little pieces of filth.
Humans underestimate fishmankind because of cowards like you!
Everyone...
That bastard!
Princess... run away... quickly... please...
As I thought,
The entrance to Ryuuguu Palace was left open!
Don't die on me, now!
Damn you Hody!
Princess Shirahoshi!
She used the connecting channel to get into the sea!
The Noah's following her!
Princess!  Please keep going!
Whoa!  It's goin' up!
Wait up, chain!
You act all high and mighty on land...
but in the sea, you couldn't even put up a decent fight
against a fishman child!
This really is the limit of human strength.
I'll make you regret ever opposing me.
Shirahoshi!
You enjoying your freedom?
The walls of Koukaku Tower kept you safe
for ten years, but they can't help you here.
Will you die from blood loss?
Or will you be smashed by this behemoth first?
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi.
Say yes, and I'll spare your life.  It's still not too late!
I'm terribly sorry, Decken-sama, but...
Marry me!
...you're just not my-
Well then, die!
You think we'd let you marry her?
We won't let you put a single finger on our only sister, Decken!
My dearest brothers,
Manboshi-sama and Ryuuboshi-sama!  And Hoe-sama!
Wha?!  Our brothers?!
We're not your brothers!
Dearest brothers, everyone in the plaza tried to...
Shirahoshi!  Save the crying for later!
My dearest brothers are angry?
We're not angry!
Father said that the Noah is an important ship,
so we can't allow it to get a single scratch -la-ti-do!
That means we have to return it
to the sea floor without damaging it!
Here it comes!
Damn it!  In any case, we can't swim near the underwater mountains or ravines.
That would damage the Noah!
So where should I escape to, dearest Manboshi?
Up!  There are too many obstacles on the sea floor!
I understand!
We'll get Decken.
From the Noah... and my endless love...
you will never be able to escape, Shirahoshi!
Hey, thanks!  You saved me!
Does the wound that you got from Hody
still bother you?
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
I don't have time to worry about a wound like this!
You may be a member of the merman race, who pride themselves on being the world's fastest swimmers...
but compared to me, it's like you're not even moving.
That guy.
Shark cutter
Hey, get me onto the ship's deck!
It's like Jinbe said...
Do you think there's water inside the ship, Jinbe?
I'm not sure, but Decken is a Devil Fruit user...
so we can assume that there must be air in there somewhere since he can make the ship move.
So it should be easier to fight in there.
I want to defeat both Hody and
that guy who keeps throwing things.
I promised Weak-hoshi that I would protect her
when I took her out of the tower.
A promise, you say...
We'll become great soldiers like our father.
Just as we promised,
we'll protect Shirahoshi with our lives!
We've made a promise too.
His strength is nothing more than a mockery, borrowed from the Energy Steroids.
It's pitiful to think that
I couldn't stand up to that rogue.
Forgive us for doubting you earlier.
Don't worry about it.  Just get me onto the deck!
Is there something you want on the deck?
Hody!
Up, up...
Oh, Hody Jones.
How's Neptune?  Did you kill him?
I'm just in the middle
of tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah.
Wasn't this a great idea?
Don't you think so, Brother?
I also have a good idea.
What is it?  Will you tell me?
If you die...
...what will happen to this boat?
Decken.
Hody... You little brat...
I just touched you... with my left hand!
Now, tell me what the hell you think you're doing!
You betrayed me first, Decken.
Honestly, I panicked for a second
when this ship blocked the sky above the island.
Breaking the island's bubble is a good idea, though.
True, Fishman Island will crumble with it, but the Fishman District will remain!
If you die here and now,
your Mato Mato powers will stop working...
and the ship will plunge straight down toward Fishman Island once more.
It will annihilate everything.
Right now, my top priority
is destroying those pesky Straw Hat Pirates.
Tens of thousands of my own men may die as well...
Oh well, I can always get more human slaves later.
You want everyone to die?
That sounds good...
but you'll be first!
Die!
No, you idiot! { def: calling the axe an idiot doesn't work in english.  the manga has "You can't be serious!" }
Now you're nothing but a historical footnote for the new Fishman Island.
You'll die before long. { def: btw, the animation for this sequence made the Mato Mato power look stupidly weak.  Hody should have at least been dodging }
Then the ship will resume its descent, and fall upon Fishman Island!
I'm a kind man.  Before your life comes to an end,
I will fulfill your lifelong wish.
I will kill Shirahoshi!
He killed Decken!
What's going on between those two?!
We can't worry about that now.  He's coming!
We will stop him!
You're in my way!
You worthless beings!
My dear brothers!
Shirahoshi!  Run away, as fast as you can!
Eliminating you will be a simple matter
now that you're outside Koukaku Tower!
Even the merfolk's underwater speed, said to be fastest in the world, is useless against me now!
My dear brothers!
Luffy-sama!  Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Straw Hat!
Brother!
Forgive me!  I was unavoidably delayed while I made some preparations!
Y-You damn scum!
Meanwhile, in Gyoncord Plaza on Fishman Island.
Cap'n Vander Decken abandoned me!
You will become a sacrifice for the death
of Shirahoshi, just like the rest of Fishman Island!
Hey Umibouzu, start fighting!
We're counting on you!
Do something about the Kraken!
Go get him, Kraken!
You can win!
They're both gigantic,
but one of them doesn't have any will to fight.
The Kraken will win for sure!
Hey, Great Monk!  You must have heard him wrong.
What Decken actually said was...
"I leave this plaza to you!"
Meaning that he never planned to destroy the island.
But... he told me that I was a sacrifice.
He meant that you should fight whole heartedly and lay down your life if necessary.
Really?
Isn't that right, guys?
Huh?  Uh...
Yeah, that's right!
It's rare for a captain to have this much faith
in one of his underlings!
You're the hero!  {Swashy-B: I concur. It doesn't make sense in context with the next line. Not sure what to change that to.}
It's time to show what you're made of!
Oh, so dat's it?
No, not really.
Now, swallow this...
and fight as our ally.  Crush the Straw Hat Pirates!
An Energy Steroid!
No way... That'll never work on someone so huge.
It was super effective on him!  {Swashy-B: Changed as per def's suggestion from, "He's one of those people whom drugs work instantly on!"}
Surume!
Cap'n Decken!  Sorry I doubted ya!
Alright!  He knocked the Kraken out!
What's wrong?!  Hang in there!
It's no use!  He's unconscious!
Yer enemies too, right?!
He's like a completely different person!
Leave dis to me!
Where's da enemy?! {Swashy-B: the "Where'th" is a bit overkill in my opinion so I removed it. The "da" is enough.}
I-It's him, Wadatsumi!
Dat guy, huh?
Yer mine!
Jinbe-chan, watch out!
Seven Thousand Tile Roundhouse Kick
Ow, ow, ow, owie!
How can someone that small
block his attack?! {Swashy-B: How bout "that small" instead of "so much smaller"? I think it sounds better and concise.}
Nami-san!  How could this happen?!
Nami-san got hit by the shockwave!
Get up, damn you!
Owie!  Who is it now?!
Hey fatty!  If you gave our beautiful navigator
so much as a single scratch... {Swashy-B: "Hey fatty!" or "You big oaf!" "Galoot" just sounds like he's a country bumpkin.}
you're gonna pay!
No way!  His kicks hurt him too!
Wadatsumi is a monster the size of an underwater mountain.
How strong are his legs?!
Aww...
Now I'm all dirty... {NO YOU ARE NOT. IN FACT YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A SPECK OF DUST ON YOU AS FAR AS I CAN SEE. AND WHY THE HELL IS THIS THE BEST ANIMATED PART OF THE EPISODE. GODDAMMIT TOEI WILL YOU STOP TREATING THE FEMALE CHARACTERS LIKE A PAIR OF BREASTS THAT JUST HAPPEN TO HAVE A WOMAN ATTACHED TO THEM ALREADY?!!!!!!!!!!!! ...Yeah, I'm not particularly fond of blatant fanservice-shots, by the way.}
Don't blame me for dat...
We will fight you, Great Monk!
Manjuu: A Japanese confection
Apologize with your life, you Jumbo Manjuu!
What is with these guys?!
Stop it!
Hyouzou-san!  We're on your-
There's something strange about him.
He's even worse than when he's drunk! {Swashy-B: Changed from "He's even worse than he usually is drunk!" Just needed to be reworded.}
His strength has multiplied!
Drunken Staggering Hash
E-Even steel shields can't stop him!
Wasn't he writhing in pain just a minute ago? Yet no one had harmed him...
No way... This is just like Hody-san's transformation!
Has Hyouzou-san turned into a monster too?!
This feels great!  My power's overflowing!
Man, I wanna cut down more people!
Let me cut you!
Run!  Somebody stop him!
There's no way to block his attacks!
Anyone will do!
Found one!
Hy-Hyouzou-san was stopped!
Zoro!
Sorry, but I'll be taking on this guy!
He might be a good warm-up before I enter the New World!
My power really does drop in the ocean...
Your power dropped?!
Inferior trash!
Do you realize where we are?!
We're in the deep sea!  A mere human doesn't even have a one to ten thousand chance of winning!
Besides, everything will be over soon.
Shirahoshi, Fishman Island, and your companions...
A weakling like you can't protect any of them!
You're wrong.
I'll protect them all!
That's what the last two years were for!