Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Those terrifying commanders...
didn't stand a chance!
Just how strong are these people?!
Wake up!
Look out below!
This is gonna be dangerous!
Wadatsumi is...
falling on us!
You should've dropped him further away,
you clumsy cook!
Shut it!  Or else I'll drop him on your head next time!
You're amazing, Sanji!
Hey, Chopper!  Shrink down a bit!
You're making my giant robot look small!
Franky, that beam was awesome!
Was that robot actually good for anything?
Nami-san!
What?
Please wear a miniskirt!
Shut it!
Exactly what I'd expect from Luffy-kun's crew.
Hey...
The N-Noah!
The Noah is almost on top of us!
Run!
The island's gonna be crushed!
If we hang around for too long,
the Neptune Army's gonna trap us in the plaza!
Hurry!  Those insane commanders are gone!
Are you alright?
Is it too late?!
Didn't it work... Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat!
He still...
isn't giving up!
Straw Hat Luffy-san...
is doing all he can...
to destroy...
the Noah!
Luffy-sama!
If he can destroy the Noah before it crashes...
then the island will be saved.
But if he can't make it...
Fishman Island will be destroyed!
Show us what you can do, Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
Luffy-kun!
You have to do it, Straw Hat!
That's right, Straw Hat!  We're cheering for you!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
You're human, yet you're fighting for us!
We're not gonna run away!
Hang in there, Big Brother Straw Hat!
Fishman Island is in your hands now, Straw Hat!
Go, Straw Hat!
We believe in you!
Straw Hat!
Stop! Noah!
Stop!
Luffy-sama!
Your wounds are opening!
Stay away!
Watch from over there!
Right now, I gotta put everything I got
into destroying this thing!
Stop right there, ship!
Father, I'm so sorry.
We must destroy the Noah.  There's no other way.
Straw Hat!
It's the ship of promise...
but we have no other choice. Our lives are more important.
Forgive us.  It looks like
we won't be able to keep our promise -jamon...
Joyboy.
Stop!
Who's there?!
Luffy-sama, please stop!
Luffy-sama!  I beg of you, stop!
Get out of my way, Weak-hoshi!
If I don't destroy it, the island's gonna...
It's alright!
Of course it's not!  Everyone's still on the island!
The Noah has already...
stopped!
Sea Kings?  Why?
Luffy-sama yelled at me again!
Hey, this is no time to worry about that!
I don't understand it either.
But...
the Noah has been stopped.
What is this?!
What's going on?  The Sea Kings stopped the ship!
Luffy-sama!  Your wounds have opened!
You're covered in blood!
W-Well... whatever.
As long as... the ship stopped.
I'm just glad... everyone's... safe.
Luffy-sama!
It's alright.
My, what a remarkable human.
What a strong human.
Even if we'd been late,
the island might have still been saved...
but the Noah would have been completely destroyed.
I'm so glad we made it.
Good thing Princess Shirahoshi called us here.
I couldn't do anything... I was so sad.
That's not true.  You were touched
by the Straw Hat child's strong emotions...
and you made a wish.
An impassioned wish...
that you could help him save the island.
Our power is your power.
You summoned us to help him.
A-Attention everyone.
T-This is unbelievable.
It'd take too long to explain it all...
but it's the undeniable truth.
The Noah has stopped!
It wasn't completely destroyed either!
Fishman Island... has been saved!
Straw Hat did it!
Princess Shirahoshi.
We've waited a long time for you to be born.
Me?
This ship was built so we could pull it.
The tale of the ship has been passed down since the old times, so that we may do so.
Is that why the Noah is so big?!
Yes.
Once every couple hundred years,
our king is born into the body of one of the merfolk.
I wonder why?
Why indeed.
It's you.
Ever since you have been born,
you have been our Queen.
Honorable brother!
Yeah... Shirahoshi... She can't be...
She must be speaking with the Sea Kings!
I can't believe it!
Several Sea Kings
suddenly appeared outside of Fishman Island.
Almost as if to stop Luffy-san from destroying the Noah.
They came to protect it.
That's what it looks like, at least.
Perhaps the Noah is somehow important to them?
Neptune-sama!
The Sea Kings.
So, it's finally awakened.
The power that could destroy the world itself.
Look.  The bubble is being absorbed by the island.
Humans can't survive on the ocean floor.
Go to him.
Luffy-sama!
This is awful!
Perhaps I was imagining it?
That human with the hat.  He heard our voices.
He couldn't have.
This happened before, a little while back.
Yes, it did.
Rayleigh, did you hear that voice?!
What are you talking about?
We're in the complete silence of the deep sea.
Who's there?!  Who's talking so far underwater?!
Hey!  Show yourself!
I wonder why.
Why indeed.
S-Sea Kings?!
T-They're carrying the Noah!
They're gonna eat us!
The ship is badly damaged.
Can it be fixed?  Can it still still serve its purpose?
Who knows?
To fix it, we'd need the skills of that clan...
but times have changed.
Can it be fixed?
Hopefully it will be fixed...
before the promised time comes.
This is Ryuuguu Palace!  Come in, Left Minister!
We have an urgent report for you!
What happened?
The mermaids who were kidnapped...
have been found inside of the castle!
What?!  So, are they alright?!
Yes.  They're a little dazed,
but they say they can
remember the face of their captor clearly!
Unfortunately, the treasure room
was found empty at the same time.
There isn't anything left at all.
Of course, this includes
the national treasure, the Tamate Box!
Your Majesty!
It appears someone has robbed us
while we were away!
Never mind some petty thief stealing treasure.
We could have lost the entire country
just now -jamon.
More importantly,
tell everybody that the girls are safe.
It might be a little late, but we must show that the Straw Hats are innocent.
We've done something terrible.
If anyone tries to use bubbles to escape...
I'll shoot them down!
Dammit!
Have mercy, Boss!  Let us go!
I was just scared of Hody and his bunch!
We can go, right?!
We don't have anything to do with
the conflict on this island!  We're just humans!
This island depends on tourism and
the money it gets from human pirate visitors, right?!
Let us go!
I never said that we'd kill you.
Wait for the Neptune Royal Family's judgment.
This is an announcement for all citizens.
The Straw Hat Pirates...
had no involvement in the kidnapping of the mermaids.
We admit that we did not check the facts properly.
We truly regret it,
and would like to offer our sincerest apologies.
The Straw Hats didn't kidnap them after all.
I knew they couldn't have done it all along!
Don't lie!
We all thought that they were the culprits.
N-No, we believed in them, right?
S-Sure.
Liars!
Quiet!
You're being unfair!
Yeah!
We must admit it.
We doubted them...
We doubted them because they were human!
That's how it's always been.
We've always seen the humans as...
Super...
Afro!
Franky-san, that is quite stylish!
Super, isn't it?
I get completely worn out
whenever I use the Monster Point,
and I can't even walk for two or three hours.
But... I can still treat your wounds.
Is everyone alright?
You aren't alright.
Everyone seems fine.
Robin-chan!
I used my ultimate technique too, so I'm completely worn out!
Let me rest on your lap!
Pwease!
Just sleep on the ground.
No, you!
Luffy.
It's the Princes!
Hody?!
Vander Decken?!
Father, you must have been worried.
I'm just glad you're safe -jamon.
Everyone!  You can rest easy!
These men will no longer be allowed to run wild!
Now we can live without worrying!
I can't believe someone so scary
was in the Fishman District, so close to us.
C-Captain Hody!
He looks like a monster!
That's great!
Hey, isn't that...
He's back!
Luffy-san!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Princess Shirahoshi!
Please, help him!
Luffy-sama won't stop bleeding!
Luffy-sama pushed himself too far for our sake.
Straw Hat.
This is awful!  I've got something to stop the bleeding in my backpack.
I'm counting on you, Robin.
Sure.
I'm really worried about our next fight, Doc!
Right, I'm ready!
I'll move you.
That's a really freaky doctor!
A little to the left... the left...
Can you save Luffy-sama?!
I can stop the bleeding,
but he's already lost so much blood.
He doesn't have enough left!
What?!
Luffy's the only one in the crew with blood type F.
That's terrible!
There must be someone else with that blood type
here in the plaza!
Anyone!
Hey!
I... I've got F.
I have type F, but...
Daddy, you're type F, right?
Uh, well...
Oh, right!  This country has a law against donating blood to humans!
What kind of law is that?!  That's awful!
Please!  Luffy's in trouble!
My blood type is different, but it's still red!
Will that do?!
Uh, no.  I appreciate the sentiment, at least.
Princess Shirahoshi!
I know!  There are some human pirates here too!
Use my blood.
It's type F.  I'll give you as much as you need.
Jinbe!
Jinbe-chan!
But, the law...
I'm a pirate.
Boss!  What a relief!
Jinbe-san!
Thank you!
Jinbe, you-
It's fine -jamon.
Y-Your Majesty?
What's the problem?  Outdated laws...
are just curses.
Jinbe, this'll hurt a little.
I don't mind.
Even when you're hurt,
even when you're doing the hurting,
red blood flows through your veins.
This thin, tiny tube,
too small to be considered a path,
is what breaks through the prejudiced fear...
and the battles that tried to
wash away blood with more blood.
So easily it flows.
It is not some fleeting vision in the clouds,
but a clearly visible path that leads to the sun.
Jinbe.
Luffy-sama, you're awake!
Luffy!
What, you were conscious?
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
This is... our new beginning,
Mother!
Hey, Jinbe.
Join my crew!
The Royal Family has made its decision!
Alright!  We're free!
Serves you right, Hody!
I thought I'd live the rest of my days as a slave!
Straw Hat Pirates, we owe you one!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
Huh?!  I don't know about that...
Idiot!  I'm gonna do it!
We can finally go to the New World!
What if their grudge against Hody
turns into a grudge against Fishman Island?
That shouldn't change my decision.  This island
is a rest stop and tourism destination for pirates.
They didn't come here with ill intentions.
There is no reason for us to keep them -jamon.
Now then, as for the remaining members of
the New Fishman Pirates!
P-Please don't execute us!
S-Spare our lives!
We didn't know anything about Hody murdering the Queen!
They're all insane!
I sentence you...
to live here, on Fishman Island's mainland!
Whaaaaat?!
What?!  You mean to live under the law?!
That's fine by me.
It's better than being ruled by Hody.
You can't do that, Your Majesty!
We can't let these guys roam the streets freely.
We'll be scared to let our children out of the house!
Of course, they'll work under my army's command...
and will be pressed into service -jamon
I will give them jobs where
their formidable strength can be put to good use!
The Fishman District,
which we cannot watch effectively...
will be completely closed off
from this day forward -jamon!
The revelation of the true culprit
behind Queen Otohime's assassination...
has brought the darkness of fishmankind to light.
The Pirate Hody Jones's plot to conquer Fishman Island...
was, ironically, foiled by human pirates who had stopped at the island.
Hey.
Where is Straw Hat Luffy -jamon?
Well, you see... He ran away.
R-Ran away?!
May I ask why you all left the plaza,
as if you're trying to run away?
What a stupid thing to ask!
Back there, our fight was staged like a show for the citizens.
If we stayed in the plaza,
we might be made into some kind of heroes.
Just thinking about it makes me shudder.
You mean to say that
you don't wish to become heroes?
Listen up!  Heroes are the kind of people
who divide up and share their booze!
But I wanna drink all of it myself!
Again, where did you guys get this idea from?!
Why won't you join us, Jinbe?!
Let's go on adventures together!  Please!
Let's go out to sea!  It'll be fun!
Yeah, join our crew, Boss!
A former Warlord in our crew would be really reassuring!
And Luffy, you need to rest.  Don't get worked up.
I'm only saying that I can't join you yet.
I'm glad that you invited me.
I'm sure it would be fun
to travel the seas with all of you...
but there are still things I must do first.
Things that I am honor bound to do.
I've only taken a short break from those obligations.
I must still complete that journey.
Once I am able to move freely again...
I will come to meet up with you.  This I promise you.
If you still feel the same way when that time comes,
will you invite me to join once more,
Straw Hat Pirates?
This is a promise!
Hey, now... When a man is fulfilling his honor,
you shouldn't pressure him.
It seems Luffy's taken quite a liking to him.
A friend of Luffy's is a friend of ours!
We'll be waiting for you, Jinbe!
Thank you.
So, what now?
Do we just head straight for the New World?
Are you saying that you're leaving already?
I wanted to thank you properly,
and spend some more time with you.
Okay, then!  Let's spend at least a week in
the Mermaid Café before we leave!
You think we don't know
the real reason why you want to do that?!
Granted, I completely agree with you!
Hey!  Please, wait!
What?
Isn't that a soldier from the Neptune Army?
Please hold on, Straw Hats!
King Neptune, I've caught up with the ship.
Good.  Luffy-kun!
Why did you leave?
We still haven't thanked-
I don't wanna be a hero!
I understand that.
I just wanted to invite you to a feast!
Let us resume the feast
that was interrupted before -jamon!
A feast?!
Alright!  Let's go call Hachi, Caimie and the others too!
On Neptune's orders,
the Fishman District was immediately sealed.
Hody, as well as the New Fishman Pirates' commanders and Vander Decken,
were all locked away in the prison tower.
We're counting on you, Kraken!  Take him to a distant sea!
Wadatsumi, there's no cell big enough for you!
You are banished from this kingdom!
Did you find any?
Yes!
Alright, let's cook 'em up
and bring 'em all to Ryuuguu Palace.
They've invited the Straw Hats to a huge feast.
We'll handle it!
We heard that sea monster meat is their favorite!
Let's bring them candy and cakes too!
I heard that they can eat a ton of food!
Bring everything you have!
Do we have enough alcohol?  We'll give 'em
so much top shelf liquor they could bathe in it!
Luffy-kun and his crew,
I'm glad you could come -jamon.
That being said, we can speak at the feast.
The long flounders will carry you to the banquet hall!
Whoa, those are some huge rays!
They're flounders.
Don't you listen, Luffy?
He just said that they were flounders.
It's a pitch-black, flooded room...
I never thought someone like me
would see Ryuuguu Palace.  I'm so nervous.
This is the first time I've been in Ryuuguu Palace.
Where are we?  Where's the meat and feast?
Oh!  Our heroes have arrived!
The floor's covered with soldiers!
Heroes!  Heroes!  Heroes!
Shut up!  Quit saying we're heroes!
I'm eating all the meat!
That's right!  I wanna drink all the booze!
You're both hopeless.
Luffy-sama, the stage is right ahead!
Stage?
First off, let me introduce the pride of Fishman Island, the number one diva on the ocean floor...
Maria Napole!
And the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
What an amazing singing voice! {Eh, I've heard better. Oh, and for the record, the song lyrics are not included in the CCs and are just about unintelligible... So no subtitles for u.}
Maria-sama!
My soul is trembling!  Oh yeah!
And our special guests!
N-No way!
Men are left breathless by their beauty!
The Mermaid Café Dancers!
Stop that!
You'll die, Sanji!
Beauty too pure to be captured by a mere picture!
These ladies are number one!
My powuh ith fadibg...
Oh, my.
Awesome!
Simply spellbinding!
Caimie!
Ishilly!  You're alright!
Finally!  Can't have a feast without this!
I've been super-waiting for this!
I'd expect no less from Ryuuguu Palace!
Thank you very much.
Most obliged.
Thank you.
Mermaid-chaaaan!
Thank you very much.
Cheers!
Now, let's start drinking!
Yummy!
You can have as much as you like.
Oh, I'm done for!
Sanji!
You should be more careful, sir.
Father!
Shirahoshi.
Cheers!
Cheers -jamon!  It's alright -jamon!
You guys too!  Cheers!
Cheers!
This drink is quite delicious.
Is it made using different water?
Oh, so you can tell the difference, Miss?
Refill!
What's with the pale faces?  My cup's empty!
W-We lose.
Akkamanbo!  Fuuri!  Fuuri!
Keep dancing, everyone!
Eat, drink, and let loose -mi fa so la ti do!
What did you want to talk about -jamon,
Pirate girl?
Forgive me.  I thought this would be
our best chance to be alone.
I-I should make this clear, I have sworn to love nobody but my wife, Otohime, for the rest of my life!
She might be dead now, but I could never betray-
Who is Joyboy?
I read a Poneglyph in the Sea Forest.
Who was he apologizing to?
You can read them?!
I'm a survivor from Ohara.
If you don't want to tell me, I won't force you.
No.
I'll tell you all that I know.
I'm okay with you knowing.
Joyboy was a man from the surface, who lived during the void century.
So he died at least eight hundred years ago?
That message was directed to the Mermaid Princess
who had lived on this island.
It was an apology,
because he'd broken a promise to Fishman Island.
Promise?
The details haven't been passed down,
but eventually somebody will come and carry out the promise in Joyboy's place.
That is the legend that is passed down
through the Royal Family.
We promised to believe in that day,
and each generation has taken its turn to watch over the Noah, as promised.
When that day comes,
the Noah will fulfill its mission, at last.
Earlier today,
after everything was finished above the island,
I heard that the half-destroyed Noah was carried into the Sea Forest...
by the Sea Kings.
Maybe Joyboy, who was going to use the Noah, had the power to control the Sea Kings?
No, it was the former Mermaid Princess
who had that power.
I knew it.
So, does Princess Shirahoshi have the same power?
Yes.  I assume that it awakened completely today.
I can't say I'm happy about this.
I understand.
Two years ago, I read a Poneglyph on Sky Island
that told the location of an ancient weapon.
It said that it was here, on this island.
The Mermaid Princess
who lived in the same era as Joyboy...
Is this what they called her, perhaps?
Or in other words, Princess Shirahoshi, who carries the same power...
will also inherit this title.
Her other name is...
the ancient weapon...{ Btwb: split this line since there is quite a big pause and it adds dramatic effect }
Poseidon!