Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Outta my way!
I've been robbed!
Somebody, please stop him!
He's stolen a lot of money!
Hey, move it!
I-If you come too close,
I can't guarantee this girl's safety!
Your Majesty?
Oh, Your Majesty!  Please wait!
You mustn't keep involving yourself in these things!
That is our job!
Please wait, Queen Otohime!
Who's that?
Stay away!  Or I'll shoot!
I... I warned you!
Did I miss?!
Damn it!  Stay away!
Is that... Otohime-sama?
It hurts!
That's the problem here?!
My hand!
Doctor!
Your Majesty!  Let me have a look.
It's a compound fracture.
From a single punch?
I do not care.
Q-Queen Otohime...
Otohime, Fisher Tiger, and the Sun Pirates!
The Fateful Encounter!
The Queen...
Why would you commit such a vile act as robbery?!
Shut up!  What would you wealthy royals know?!
I've got ten kids at home,
and all of them crying because they're so hungry!
That just makes it worse!
Y-Your Majesty!  Please, stop hitting him.
You know your body is much weaker than the average person's!
I do not care!  This is for his own good!
Even if my hands are destroyed, I must make him understand!
Do you think that children raised on stolen money
can ever be truly happy?!
A man should live a life that
his children can be proud of!
However...
I wish to... apologize as well.
I'm so sorry!
I am your Queen...
yet I did not see your suffering,
even though we live in the same kingdom.
The pain that you feel in your heart...
also pierces through my heart.
The hardship you've faced must have been terrible.
I... didn't want to do it either!
But I didn't have any other choice!
My store caught fire...
Someone burned it down and stole all my money!
I don't have a job, and my debt is terrible.
My kids are famished and I feel so sorry for them!
So that's why.
I understand.  I understand completely.
But it was still wrong!
Whaaaat?!
If you do the same thing that was done to you, you'll just continue the chain of misfortune!
I'm sorry!
Even so, please forgive me!
We could not be there for you so the blame lies with us too!
No, you're too kind.
I don't deserve such kind words.
But it was still wrong!
I'm sorry!
I promise, I will change my ways!
Thank you for crying for someone like me!
Your Majesty!
That is wonderful!  Please, do your best!
It's exceptional just to have the royal family
leave Ryuuguu Palace and walk around the kingdom.
But for the sake of a single citizen,
she's willing to shed tears and slap him.
Otohime-sama truly is an unusual queen!
Truly a loving person.
Look!  Even the children adore her!
Otohime-sama!
I do this all for the sake of you children.
Whaaaat?!
Your nose is running.
For your sake, I had to slap you!
You look like a fool,
with snot running out of one nostril.
If your nose is going to run,
it should run out of both nostrils.
It's so touching!
Is it?
A passionately loving person.
Queen Otohime would come down from Ryuuguu Palace every day,
and appeal to the citizens of the kingdom.
We must bring Ryuuguu Kingdom up to the surface!
"The color of their skin is different.
So is the shape of their bodies."
We should not wait for the humans,
who think like that, to understand us.
Instead, we should approach them ourselves and learn about their ways!
There are ten thousand meters between the sea floor and the surface.
The same distance separates
the humans' way of thinking and our own.
Do not misunderstand!
The humans who come to this island
are a certain type of humans called pirates.
And the ones who buy people from slave traders are an elite minority called Nobles.
We are biased because we only come into contact
with certain kinds of humans.
We still do not know anything about them.
Certainly, there must be many kind-hearted humans up on the surface as well!
We will bring our kingdom up there,
so that we may live together under the same sun!
At this year's world council meeting,
let us express our wish to emigrate into their world!
All of you, please sign this petition.
I don't know...
Even if it's you asking, Queen Otohime.
Compromising with the humans.  I just don't know.
You should not say that.
Rather than never trying because we think it
can't be done, we should take the first step ourselves!
Now, then!
I'm sorry.
It's no use.  History has already given its answer.
I'm back, children.
Welcome home, Mother!
I'm back, Shirahoshi.
Ah, Shirahoshi, my oasis of peace.
I am sorry for being late.
My, you have snot hanging out of your nose,
and yet you are still so cute.
We were with her the whole time, so she's alright, Mother!
She's alright, she's alright!
Thank you, my dear princes.
Mother, is your hand alright?
Oh, this is nothing to worry about.
Your mother will change the future you will live in!
If Her Majesty wants to give a speech,
she should just do a video broadcast.
It's because of Kenbunshoku Haki that she was born with -jamon.
She doesn't want to talk from a palace up in the sky,
but to face them directly,
close enough to feel their hearts.
That is what Otohime believes is right.
Even I cannot stop her.
But there are so many human pirates on the island.
Even if we're being protected by
the authority of your friend, the pirate Whitebeard,
you never know what might happen.
She's aware of that.
The world that Otohime dreams of
is an ambition from several hundred years ago.
Our distant ancestors had the same dream,
but they were never able to realize it during their time.
What do you mean?!
I cannot stop Otohime.
Make sure to protect her for me.
Yes, Sir!
This Otohime-san was
a pretty strange person, wasn't she?
You cry all the time...
Is that something you got from your mother?
Well... W-Who knows.
So you were a soldier in this country?
It was pretty much the only option I had, growing up in the Fishman District and only knowing how to fight.
The Fishman District?
Hachi, isn't that where you're from, too?
It sounds like a kind of scary place.
Indeed... Though in the past,
it used to be a giant orphanage that
took care of the children that didn't have relatives.
But before long, the inhabitants began to fight and
it became too much for the administration to handle.
It has turned into a lawless zone where
all the outcasts from Fishman Island gather.
The man who used to be
the leader of the Fishman District, Fisher Tiger,
eventually left the country to go on an adventure.
And I, who was supposed to succeed him,
joined the royal army.
The Macro Crew, despite being fishmen,
went on to become slave traders themselves.
And the others...
They all went their own separate ways.
And then, one day...
Please, give it back!
If you want it back, then why don't you try taking it?
Give it back!
Do you have any idea how many signatures there are on those sheets?!
Why should I care how many signatures there are?!
Hey, stop right there!
You're Arlong from the Fishman District, aren't you?!
Arlong from the Fishman District?
L-Let me go!
That's not quite right.
I'm Captain Arlong, of the Arlong Pirates!
I live by hunting those inferior pirates...
who have the run of this place
even though they can't breathe underwater.
I'm hunting down pirates in your place!
The Neptune Army should pay me to show their gratitude!
B-Boss Jinbe...
Don't just sit there and watch.  Help me!
Jinbe?
Ryuuguu Kingdom, Soldier in the Neptune Army
Jinbe, 30 years old
Hey, hoodlum.  Let go of that rookie!
He happens to be my underling.
Oh, and while I have no interest in
that paper with the signatures on it,
it's really important to the Queen.  So give it back!
It's Boss Jinbe from the Neptune Army!
We're saved!
Boss, huh?  That's a good title for you!
You won't find another soldier
that acts more like a mafia boss, after all!
Do as I say, Arlong!
Fine, I got it.  Here.
Here you go!
Now, don't be so upset, Brother.
B-Brother?
Long time, no see.  We're comrades from the Fishman District, aren't we?
Don't lump me in with you.
You're still a pirate?  Scum!
Don't call me scum, Brother!
Then is trash better?
Trash?!
I thought of you like a brother,
but you still speak to me like that?
Hey, everyone!  It's Fisher Tiger-san, the adventurer!
Tiger-san has returned!
Tiger-san!
Tell us about your voyage!
Brother Ti!
Big Brother!
Jinbe, Arlong!  You look like you're doing well.
Your journey was quite long this time.
Yeah.  A lot of things happened.
Come to my ship!
Sure, later.  First of all,
I have some business at Ryuuguu Palace.
Then allow me to take you there.
Looks like he has no business with pirates.
What?!  Big Brother never said anything like that!
Try to get along, will you?
You want to free the slaves?
I can't take it anymore.
Being a slave is living hell.
Even now, as we speak, I'm sure they're being treated in utterly inhumane ways.
But still...
I've made up my mind.
You... What did you see on your latest voyage?
Humans.
And not long after that, a major incident occurred.
Big news!
What happened?
B-Boss Jinbe!
T-Tiger-san... attacked the Celestial Dragons!
The Celestial Dragons?!
Fisher Tiger attacked the Holy Land, Mariejoa.
He came to be known as
the hero who freed the slaves.
At the same time,
he was labeled a dangerous criminal.
As of this moment, I am resigning.
Jinbe!  Are you going to abandon your duties in the army?!
The duty of protecting the island
suited me better than I thought it would.
However, there are times when one's morals are more important than one's duty!
Big Brother Ti has finally done it!
The Arlong Pirates will join with Fisher Tiger immediately!
Let's go, men!
And so the former outcasts of the Fishman District,
who all looked up to him, gathered together.
Welcome to the pirate business.
From now on, the world itself will be our enemy.
All who are prepared for this, step forward!
To avoid discrimination between the former slaves who Tiger had freed and those who came freely...
every member of the crew branded the emblem of the sun where it would hide the marks of slavery.
The fishmen had formed the Sun Pirates.
So he really went and did it.
Fishman Island's standing has fallen once more.
We probably won't even be able to
attend this year's world council meeting.
What should we do about this?
But, on that day...
I couldn't have stopped him.
You... What did you see on your latest voyage?
Humans.
When I listened to his heartfelt voice, it was screaming terribly.
Extra!  Extra!  Breaking news!
He made a surprise attack on the Celestial Dragons.  People aren't even supposed to touch them!
That's Fisher Tiger, the hero of Fishman Island!
Amazing!  A fishman's made history!
Everyone, please listen!
Oh, it's Queen Otohime!
This again?
We were all afraid.  We ran away and hid ourselves.
But what have we learned from that?
Just because some human nobles
have committed unforgivable crimes against us,
Fishmankind must not start
mercilessly killing all humans.
Now then, let us try to coexist with the humans.
Let us try to learn more about the surface dwellers
who live under the shining sun.
We know more than enough about them.
Yeah, I feel bad for the Queen, but...
You two, over there!
Sign this.
I can't, Otohime-sama.
Right now, everyone on the island is in support of Tiger's amazing feat.
This incident's going to mean a complete separation from the humans.
But the humans are obviously in the wrong...
So right now, we just can't...
If it's impossible now then we can wait seven, eleven, or even fifteen years.  Whatever it takes.
For the day when this country
participates in the world council meeting again...
Please!  Sign this form!  Please!
Fisher Tiger's amazing!
Just like when he was boss of the Fishman District.
It says the Celestial Dragons are really pissed off.
You know, those Celestial Dragons.
Oh yeah?!
He took out those sickening humans.
All humans are trash.
Just like Arlong-san always says.
They really are inferior!
The Sun Pirates on the surface, going wherever they want and beating up all the humans -dosun.
They're amazing -dosun.
If we were stronger,
we could have gone up there with them -hi.
Great!  Great!  One day, I'll join 'em!
Take them out, Sun Pirates!  Kill the human scum!
Yeah!
Boss!  Boss!  An enemy ship's been spotted -nyuu!
Boss!  Boss!  Boss!
Boss Ti!  There's trouble!
Man, shut up, Hachi!
Why don't you calm down?
You sure are noisy.  Is it the Navy?
There's no mistake, it's the Sun Pirates.
Take Tiger's head!
You missed!
Fire!
What're you doing?!  Aim properly!
But they're submerged under the water!
Whoops.
You damn fishmen!
Hand over all the runaway slaves!
Then maybe we'll overlook your crimes.
R-Rear Admiral...
T-They're attacking through the hull.
What?!
Quietly hand over the slaves!
What you're doing is a major crime!
Attacking humans?  Fishmen should know their place!
What was that?  Say it again.
Just try to say it again!
Help...
Damn slavery is okay, but liberation's a crime?
And she wants us to love the humans?
That Queen Otohime...
Fire!  Fire!
Aim and fire!  We've got the intel!
You're harboring runaway slaves!
N-No way?!
Runaway slaves, you say?
Is he a monster?!
Do you see any evidence of them here?
Look at all of our bodies.
The mark that runaway slaves are supposed to have...
Do you see anyone here with it?
Lemme go!  Stop it!  What're you doing?!
No!  Help!
Relax.  I'm going to let you go.
I'm not like you humans.
Listen up men! Grab their loot and food,
and get back to our ship!
I sentence you to death.
Human, your very existence is an inexcusable crime.
Hold it!  Arlong!
Die!
Vice-Admiral Borsalino...
Unit G2, Rear Admiral Kadaru's ship... has been lost.
Oh?  Why'd they try to fight them?
I told them to just report their location.
They're saying that if you get close enough to see them then they'll surround you.
Oh, how scary... Guess I shouldn't expect any less
from underwater professionals.
So?  What kind of people were on the ship?
Sir.
Some pirates who were recently on the sea floor
near Fishman Island, Arlong's crew, are on the ship.
Since they're naturally adept at fighting in the water, it's difficult to measure their combat abilities.
Arlong... I've heard the rumors.
There's also talk of
another strongly built man in Tiger's ranks.
He's incredibly strong,
but we don't even know his name.
Oh, how troubling.
That hurt!
What's that for?!
Just because I took out one or two pieces of inferior trash?!
You two went too far.
We're not some band of common murderers.
Don't get carried away!
But, Brother Ti... I mean, Boss,
they were shooting to kill you.
It's only natural that we should hit them back just as hard!
It makes us mad, after all!
We lose if we kill them.
Do you want to become like them?!
This isn't a mission of revenge for the history of segregation.
What I did at Mariejoa wasn't either.
I may have broken their ridiculous laws, but
it was only to free those who were being oppressed!
The Sun Pirates fight for freedom and liberty.
Nothing else!
If we hold onto grudges and
start taking revenge on the humans,
it will just spawn more tragedy
since the humans will try to get revenge in turn.
Future fishmen, innocent of any crime,
will be punished for the crimes of their ancestors!
Don't you understand?!
We can fight and steal from
those who pursue us, but that's the line.
We don't kill anyone!
I've been wanting to say something
to you for a while now, Big Brother.
Worried about the humans taking revenge?
If they try to take revenge, we can just kill them!
We should be so brutal
that the humans tremble in fear before us!
If we do that, they won't even think of striking back.
They just don't know about
the strength and ruthlessness of fishmen.
We should burn it into their eyes...
Fear us!
What the hell're you doing?!
Jinbe, Queen Otohime's campaign is the ideal solution.
To her, what's the difference between me and Arlong?
The thing that scares me the most
is the demon living in my heart.
Nyuu- A pirate ship!
That's a huge ship!
They're trying to get famous by defeating us.
So now we have to deal with guys like this too?
If we keep sinking them,
they'll stop coming eventually.
We were wanted by the Government and had to fight every day.
Queen Otohime also tried to
fight against the world in her own way.
Sign it!
To live together with the humans?
We'll pass, Your Majesty.
Sign it!
Hey!  Bounties have been placed
on Boss Ti's and Jinbe-san's heads!
What?!
Wow!  230 million beli!
And Jinbe's at 76 million beli!
Wanted posters!
It looks like their bounties have gone up!  Wow!
Looks like the World Government is shaking in their boots.
Down with the Navy!
Sign it!
Give me a break!
It was like that for three years.
But then I encountered a girl on a certain island.
Will you do us a favor?
Three years ago, when you freed us slaves,
this girl escaped from Mariejoa with us.
As you can see.
But the town where her family lives
is quite far from here.
We wanted to take her
but we can't sail these dangerous seas.
I'm Koala.  I'm eleven years old.
Thank you very much for saving me three years ago.
Even if she's just a kid,
she's still human!  Disgusting!
Why'd you let a human on the same ship as us?
It's progress.
Quit grinning like that!  You're really pissing me off!
Arlong-san!
Lemme go, Hachi!  I'm not finished!
Indeed.  She never stops smiling, and it's kind of creepy.
You...
I'm sorry.  I'll work.
I'll do all the cleaning and never stop to rest,
so please do not hit me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.
What're you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.
Hey, you're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
No matter what, I won't cry.  So please don't kill me.
Hey, you can stop that.  Do you think we're so scary?
Yes, but I want to see my mother.
So I grit my teeth and boarded your ship.
If I take a break, you might kill me, right?
I'll make myself useful, so please do not kill me.
She knows nothing other than slavery.
A slave may be killed for something as trivial as crying.
They can also be killed for
taking a break from cleaning.
They're always thinking, "Maybe I'm next."
They live in continual fear but won't show it.
Boss.
Bring this kid to my room.
What're they doing in there?
Giving her a lecture won't help.  Her spirit's been broken.
Boss!  What're you doing in there!?
Cauterizing the wound.
It's violent, but as long as she bore the mark
she'd never forget things that are best forgotten.
Hey, are you alive?
Oh, she's awake!
It seems I fainted.  I'm sorry.
But look, I didn't cry.  So please do not kill me.
No matter what you do to me,
I won't cry.  So please do not kill me.
There's nothing wrong with crying!
Don't think that we're the same
as those stupid Celestial Dragons.
Watch closely.
We don't kill anyone.
Men, we're off!
We're going to take this girl...
and make sure she gets home!
Koala has returned to her home,
but the Sun Pirates are ambushed by the Navy,
and Tiger is confronted by Strawberry.
After a bloody battle, Tiger reveals his shocking past.
After Tiger's death, many of the citizens on Fishman Island withdraw their signatures.
and Jinbe decides to join the Shichibukai, to protect the former slaves freed by Tiger.
Next time, on One Pace:
The Shocking Truth of Tiger!
The End of the Sun Pirates