Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bonds that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Tsuki
Yibis (Opening)
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
Video editing
Sewil
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Raw provider
Crunchyroll
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose! I'll find One Piece. I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
The Colosseum of Many New Faces
and Maynard's Pursuit!
Hey, what's with that shrimp?!
Spartan got beat!
No way!
He's one of the star gladiators of this Colosseum!
Maybe, he just tripped over himself.
That wouldn't lodge someone in the ground!
Now, where should I sit?
Did you just start that fight?!
That isn't allowed! You're disqualified!
What?!
We don't need hooligans like you
causing scuffles before a match...
Whoa-whoa!
Flower Country Gang
Chinjao Family
Hold it right there, you idiot!
Above:
Don Chinjao
Right:
Sai
That big one started it! If you're gonna throw someone out, it's gonna to be him!
Left:
Boo
He's unconscious though.
Oh! It's Sai and Boo from Flower Country!
Even Don Chinjao is here!
He's a legend!
You saved me! Thank you!
Nah, don't mention it.
Honestly, you don't have to mention it...
You don't have to say "Thank you"...
Don't say the words "Thank you."
Take back your "Thank you," you bastard!
You don't have to refuse
his thanks that much, brother!
Don't ever say those words to me, idiot!
Sorry. He's really excitable.
There are all kinds of people in the world.
You... Stop ganging up with other powerhouses from your block, Dagama!
Hey hey, look at them.
Yeah, there are a whole bunch of big names from each and every country!
Assassins from a neighboring country
Funk Brothers
It's an international war for the devil fruit!
Ganging up and paying people off?
Older Brother
Kelly Funk
You make me sick!
It's a one-on-one fight.
Younger Brother
Bobby Funk
Even if you cheat like that, only one contestant per block can go to the next round.
Cut the crap!
Prodense Kingdom - Military Tactician
Dagama
I know you two are here on your country's orders, too!
Any country that has the Flame Fruit,
which is more powerful than any weapon,
King of the Prodense Kingdom · The Fighting King
Elizabello II
would give any country an advantage in diplomatic relations.
Look around you. See those faces?
There! He is a Class-A war criminal who was involved in the Sea Battle of Dias - Suleiman the Beheader!
They're the former bounty hunters who bombed a government institution - Abdullah and Jeet.
A fake adventurer - "The Surmounter" Orlumbus.
Sponsored by the Donquixote Family...
a sadistic pirate who's worth over 100 million - Bellamy the Hyena.
And the "Pirate Noble" Cavendish is here...
...as well as the crazy rookie Bartolomeo who became infamous a year ago.
Now, do you really think that none of these ill-famed people are plotting anything?!
It's crazy to think they don't have a plan!
I'm sure you guys have something! Don't you?
The first round is a battle royale!
Only one winner per block
will go to the next round.
Yeah!
Block A's match will start soon!
Followed by blocks B, C, and D.
There are over 550 competitors here.
And only four of us will win the first round!
It won't be so easy.
So I guess...
...you brothers are in the same block because of paying somebody off, am I right?
It's just a coincidence.
It's a coincidence.
Which block am I in?
I'm sure the receptionist told you already.
Your number is 556 so you're in Block C.
I know everybody has different goals...
but the world could fall into chaos depending on who gets the Flame Fruit.
Let's cut the crap and
do our best, everybody!
Armor! Helmets!
This is awesome! Can we use anything here?!
The Colosseum Armory
You can use anything
except projectile weapons.
A half-naked statue of an old warrior man!
Cool!
I want it!
I will wear this armor!
And a helmet that's cooler
than that old man's!
So cool!
I want to show this to Usopp and the others!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Th-The nobleman is so...
Nobleman?!
All of the women are fainting.
What?!
No, its too much!
Look, that's Cavendish!
The Pirate Noble?! He's alive?!
I can't believe how beautiful he is!
This is the dressing room, huh?
Hey you, right there.
That won't do.
There is a weight limit for gear.
Gladiator
Lucy
Well, whatever you do,
you have no chance.
I will win the Flame Fruit.
Captain of the Beautiful Pirates
"White Horse Cavendish"
Bounty: 280,000,000 Belly
Yes! With that beautiful power that belongs only to me.
You're overweight.
What?!
I told you earlier! Come here!
Tsk! But I look so cool in this!
That explains why everybody's half-naked.
Gladiators are just part of a show for them.
People get excited seeing a loser's blood.
At the Colosseum, people
show their true colors.
How is watching a match between two heavily-armored competitors any fun?
For them, this battle is just a show.
I wonder if I have to take off this cape too?
It looks so cool!
Hey you.
I watched you take down that big guy earlier.
Who are you?
I'm Luffy!
What?!
Lu...
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
You mean Lucy!
Oh yeah, I'm Lucy.
Don't confuse us!
Oh, you're Lucy!
I thought Straw Hat Luffy was here!
There's no way!
I heard the real one is
a eight-meter-tall giant!
This is nice!
If you were really...
Straw Hat Luffy, I would have...
killed you here and now.
What?
I came to the New World three years ago.
The whole world was talking about this beautiful rookie who was worth over 200 million.
I was in the newspapers everyday.
Girls went nuts over my wanted posters.
They would steal all of the posters in town.
Everybody was going crazy over me.
"Hey, big star!"
"Who? Me?"
"Of course!"
But...
...one year later,
Whitebeard's War drew their attention away from me!
The whole world's attention was on Straw Hat Luffy and Whitebeard!
On top of that,
new rookies kept coming up one after another, became known as the Worst Generation,
and wreaked havoc like crazy!
Reporters won't pay attention to me anymore!
That's why I'm gonna kill them!
Every one of those annoying newcomers!
All of them!
What you're saying is absurd.
Say whatever you like!
To recapture world attention again,
I would kill as many newcomers as it takes!
To do so, I'm gonna win the Flame Fruit today!
Your good to go.
You're taking the same attitude as them!
Are you a competitor?
You look weak but you're a cutie!
Hm... Interesting.
I ended up looking like this old man.
Are you interested in him?
Who are you?
Rebecca. I'm a gladiator.
Corrida Colosseum Gladiator
Rebecca
Thank you for what you did earlier.
I didn't like Spartan.
This statue is cast after a legendary man.
He was the strongest gladiator in the history of Corrida Colosseum, Kyros.
He won 3000 out of 3000 matches.
The only wound he ever
received was a single slash.
Wow! He was that strong?!
He used to fight here up until 20 years ago.
But no one in this country knows about him.
Huh?
None of elders or gladiators in this country
have ever seen him.
It's the most mysterious statue in Dressrosa.
We don't know if Kyros the Gladiator actually existed...
or if somebody made up the story and put a statue here.
All we know is
what's written on this plaque.
Although nobody knows about him,
nobody wants to remove it.
That's also strange.
Hm... I don't get it at all but...
I like this statue! It's so manly!
I like it, too.
Hey, Great Warrior Rebecca-chan!
The undefeated girl!
We know you'll do it today, too!
I'm sure you were relieved earlier...
That Spartan guy who bullied you for
a long time got his ass kicked.
Stop it, idiot! Let's go!
What's with them?
Ignore them.
I...
I'm gonna fight for the last time today.
I'm gonna win the Flame Fruit and...
I'm gonna kill Doflamingo!
What?! Mingo?!
What block are you in?
C.
Good. I'm in D.
I hope we both survive the first round.
Lucy.
The winner of Block A is the masked man!
Mr. Store!
That was so fast!
Oh? Is he going to take his mask off?! For real?!
He took it off!
What?!
I can't believe this! We all know him!
What an interesting start!
And an unexpected competitor!
The winner of the Block A battle royale is...
Oh, he's...
the captain of the first ship of
the fearful Emperor Blackbeard's pirate crew.
it's Jesus Burgess!
He's...
That champion from way back then!
Burgess! Burgess! Burgess! Burgess!
Scene 1
"Corrida Colosseum"
The Blackbeard Pirates, huh?
I was expecting
Luffy to win this thing pretty easily but...
it looks like it might be a bit harder to do.
I hope no one finds out who he is.
Now, I've got work to do.
Hey! Wait a minute!
I'll come with you!
What?! You're in the way!
I don't need a guy who doesn't
know where the factory is!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of some high-ranking guy in the Doflamingo Family...
Whoa-whoa! Wait! Be quiet!
and make him cough up where it is.
What is it now?!
Let's go someplace else to talk!
Such radical speech here is taboo!
Who the hell are you?
Same location
"Audience Seating"
"Pirate Mercenary" Hajrudin...
Cavendish!?
Even "The Missionary" Gambia?!
Let's go!
Hey hey, you don't have to rush like that.
Yeah, there are a bunch of bad guys.
I was surprised about Burgess, too.
I'll talk to Issho-san right away.
Okay.
Hey hey!
Sonny, are you talking to yourself?!
Or were you talking with someone on the outside?
Staff officer of the "Barto Club" pirate crew
Bounty: 67,000,000 Belly
You're strange!
"The Missionary" Gambia
Am I right? Am I right?
What's that note?!
You were whispering those cool guys' names!
Don't tell me...
are you a...
Are you all right, sir? Please respond.
Everything's fine.
I'll call you back in ten minutes.
The Colosseum is still excited
from the battle of Block A!
I wonder how it's going to go for Block B!
Shall we go out?
There are so many familiar
names, aren't there?
So what should we do now?
Oh, your coat.
We need, maybe, three warships.
And in the meantime, let's head for... uh...
Navy Headquarters Admiral
What was the name?
It's Green Bit.
Fujitora
(Issho)
Yes, let's go there.
And um...
We'll need as many medics as we can get.
We can't have any casualties.
I also want to know how many spectators
there are in the Colosseum...
and the population of this town.
Okay... Instead of the enemy numbers?
Is it necessary?
What we have to consider first is
not the number of enemies...
...but the number of people we have to protect, don't you think?
Yes, sir!
This is Maynard.
Excuse me for hanging up earlier.
Everything is okay here.
Toilets / Garbage dump
Oh, and earlier, I mentioned a name; "The Missionary" Gambia...
who works under Bartolomeo.
Fighter 0429
Capman
You can cross that out.
It wasn't him that I saw after all.
D-Damn! That Marine.
Navy Headquarters Vice Admiral
Maynard the Pursuer
I'll continue with the plan we have for here, also.
At a café in the northeast
Scene 2
Caesar exchange team
Green Bit?
It wouldn't be wise to go there.
Are you people some kind of researchers or explorers?
You better not go unless you have a purpose that's worth risking your life for.
That bridge looks very strong...
Yes, it's made of iron.
But look at the entrance.
Nobody is crossing it nowadays.
A school of Fighting Fish inhabit the area around Green Bit.
Before they came, people used to come and go freely,
but that was 200 years ago.
Mister, what's a Fighting Fish?
It's a savage fish with horns.
If you approach them by ship, they'll capsize you.
That's why they reinforced the bridge with iron, but it doesn't help.
No use?! What do you mean?!
Are you saying they can take down an iron bridge?!
Well, I don't know the current condition of the bridge.
Only people who crossed it know, but I don't know anyone who's came back.
What?!
Hey, Tra-guy!
You have to change the hand-over spot now!
He's right!
Think what it's like to be handed over at such a place, fool!
You fool!
We'll stick with the plan.
We're already here, so stop making a fuss.
More importantly,
I'm worried about the situation of this country.
Their king suddenly abdicated.
How come they are so calm?
There's something strange going on here.
That's what worries me!
W-What are you doing, Robi-
What's going on?
CP-0.
What?! "CP"?
The strongest intelligence organization in the world.
Cipher Pol Aigis 0!
D-Don't tell me they're related to CP-9!
They're the strongest of all of those organizations!
When they're on the move, bad things follow.
Indeed.
Scene 3
The fairy and Zoro
Gotcha!
I'll be taking my sword!
Oh no!
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
I'm so dumb! This human will see me!
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
Scene 4
Kin'emon, alone and astray
Who are you people?
I'm just an old man out for a walk!
Don't lie! Isn't that a topknot under your hat?
You're the samurai, Foxfire Kin'emon, aren't you?!
We saw you in the video from Punk Hazard.
And we figured you would come back here,
samurai.
Am I right?
Now now, just come along quietly!
If you care about the life of that Kanjuro you're after!
Scene 5
Sanji, in love
Target confirmed.
Violet-chan!
Dear Nami-san and Robin-chan.
How is the weather there?
I can't believe it! You're so strong!
It was nothing! Anybody can detect a sniper sitting 16 meters above the ground!
It was nothing!
How reliable!
I'm in the middle of a hurricane called love!
I'm...
...in love!
I'm here for you!
Scene 6
Sunny safety and security team
All wrong! You shouldn't drink it all up!
Listen! The taster's role is to try just a little of the shogun's food to check for poison!
Understood?!
Yes, sir!
Try again!
Get me a cup of tea, Choppa'emon.
Yes, sir!
I'll bring it to you right away, sir!
Retainer: Choppa'emon
Maid: O-Nami
How are you feeling now, sir?
Ah, this is so comfortable.
I'm feeling great.
Yeah? That's good.
I'm feeling great, too!
Th-That hurt, Nami-san!
I thought it was a sleeping-in-your-lap party!
What kind of party is that?!
He's playing shogun.
Playing shogun?
Whenever we leave Momo alone, he gets very serious and depressed.
He's not gonna share it with us, but...
maybe he has had some kind of trauma at a young age.
What?!
I see. It was something like that.
Hey, Bone-kichi!
Yes?
Do something to warm the place up.
No. Luffy-san is the only one I take orders fro-
Just do it!
Don't like it I don't like it!
Doesn't matter how many times we bury him...
He's gonna come back!
Yeah!
The Vitality Corpse!
Come on!
Thank you, everybody!
Huh?
I don't like it...
What?!
I thought it was just the four of us on the ship.
So did I... I wonder what's making that noise.
Creepy!
I'm scared!
O-Nami!
I don't like it... Honestly...
I-I-It's from the men's dormitory.
Oh, I don't like it!
There is somebody in there!
Who is it?
Corrida Colosseum
Competitors of Block B! Is Capman here?!
And Bartolomeo?!
You're Bartolomeo, aren't you?
Block B's match will start soon!
And did you see a competitor named Capman?
Well...