Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing         Sewil
Raw provider      Crunchyroll
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
The Plight of the Riku Clan!
The Lurking Hero Awaits in the Shadows!
They're raining down, one after the other.{Changed the timing here a bit, as that first sound he makes isn't really part of the sentence. -Starfish}
Gramps, big bro!
It stinks!
So you were thrown down here too, Boo.
Where are we?
A mountain of toys and rubbish?
That's what I wanna know.
Another one's gonna fall, you should move.
Former Gladiator Ricky
I didn't know that such a large scrapyard existed underneath the country.
If I'm mistaken, please forgive me.
Dressrosa Squad Captain
Tank Lepanto
But I've got a nagging feeling.
Are you...
Might you possibly be...
His Highness, King Riku?
King Riku?
King Riku? That's impossible!
Isn't he dead?
Speaking of Dressrosa's former King,
I heard that he went crazy and was killed.
After having fallen so far,
there really isn't any point in hiding it anymore.
Indeed I am him.
But please do not call me a king, Commander Tank.
Former King of Dressrosa
It's King Riku.
Riku Doldo III
(Rebecca's grandfather)
You were alive?
Thank goodness you were safe, King Riku.
I am only an old man now.
A sinful old man who couldn't even save his only granddaughter.
It has been such a long time. {Xemnas: Can the editor change the wording of this to make it sound more formal? Mainly because Elizabello says the same thing a bit later, but since they're both kings and his tone is much lighter and less formal, I guess I just wanted to make a distinction between the two.}{Seconding this request. This sentence really should sound more formal, though I can't think of a way to do so myself.[/not a native speaker] -Starfish}
I am now...
Doflamingo's...
There's no need to say it. I understand.
You were watching over Viola.
How could I ever doubt a man with as much honor as you?
It must have been a difficult decision.
No, compared to your troubles...
Oh my, so you were King Riku!
Oh, the king of Prodence.
That really takes me back.
You have saved my country from crisis, many times over.
I'm glad you are alive.
Hey now...
Ever since you disappeared,
there's been a power imbalance in the surrounding countries, resulting in constant war.
I'm really tired of it all.
Hold up, Elizabello!
You may be tired of it, but if someone's laughing, someone's also crying!
Someone has been making a massive
profit from instigating all the wars!
By supplying weapons to all those warring countries!
The broker is a man named Joker.
Which is Doflamingo's alias in the underworld.
But we don't know where those weapons are being made or stored.
Our Flower Country has been losing badly in the war because of those weapons.
Our entry in the colosseum's tournament was merely part of our investigations.
The Happou Navy was ordered by our king to destroy the weapons factory. That's our true goal.
King Riku, because you committed that act which allowed Doflamingo to become king,
many of the neighbouring countries are in big trouble!
Exactly so, Elizabello-sama.
It's true that we owe a lot to Dressrosa for what they have done for us.
But your worry for that man is unnecessary.
Right now, the name King Riku-
Shut up, Dagama!
You don't know what really happened on that tragic day ten years ago.    {Isis:didn't a prisoner say "what happened on that night " just an episode ago!! O_O}
How dare you speak ill of the king?!
It's alright, Tank. It doesn't matter now.
King Riku, I am also a former soldier of your army.
As am I.
Me too, King Riku.
What's this?
The toys have started moving.
I thought they were just trash!
All the former soldiers of Dressrosa and even the toys are bowing down to him.
What's going on?
Wasn't King Riku hated by the entire country?
With such a large pitfall here, it seems that there are some secrets hidden underground.
Understood.
Continue with your investigation.
Big bro!
What the hell's this?!
What's going on now?!
Sai!
Big bro!
Hey, hey...
It's over now, so you can go.
Do not harm any humans.
And follow the orders of the family.
Make sure you follow these rules.
Exit through that door and you'll reach the factory and trade port.
Go.
No talking! Make sure you work hard!
All the participants are powerful, so they won't break very easily.
What's going on?
My body won't listen to me.
I can't go against his words.
What's just happened to me?!
She did it!
Colosseum
Prisoner Gladiator Lodging
Hey, who cares about Cabbage?! Show Rebecca!
Actually, come to think of it, it's really hard to see here.
I'll cheer her on from somewhere closer.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I used to think
this country looked really fun and happy...
but looking at you guys, maybe I was wrong.
What you saw was the flowery world of the winners.
Doflamingo divides the world
into obedient winners and disobedient losers.
He's exactly like the World Government.
Those who oppose him
are losers who get treated like garbage.
Hide the garbage in darkness, and sure,
the country ends up looking perfect from the outside.
Let's go search for treasure!
It's just like the country I grew up in.
Once you start questioning things,
you see that something is wrong in this country.
We believe that there are even darker secrets.
You better be careful.
Alright. See ya.
Luffy-senpai!
Flower Fields - Riku Royal Fighters Rebellion Headquarters
Ancient writings say that long ago, our ancestors went out to sea,
searching for resources that their country didn't possess.
But when they were discovered by the big humans, they were brought to the brink of extinction.
There they are.
Dwarves!
But one day, the king of Dressrosa,
a neighbouring country, offered them a deal.
In exchange for a bit of manual labor, he would offer them the resources they desired and their safety.
The name of that king was Donquixote.
That's the worst part of our history, which continued until 900 years ago.
The age of slavery.
The writings that follow show what the royal family truly were...
Demons, through and through!
Our people were forced to work day in and day out, deep underground where no one could see them.
The big humans lived on the riches and prosperity brought by the Tontatta.
No one knows what happened in the void century but...
800 years ago, a new king was born into Dressrosa.
King Riku!
After hearing of the dwarves' inhumane treatment for the past few hundred years,
it is told that he shed tears and deeply apologized from the bottom of his heart.
And the next action of the
new king was one of repentance.
He said that we could take anything we needed from this country.
That we didn't need to work.
The king called it the work of fairies and calmed the citizens with laughter.
He successfully created the legend of the fairies in this country.
King Riku the First, you're so cool!
The country led by the kind Riku line even provided support for neighbouring countries in danger.
I can't say the country was wealthy and prosperous,
but it was a wonderful one full of smiles.
Our ancestors paid tribute to the kind King Riku,
by turning this country into one of beautiful fields and flowers.
That is the 800 year long bond between our Tontatta Kingdom and the Riku royal family.
But after 900 years, the descendant of the Donquixote family, Doflamingo returned.
Strangely enough, he is trying to replay our horrible history.
Over 500 of our people, including my daughter Mansherry have fallen prey to his sinister ways.
We mustn't let those times repeat themselves!
We won't let it.
We'll fight!
Indeed, to Dressrosa, and to the Tontatta,
the Donquixote Family's rule
will only bring suffering!
We'll fight alongside our hero!
With Usoland on our side, we can't lose.
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
I was thinking the same thing!
As expected!
King Riku was such a good guy.
He was nice to the bug people.
Who are you calling bugs?!
I meant it in a good way.
Then it's okay!
Captain-san.
The female gladiator fighting in the colosseum, is being called King Riku's granddaughter, {Once again, this cannot be here. She is fighting Logan later in the episode and earlier....}
Drop dead, Rebecca!
and is really being insulted.
You're the shame of Dressrosa!
The people of this country seem to hate King Riku.
I was thinking the same thing!
Yeah!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
On that day, 10 years ago...
Usoland!
an incident happened that caused King Riku to lose the country's trust in one night.
Even though the king tried to protect the country all the way until the end.
The citizens don't know the truth about that incident!
I'm sorry, I couldn't protect your mother.
At that time, Doflamingo tried to destroy the Riku blood line, but...
I took King Riku's granddaughter Rebecca and continued to run for a long time.
But, she was eventually captured.
And now she is put on show at the colosseum.
I'll gladly lay down my life to protect
King Riku's integrity and Rebecca's life.
I am betting everything on this fight!
Just why are you...
I couldn't protect Rebecca's mother.
Never for a second have I forgotten what happened on that day.
Having been turned into a toy, she may no longer remember me, but...
I am...
Rebecca's father!
Your back's wide open!
What's this? Rebecca saw her chance and escaped!
Rebecca is scurrying around like a mouse!
And Rolling Logan is in hot pursuit,
taking down any fighter that gets in his way!
That's cheap, Rebecca! Fight!
Fight and let us see some blood!
Damn descendant of King Riku!
Your family's pure evil!
If you're her father...
doesn't that mean...
since she's King Riku's granddaughter...
that... back when you were human, you...{Honestly in this case even I'm getting annoyed by all the trailing-off. -Starfish}
It all began on that night.
Answer me!
You must be King Riku's...
No, actually it may have started long before that.
On the day when that woman, Monet, began working in the palace.
Monet?
The bird-woman from Punk Hazard? {Cecil: The way he reacted to seeing her, YESTERDAY, you'd think he's scream his head off right there.}
This country has changed a lot in the past 10 years.
Both the land and its people. {Cecil: This is my favourite song from dressrosa, I patiently await for some sort of soundtrack to come out with it.}
Dressrosa 10 Years Ago
Hey, what happened?
Pirates attacked my house.
Though since the Riku Royal Army protects us, the damage wasn't that bad.
It hasn't rained in two weeks.
Yeah. But despite the drought, the flowers haven't wilted.
Why?
It's all thanks to the fairies.
They protect our flowers.
I want more food!
If you have enough energy left to shout, then you're fine.
We may be poor, but this country is free from war.
Don't you think that's more important?
Yeah! {...No seriously, this entire sequence just BOTHERS THE CRAP OUT OF ME. I refuse to believe that it could have been as idyllic as they portray it here. -Starfish}{most unrealistic reaction from a kid that's never experienced anything horribly traumatic like that before.}
In the 800 years under the Riku Royal Family's rule,
this country has never fought a single war.
That's amazing.
Indeed. Miraculous, even.
Dressrosa was a truly peaceful country.
But then...
without warning, a nightmare descended upon the royal palace.
Who's there?!
Don't shout. Don't call for anyone.
W-Who are you?
I am Donquixote Doflamingo.
The rumors about this pirate Donquixote have caused me some concern.
Yeah, your worries were spot-on.
I am a descendant of the Donquixote family, the old rulers of this country.
I am the rightful ruler of this kingdom. The king has returned!
From what I heard, you robbed a transport ship that was carrying tribute for the Celestial Dragons,
and used that money to blackmail the Government into making you a Warlord.
They don't know how to deal with me.
The fact that I don't fear the Celestial Dragons really worries them.
If you know who I am and what I can do, that simplifies matters.
I'll sell you the country for 10,000,000,000 belly.
You'll sell the country?!
Normally I'd just take it without giving you this chance.
If I can use money to avoid bloodshed, then so be it.
But this country doesn't even have
10,000,000,000-
Of course it does.
You have until dawn.
No getting help from other countries. I'm testing your power as king.
However, you are not to tell your citizens about me.
You have two options.
Either avoid a fight by gathering money,
or fight and see the blood of your subjects.
Choose whichever you prefer.
Wouldn't it be better to fight Doflamingo, Your Majesty?
No!
Calling it "fighting" might make it sound nicer, but it would be manslaughter, an inhuman act!
But even if we try to gather up money, there aren't many rich people in this kingdom.
The fact that Dressrosa has been at peace for 800 years proves that we are not beasts.
Don't lower yourself to the level of animals! Be human!
I will not let people kill each other!
We have no time!
Send troops to all towns in Dressrosa!
We must gather up 10,000,000,000 belly from this country!
If we don't, this will become a kingdom ruled by pirates!
I'm sure that gathering the money will mean that I'll lose the people's trust,
but only for a few hours!
Once this is all over, I will do whatever I can to make it up to them!
That is all we can do.  We can't solve this through lies or stalling.
Keep gathering money for as long as you can! The life of this kingdom depends on it!
It's the army.
What could they want so late at night?
Isn't that Commander Tank?
Listen to me, all of you!
I want you to gather all the money you have and bring it here!
Hey, what's wrong?
Do you really think the king will let you get away with this?
This is an order from the king!
Quickly! We can't explain our reasons, nor do we have time to wait!
Please, just have faith in King Riku and bring whatever money you have here!
But this is just so sudden...
This is madness! There's no way they'll accept this!
A Projector Snail?
To everyone in Dressrosa.
King Riku!
It's King Riku!
I have a request. It's rather sudden, and so unreasonable you might doubt your hearing, but...
please don't ask me why I'm doing this.
Please just get whatever money you have...
and lend it all to me!
The king's bowing down!
Your Majesty!
But why would he ask this?
It's just so sudden.
Your Majesty, why are you bowing down to your people?!
You mustn't! You are the king!
Please, stop this!
Raise your head!
If you're seen acting like this, you'll bring shame to your ancestors!
You'll become the whole world's laughing-stock!
Stop this, now!
I beg of you! This is no joke!
If you want proof of my sincerity, I'll gladly cut off my own hands or feet for you, right now!
Listen close, Tank.
Should the worst happen, I will at least try to take Doflamingo down myself.
King Riku, isn't that...
I leave the rest to you.
We must gather that money, whatever it takes!
Hurry up, everyone! Get your money, like the king asked you!
That's right!  The king is kind, he'd never do this for selfish reasons!
Yeah, he's gotta have some good reason for this!
Bring all your money!
Alright!
This proves the king's greatness.
Here.
Thank you.
Forgive me!
People have wholeheartedly trusted the Riku Royal Family for 800 years.
What a magnificent kingdom!
This country will be saved!
We will repay you!
Now carry the money back to the palace!
Hurry!
Commander Tank!
His Majesty is in the town of Sevio.
Look at the screen.
What?
Southern Town Sevio
Your Majesty. You didn't need to come here.
Run...
King Riku! We may not know what your reasons are, but we believe in you!
Run away! {Why would you have two lines in a row with the same dialogue be translated different ways? O_O}{Xemnas: Well "run, run, run" over and over again gets tedious and the last one is extended.}
King Riku! What are you...
King Riku!
King Riku?!
No! Stop this!
King Riku, please stop!
What's wrong with you?
Move! Stay away from me!
Get away!
He's even killing the soldiers?!
My body's moving on its own!
What... is going on...
King Riku?!
Unbelievable!
What a horrible king!
The night is still young.
Now, soldiers! You dance too!
Parasite!
Now the soldiers have gone insane too!
Help me!
C-Commander!
King Riku, why?!
He's never done anything wrong!
Is it something we did?
There is no excuse for this.
The country is done for!
This was Doflamingo's trap!
What has happened to you, Your Majesty!?
Please, stop!
Hey, hey! Can we start now, Doffy?
Don't be so impatient, you fool.
We will wait until the country has been plunged into the very depths of despair,
and they curse King Riku with all their hearts.
That is when the heroes will appear!