Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Soundtracking
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
Video editing
Sewil
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Raw provider
Crunchyroll
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
A Sad Past!
Rebecca and Soldier-san
The battle royale at Corrida Colosseum continues!
Currently, three fighters have won
the right to challenge the Donquixote Family!
The victor of Block A,
the Blackbeard Pirates' "Champion", Jesus Burgess!
From Block B we have the captain
of the Barto Club Pirates, Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
And from Block C...
Our very own gladiator, Lucy!
Only one more finalist remains to be selected!
However,
due to the massive damage done to the arena,
we will postpone the start of Block D
for fifteen minutes!
Bring out a replacement arena!
Fix it already!
Please be patient until the Block D fight begins!
Straw Hat!
There's nowhere for you to run now!
Cabbage?!
Durandal!
Cavendish has lost it again!
That lowlife!
What's going on?
He shouted "Straw Hat" again.
Oh yeah, Straw Hat.
Wasn't he that pirate who failed
to save his brother at Marineford?{Yeah they say "choujou sensou", which we have always translated as "the great war" here... but over time I have grown to not particularly like that translation at all so I prefer to just say Marineford personally. They both get the point across anyway. -Starfish}
As if not saving someone is special!  I can do that too, you know.
W-W-Whad're you doin'?!  Cut i' out! {Note that due to being kinda flattened by a barrier he's having some trouble enunciating clearly. Hence the "doin'". If possible, plz add some more indicators of this. -Starfish}{ def: changing t to d represents it well but makes a bit tough to read.  just went with i' instead of it }
I am a noble from the Kingdom of Biggschots! {Yeah I just copied FUNi's translation of the place here. It's originally "Doereena Oukoku" which translates to something like "Super-Great Kingdom". -Starfish}
Stop it!
Y-You're crushing me!
Do you have any idea who you were just casually laughing at?!
Now listen up! Straw Hat Luffy-senpai is the man
who will someday stand at the very top of this era!
He is the future Pirate King!
I was there...
on that fateful day, over two years ago!
In Loguetown... in the East Blue!
On the legendary execution stand,
where the Pirate King Roger himself died!
Trapped in a hopeless position, that man declared...
I'm the man who will be the Pirate King!
And in that moment, the heavens...
brought down the lightning, and saved him!
I witnessed a miracle!
Ever since that day, I fanatically read
everything I could about the Straw Hat Pirates.
Alabasta, Enies Lobby, Impel Down...
And last but not least,
the fateful events at Marineford!
That incident sent shivers down my spine!
Boss! What should we do
with the enemy soldiers we just defeated?
Just throw'em in the sea.
Back where I lived, I was just a crimelord whose turf covered a measly one hundred and fifty towns.
I looked up to Luffy-senpai.
And finally, I set out to sea myself!
Just try to say something like that again!
You put your pathetic existence on a pedestal
and act like you're looking down on Luffy-senpai!
What can you do?  You pathetic insect!
Now Bartolomeo's gone crazy too!
Let go already!
Why should I have to fight you in the first place?!
I'm exhausted!
Hey!  Somebody stop them!
I'm not getting involved!  It's too dangerous!
Y-Yeah, there's no way I could go up to him!
I'm chickening out and losing my chance!
I'm just too nervous to approach him!
That scar underneath his eye... He's the real deal!
He's so friggin' cool!
Huh?  My eyes are tearing up so much I can't see.
How I wish I could kill that filthy cabbage
and protect my hero!
Hey you! Gedh awah fwom him, cab...
It's no good, I can't!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Listen up!
Gramps has something he wants to say to you.
Hang in there, Grandpa!
Huh? You're still doing this?! Look, I won fair and square!
You've got it wrong!
I don't even hate Garp any more.
I want to convey my immense gratitude!
Please, just let me thank...
Wait, grandson of Garp!
Hold it, Straw Hat!
He ran straight past me!
Um, wait!
Hey, don't run away from a fight!
W-W-W-What do I do?
I wanna talk to him, but I just don't know how!
Please, wait!
I wanted to show my gratitude
for putting my head back to normal...
by offering to make
my grandchildren's Happou Navy serve you.
Wait!
What is with all these guys?  They're so persistent!
Hold it!
Please, wait!
Really... I just want to relax for a bit.
This way, Lucy.
Oh, it's you! Um...
It's Rebecca.  You sure have a lot of enemies.
Follow me.
Right, thanks!
Well, you could say the same about Shiliew.
But I don't trust Aokiji.
Oh, hold on, Captain.
Straw Hat's here.
Oh, you're there too?
Straw Hat?
Blackbeard?!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I sure was surprised when I heard that you were Commander Ace's little brother!
Shouldn't you be there?
They're gonna start soon, ya know?
Your brother's execution, that is!
Blackbeard?
That's right.  It's been a while, hasn't it? { def: if he says the same thing as the flashback then we should keep the line the same }
So I understand you're participating in the tournament, "Lucy"?
But my man, Burgess,
is going to win the Flame Fruit!
It's almost like Ace is joining my crew.
It's going to be great!
I mean, he did refuse the offer last time!
You're the last person I'd let have Ace's power!
I look forward to fighting you!
You know that pirate?
Yeah.
I can't let him win the tournament!
Don't you have any more free samples, lady?
You're just going to eat samples
without buying anything, aren't you!
Hang on!
I'm so sorry, Miss.
What do you want, Lucy?
You're gonna buy me food?!
Oh, he's a friend of yours, Rebecca?
Thank you very much.
Sorry, I couldn't afford much.
Don't worry. Thanks for treating me, Rebecca.
So, where are we?
This is the dormitory for the colosseum gladiators.
Though some people would call it a prison.
Guest competitors never come down here, so you can relax here until the finals.
Really?  That's great!
Gladiator Exclusive to the Corrida Colosseum
Rebecca
That was some fight.
You're a lot stronger than I expected.
Is it good?
Yup. The colosseum-lunch is delicious!
You're not hungry?
Mother, I'm hungry.
No, I... I don't get hungry.
Really? You're like a samurai.
Got you! Rebecca, this is your chance to kill him!
What?!
Isn't that why you brought him down here?!
Hey, what's going on here, Rebecca?!
Hurry up!
H-Hey! You'll spill the food!
Kill him!
What's wrong?
You have to kill him,
or you'll never accomplish your goal!
Goal?
Rebecca was pinned!
I can't believe he moves faster than she does!
Do whatever you want.
I deserve it.
I wouldn't do anything
to the person who bought me lunch.
I tried to kill you!
It doesn't matter.  I'm not dead.
Besides, you weren't really trying to kill me.
Ow...
How could he forgive you so easily?
That really shows the difference in power
between you two, Rebecca.
If we'd been able to take out one of the big shots here,
at least we would've had a little hope.{Halee: I think "If we'd been able to take out one of the big shots here, at least we would've had a little hope." sounds better.}
A mummy?!
We're not mummies!
We're the prisoner gladiators.
Rebecca is one of us too.
We have to keep fighting in the arena
until we're killed for the amusement of the audience.
All because we showed some slight resistance toward the Doflamingo Family.
The king says we can earn our freedom by winning a thousand matches...
but even the most talented fighter would lose if
he was forced to fight to the death a thousand times.
And anyone who tries to escape is shot to death.
There's no way out for us.
Ten years ago, before Doflamingo became king,
colosseum battles weren't fought to the death.
But under his rule, the country has become sharply divided between light and shadow.
I...
will win the tournament today, whatever it takes...
and use the Flame Fruit's power
to kill Doflamingo!
Today, Soldier-san's army
is going to challenge Doflamingo... {Her waist is smaller than Nami's here... seriously, she looks like a concentration camp victim O_O}{Xemnas: Well considering she's a prisoner, and I doubt she gets much money if any at all, I don't think she's fed properly.}
in order to free us.
He intends to sacrifice his own life...
to bring down this kingdom!
It's alright!
Soldier-san is brave...
and he will always watch over you!
I will do it before he can!
I'm tired of always being protected!
This time, I'm going to protect him!
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Soldier?
The toy soldier with one leg.
A toy?
Oh, pardon me old man.
I met a guy like that at the entrance to the colosseum.{The following line doesn't really make sense if he outright says "Oh yeah, I met THAT SPECIFIC GUY". The Japanese line literally just means "someone like that" anyway. -Starfish}
Yeah, that's probably him.
We can't leave this colosseum.
Even if something's going on outside, there's nothing we can do.
So you're worried about a toy dying?
I think it's stranger that a toy's alive to begin with.
Since you're an outsider,
you probably wouldn't understand.
They're no different from humans like us.
They befriend people who are lonely.
Look after people with no siblings.
And become lovers for the loveless.
We're so close, I don't understand why we can't live together.
Ever since I lost my mother, the last family I had,
Soldier-san's has been there to raise me.
He's like a father to me.
Hmm, so that toy...
Sorry to keep you all waiting!
The broken ring has been replaced!{He specifically says that they've REPLACED it, not repaired the one that was already there. -Starfish}
Your match is about to start, Rebecca.
Hey, what are you doing, Lucy?!
During that scuffle earlier, some food fell on the floor.
Sorry. You spent all the money you had on these,
so I don't want it to go to waste.{This could perhaps stand some trimming down... I just thought the previous translation was a bit confusing so I thought I'd clarify it a bit. -Starfish}
They're still good though, even though they've been on the ground!{Yeah... I still wouldn't eat that personally though. Ah well, you're the one who's gonna have a terrible stomachache later. -Starfish}
You don't look like a prisoner to me.
Let's meet in the finals.
The match is about to start!
Block D participants, to the ring!
Mother!{It was "Mother" and not "Mommy" last episode... Plus as Xemnas points out in the following line, Rebecca does speak in a very formal tone. -Starfish}
Mother, look at all the flowers I picked.
Oh, Rebecca!
Would you like one?
Thank you, I think I'll take one.
This is from mother to you.
Now, let us go.
Yeah.
The Riku Royal Army has set the village on fire!
Please stop!
What has gotten into the king?!
The royal palace... it's burning.
What's happening to this country?
Please keep running, Scarlett-sama!
Who's this midget!? Out of the way!
Keep running!  Get as far as you can!
Mother, I'm hungry.
I know. We haven't had anything to eat for two days.{Indeed it is. The previous and next lines too. They were from 650. So I have replaced them with the lines from 650[timed][editad][TLCed][qced].ass. -Starfish}
Rebecca,
can you manage on your own for a little while?
Promise you won't leave this place.
I'll go get us something to eat.
Okay!
Mother?
I-I couldn't protect her.
I'm sorry, I couldn't protect your mother.
She wanted me to give you this.
She said...
that you were waiting with an empty stomach.
Mother, I'm hungry.
I'll go get us something to eat.
There were blood stains on the staircase.
They must be around here somewhere.
Find them!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Your mother was a very important person.
Did you know that a new king has taken the throne in this land?
He's trying to catch all the important people from before.
Since you're the daughter of your important mother,
they're trying to catch you as well.
I couldn't protect your mother, but I'll protect you with my life.
Until the day you can find true happiness, I'll always be by your side.
I want my mother.
You couldn't protect my mother. I hate you!{Unless there is a very good reason for using third person in reference to the specific character being addressed... We probably should stay away from using third person in reference to the specific character being addressed. -Starfish}
How about this?  How about this?
How about this?
Where are you going, Rebecca?!
I'm going home!
You can't.
The new king has agents waiting for you
in town and at your house.
Doflamingo-sama!
Doflamingo, Doflamingo!
For hundreds of years, the Riku royal family has brought suffering upon this poor country!{ manga: For hundreds of years, the Riku Royal Family have brought nothing but suffering to this poor kingdom! } {Halee: In theory we could remove the comma, unless the "For hundreds of years" is to be emphasized.}
And finally, they've tried to steal what little money their subjects had, just to satisfy their own greed! { manga: In the end, they even had the gall to steal from their own subjects out of greed! }
I'm going to bring wealth to this country!
So toys can work too?
I need the money.
Rebecca!
Boo!
You idiot!
Look at how sturdy I am.
I'm a sturdy and strong super toy!
Soldier-san is brave...
and he will always watch over you.{Exact same phrasing as in the last episode (though he wasn't singing it there... despite the manga clearly indicating that he was supposed to be), so I copy-pasted the translation from there. -Starfish}
It must be cold.
Though I can't feel anything with this tin body of mine.
Does it feel warm?
Yes, it feels very warm.
Soldier-san is valiant...
and he will always watch over you.
How much is the rent for this house?
It's abandoned, so you can just use it.
This area was ransacked by the Riku Royal Army.
So most of the residents have left.
This house is warm.
You should close the window.
No.
There are toys here as well.
Children as well. Go and play with them.
Since people are watching us in this village,
I'll have to abide by the laws for toys.
So I'll have to go to the Toys' House when you go to sleep, but I'll definitely be back before you wake up.
As proof that I'm always by your side,
I'll drop a single flower petal
through the gap in the window every morning.
Good morning, Soldier-san.
Ah, good morning.
She must be an orphan.
So the family won't be a problem.
Rebecca!
She's pretty cute,
so we'll probably get a good price for her.
Rebecca!
Damn you, how dare a toy go against humans!
I'll break you!
Soldier-san!
Rebecca!
Forgive me. I've become a wanted man.
Then we're the same.
Let's look for another house.
I want to live in the same house as you, one day.
I'm gonna teach you how to fight.
That's okay, I've got you to protect me.
And what do you plan to do
if something happens to me?
Mother said that it's bad to hurt people.
I'm teaching you this so that you don't get hurt.
Now come at me.
You were always by my side.
You protected me time and time again.
Here she comes!
Are you ready, everyone?!
Our colosseum's very own beautiful female gladiator.
The phantom princess!
No one gets the audience worked up like she does.
Please don't die, Soldier-san.
I...
Screw you, Rebecca!
Today's the day you die!
The entire Riku family can burn in hell!
Your family is scum!
won't lose!
Why does everyone hate her?
She's a good person!
Screw them, she bought me lunch-
We know!
But Rebecca's grandfather
is hated by the entire country.
He's the previous King.