Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing         Sewil
Raw provider      GS-Raws
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
What a shocking conclusion!
There were roughly twenty competitors still fighting,
but they've all been knocked out mysteriously!
This has never happened in all of the Corrida Colosseum's history!
But in the center of the ring,
I can see the shadow of someone getting up!
Is this the winner?!
Is this the fighter who did this?!
Wha-
R-Rebecca?!
Rebecca is back on her feet!
All the renowned fighters in Block D, the people we expected to win...
are still out cold!
The fourth finalist in the Corrida Colosseum's battle tournament is...
the descendant of Dressrosa's shameful King Riku, the prisoner gladiator...
Rebecca!
Get real!
What kind of trick did you pull, Rebecca?!
Investigate her!
Prisoner Gladiator Lodging
Well done, Rebecca!
What happened?
Who cares how she did it?
The point is, Rebecca's won!
What the hell is this?! What did that wench do to Cavendish-sama?!
There's no way Admiral Orlumbus could lose to that little girl!
Slicing Wind?
The Slicing Wind of Rommel.
You wouldn't know...
about the mysterious tragedy that once befell the kingdom of Rommel.
They say the wind started slashing up people once the night fell.
The Navy was dispatched immediately, but...
quite a few marines were felled by that wind, as well.
In the end, the only thing they learned...
was that the wind was actually a man calling himself Hakuba.
We still haven't managed to capture him.
Even after leaving the Rommel Kingdom, Hakuba has continued causing trouble in other places.
Wherever Hakuba appears, a
certain pirate is always there.
What?
Do you think you can escape me, girl?!
Get out of my way!
There's something strange about him.
He fell asleep?! {Xemnas: Post QC change, changed this to better fit what was being shown as he was awake moments before.}
S-Sleepwalking?
That's right.
Hakuba is in fact an alternate personality that only appears when Cavendish is sleeping.
Because of the crimes Hakuba has committed,
Cavendish was driven out to sea and became a pirate.
He's rather unfortunate, then.
He's not worth pitying!
Cavendish enjoys his situation.
Stop to pity him, and he'll just attack you while your guard's down.
He already was an expert swordsman,
but Hakuba is twice as strong.
Still, the fact that he falls asleep whenever his other personality emerges...
has made him ill-suited for this battle royale.
There's no way Rebecca could win!
She must have used a pistol or something!
She won without cutting down a single opponent.
It's a respectable fighting style.
Besides, she was the only one who saw Hakuba's sword coming.
You can't just chalk that up to dumb luck.
Regardless of her circumstances,
I will not let her have the Flame Fruit.
They've really kept me waiting! Now I finally get to fight!
Dressrosa Royal Palace
Did you see that?
Your granddaughter sure is lucky.
Still, I can't believe both you and your granddaughter competed,
King Riku.
For a former king to seek a Devil Fruit, you must really feel driven into a corner.
Rebecca...
And I must say, your family sure is causing me no end of trouble today.
Even Violet betrayed me.
Is there some sort of anniversary today?
It seems you don't realize...
what your actions this morning meant to us.
Regarding the worldwide announcement of Doflamingo
renouncing his throne and title as a Warlord...
It was a mistake.
The information was incorrect.
I simply had to fight back.
That's all.
I see. So that's why you took action.
But that doesn't explain Viola.
Unlike you, she is cunning.
She would never let her emotions get the better of her.
She must have made a wager.
The promising newcomer who dared to defy me...
The Warlord, Trafalgar Law.
And the man from that powerful bloodline, who caused such a stir two years ago...
Monkey D. Luffy.
That woman hopes their pirate alliance will be enough to bring me down.
But Law is already out of commission,
and when Straw Hat Luffy leaves the Colosseum, he will no longer be human.
As for the other Straw Hats...
I hear that Cyborg Franky is attacking the Toys' House on his own.
It remains to be seen if he can beat my commanders.
The other pieces in play would be...
Pirate Hunter Zoro, Foxfire Kin'emon, Nico Robin and Sogeking.
But they won't even make it to the underground.
I don't know left from right down here, so let's start from the right, please.
At the Foot of the Royal Grounds
The lift is up ahead.
Luffy
in Carp
Zoro
in Cat
Kin'emon
in Frog
Listen up, all of you.
The royal palace, where Doflamingo is,
the Toys' House,
and the trade port where the Smile factory is, are all connected.
So if we go into the royal palace, we can also reach the Toys' House and the factory?
Exactly!
If you want to go to the factory, you'd normally have to go through either the palace or the Toys' House,
but my allies should have gotten in via a secret passage they've been digging.
We should head for the royal palace first.
Very well, I understand.
But I must say, even seeing one right in front of me,
I can hardly believe that such small people could exist.
Yeah, she's like a toy! It's so cool!
Normally, we're not supposed to show ourselves to any big humans outside the royal family.
You Straw Hat Pirates, aka Usolanders, are the only exception!
Usolanders?
Operation SOP is already in motion.
Look, there it is!
The lift that leads up to the royal palace entrance.
You'll have to show the guards a pass if you want to ride the lift...
No problem. I'll just beat 'em up.
You can't!
If you do that, you'll cause a commotion and attract more enemies!
There's somebody there.
Who're you?
Straw Hat Luffy, I take it?
Yup, that's me.
Don't answer!
I've been waiting for you.
I'll take you inside the palace.
Now all that's left is the final!
However...
The four commanders who were meant to participate in the finals are unfortunately unable to do so. {Halee: Shall we put "unfortunately" at the beginning of the sentence (with a comma, of course)?}
But you needn't worry!
Because our Colosseum's hero...
Mr. Diamante...
has been selected to fight in their stead!
Diamante!
Diamante-sama!
To the medical room!
Hurry!
Lucy!
I'm in the finals too!
Lucy?
You're not him.
Hey you!
Show some respect, this man is...
You're Rebecca, right?
I know what you've been through.
Things might get chaotic out there, but I won't harm you.
If you look past the outward appearance...
this country somehow...
reminds me of the one where the three of us grew up.
The Royal Grounds
I have the entry permits.
Lift Leading to the Palace Gates
This lift can take you to the palace gates,
but if you're discovered, it's all over.
And most importantly...
Most importantly?
You're far too suspicious.
That, I did not account for!
Aren't you the woman our cook went off with earlier?
Sanji?
Black Leg.
My precious Violet-chan!
He went off to save your ship, and then...
We know the rest.
Did you tell him that the Sunny was in danger?
And could it be that you gave Sanji-dono the map to the Toys' House that he passed on to me?
Yes, that was me.
Why would you do such a thing?
I was one of Doflamingo's subordinates.
What?! Mingo's?!
She's pretending to work for Doflamingo!
Wicca!
You remember me?
Did you forget about my powers?
I've been watching you the whole time.
I know that you've teamed up with the one-legged soldier who raised Rebecca after my sister died,
and that you're about to start fighting back.
I saw it all! {So does her clairvoyance-powers also allow her to HEAR the things she's spying on? I mean I have to assume so because otherwise it'd be a bit weird that she'd know the details of their plan. -Starfish}
Thank you for believing in my father.
Viola-sama!
What?!
You're the king's daughter?!
That's in the past.
So if Rebecca is the king's granddaughter...
You're her mom?!
Rebecca is my niece.
She's my sister Scarlett's daughter.
Could this be...
A hidden door?
You were a ninja all along?!
This is an emergency passage known only to the Riku Royal Family.
Not even Doflamingo knows about this place.
What might this giant basket be?
A pulley to carry items. Look.
This place is really tall.
There are stairs as well.{Okay seriously, has Kin'emon been hanging around Legolas from Lord of the Rings lately? Because he sure seems to have picked up a knack for stating the glaringly obvious. -Starfish}
These stairs will take you to the Rampart Tower, where the palace gates are.
Luffy. You should take this stone and go to the top.
Oh, that is an inspired idea.
He can grab the chain at the top and come down with it, and we will get up quickly.
That's crazy.
Alright!
I'm off!
Hurry, Luffy!
Get on board, ninja-woman.
W-What?!
Toys' House
You're such a pain!
Franky...
Rocket...
Shoulder...
Launcher!
Run!
He's too dangerous!
And that pistol on his head is just for show after all!
Senor! Run!
Use your power to dive into the ground!
This is no time to be brushing your teeth with a shoe brush!
What?
I can't...
He's too hard-boiled!
Senor!
This is horrible!
Senor Pink!
Senor!
Why didn't he use his power to escape?
Don't get the wrong idea, kids.
My Swim Fruit power, that allows me to swim freely through the ground and the walls...
... does not exist so that I can escape from my enemies.
I...
swim when I want to.
That's freedom!
B-Brandy?
He's covered in blood, and I'm sure his bones are broken, yet...
He's disinfecting his wounds with brandy!
That's not it!
Senor, the reason you risked your life to take that attack face-on...
was because you've got an immobilized ally lying behind you, right?!
My stomach hurts -in.
Senor!
My heart feels like it's gonna burst!
That was so long ago. I don't even remember.
Hold me, Senor!
Hey Vise, can you stand?
I'm fine -in!
That guy is so hard-boiled.
Ton Ton!
My stomach hurts -in.
I missed again -in.
Donquixote Family (Diamante Army ♦ Officer)
Machvise
You sure are fast -in.
Shut it! What's your super deal?!
Hold it right there!
Cyborg Franky, from the Straw Hat Pirates!
The Navy has got the Toys' House completely surrounded!
What's the Navy doing here?
What? Didn't you know -in?
Another noisy bunch.
The Royal Palace
The Navy has made their move. {Xemnas: It does sound weird, but it represents the 4 suits in trump cards and I don't know what else we could change it to.}
You made the right decision, Fujitora.
The Suit
Chamber
It's not like I'm on your side.
If the Straw Hats, as well as several other suspicious individuals, are on the move...
it is only natural for me to take action.
My men should fight in order to keep civilian casualties to a minimum.
If Straw Hat is truly after your head, he would probably cause major damage.
In that case, stopping him is my justice.
As for you... I'll deal with you later.
What?
I may be a newcomer who was conscripted into the Navy,
but there are things I want to do, now that I have the rank of Admiral.
To completely eliminate the system of the Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea.
There once was an incident when a certain pirate attempted to take over a country.
Had he succeeded, I'm sure that land would have become as shady as this one.
What about the balance between the three great powers?
Who knows? There's no way to tell without actually shattering it.
So...
If you don't behave...
your head will fly, Sir Heavenly Demon.
I feel like you're telling me to kill you while I have the chance.
Don't be hasty. Let's try to play nice for now.
I'm saying I'll protect your kingdom.
Whatever filth may be exposed in this country in the near future...
I won't be able to see it, so you needn't worry.
This is the year the World Council Meeting Reverie will be held. {Well, finally they acknowledged the name of the meeting. Seriously, this thing was mentioned rather frequently back during Fishman Island, but not once was it ever referred to as anything other than "the world council meeting". Even though the name "Reverie" was established in the manga the very first time it was brought up. -Starfish}
For better or worse, the world will change.
It's time for the Corrida Colosseum battle tournament's...
final round!
I made it!
The entire country's eyes will be on this match! The special arena has been prepared!
Now we all wait for the five contestants to enter the arena!
This is where the fun begins.
Alright! Let's go, Marincolosseo!
It's Bartolomeo! Where'd you even get that name from?
Now, the first one to enter is...
It's him!
The rising star of this tournament, our very own Lucy, has arrived!
Watch me, Ace!